 House Vacancy Announcement and Placement Service (HVAPS)
B-235 Longworth House Office Building Washington, D.C. 20515 202-226-5836
Vacancy Bulletins are available for pick-up in
Longworth HOB - B-227 (CAO First Call Customer Service Center) or in the CAO Human Resources Office - Ford HOB 102.
   MEM-513-18
To Subscribe or Unsubscribe to the Vacancy Listserv visit:
http://www.house.gov/content/jobs/
Job Line: 202-226-4504
MEMBER AND COMMITTEE VACANCY LISTING
Week of December 31, 2018
The Office of Congresswoman-Elect Veronica Escobar (TX-16) seeks a Scheduler to begin in the new year. This individual will be responsible for maintaining the Member-Elect's official schedule, travel plans, personal schedule, along with coordinating press interviews, radio and television time with the Press Secretary; legislative briefings and hearings with the Legislative team and other tasks as assigned. This position will also be in charge of coordinating with the district director all district visits. This is NOT AN ENTRY LEVEL position. Prior Capitol Hill experience and previous scheduling and administrative experience (one year in a similar position) is required. Texas, southwest ties and Spanish language proficiency a plus. Women and minority candidates are encouraged to apply. This position will report directly to the Chief of Staff and will require availability by phone and email on weekends and evenings. Please email resume, writing sample and cover letter to tx16resumes@gmail.com with the subject line SCHEDULER APPLICATION.
 Page 1 of 33

MEM-512-18
The Office of Congresswoman-Elect Veronica Escobar (TX-16) seeks a Staff Assistant to start in the new year and join an active office in Washington, DC. Responsibilities will include managing front desk operations, answering phones, sorting mail, coordinating tours, supervising interns, greeting visitors, processing flag requests and other duties as assigned.
This is an entry-level position and prior Hill internship preferred. Successful candidates will be able to adapt to a startup environment and work under tight deadlines. Texas, southwest ties and Spanish language proficiency a plus, women and minority candidates are encouraged to apply. Please email resume, writing sample and cover letter to tx16resumes@gmail.com with the subject line STAFF ASSISTANT APPLICATION.
Progressive New York City Member seeks Legislative Director to oversee and support the Member’s legislative priorities. Responsibilities include providing the Member with vote recommendations, setting legislative priorities and managing staff to achieve them, planning dynamic events to raise awareness of the Member’s actions, writing talking points, liaising with community leaders, and spearheading legislative initiatives within their own portfolio. Ideal candidates will have a strong understanding of housing and immigration policy, an advanced degree, and 3-5 years of legislative experience on Capitol Hill. Strong written and verbal skills are essential as is the ability to work collaboratively in a fast-paced, dynamic environment. This is not an entry-level position and New York City ties are a plus.
Interested parties should email a cover letter and resume to Kendall.Mitchell@mail.house.gov with “Legislative Director” in the subject line. This office is an equal opportunity employer; we do not discriminate on the basis of race, sex, color, age, religion, disability, national origin, uniformed status, sexual orientation, or gender identity or expression.
Rep. Ro Khanna, a very active leader of the Progressive Caucus, seeks a Digital Specialist and Press Aide to create original content in videos, social media and other messaging vehicles to expand the reach of the Member’s vision and priorities. This individual will work collaboratively with the Communications Director in managing the Member’s social media channels (Facebook, Twitter and Instagram) and using the platforms to frequently share content and elevate the Member’s online presence.
The Digital Specialist and Press Aide will work the Communications Director to design and implement a robust communications/digital/social media plan. This individual will be proficient in video/audio production, graphic design and editing. Audio and video clips of various topics and events attended by
 MEM-511-18
 MEM-510-18
Page 2 of 33

 MEM-509-18
the Member will be used to develop creative content for use within videos and online communications distributed by the office.
Successful candidates will possess at least two years of relevant video experience in a legislative office, political organization or progressive advocacy group; proficiency in video filming, editing and graphic design software; knowledge of live-streaming platforms, digital trends and developments in media; and strong organizational, time-management, problem-solving and story-telling skills. After hours and weekend responsiveness will be required.
Qualified candidates should include in their application: resume, cover letter, two writing samples, three graphic design samples and links to three samples of video work. Please apply to RepRoKhannaCA17@gmail.com, applications will be accepted on a rolling basis.
Press/Digital Assistant – Progressive Democrat and Senior Member of the House Judiciary Committee is seeking a Press/Digital Assistant to work closely with the Communications Director to elevate the Member’s communications operation. Duties will include monitoring and maintenance of the Member’s social media accounts, drafting and posting content for social media, producing graphics and videos, maintaining the website, compiling daily press clips, meticulously proofreading and fact-checking written materials (including letters, social media posts, press releases, newsletters, talking points, and more), creating e-newsletters and franked mailings, creating targeted mailing lists for mass outreach campaigns, and other responsibilities assigned. The ideal candidate will be organized, detail- oriented, tech-savvy, able to work long hours in a fast-paced environment, have superior writing and proofreading skills and the ability to work closely with a communications and legislative team. Ties to Tennessee’s 9th District, previous congressional or campaign experience, and photography/videography/graphic design skills strongly preferred.
Qualified candidates should submit a cover letter, resume, 2 writing samples, an original graphic and/or video, and sample tweets to tn09jobs18@mail.house.gov. Please write “Press/Digital Assistant” in the subject line. Please be aware this office has a dog. No phone calls, faxes, or walk-ins, please.
 Page 3 of 33

MEM-508-18
Digital Director/Washington Press Assistant – The office of Rep. Debbie Wasserman Schultz seeks an experienced Digital Director and Press Assistant to handle a range of fast-paced media issues, and will report to the Communications Director. Duties will include working with local and national reporters; long-term planning; drafting e-newsletters, social media posts, press releases, op-eds and speeches. This position will be responsible for managing digital media accounts and producing video content. It requires excellent writing skills and an ability to work closely with legislative and district staff. This is a fast-paced work environment, and not an entry-level position. Prior work in another Congressional or Senate office with Florida ties, and graphic design capabilities, are a plus. Interested parties should e- mail a cover letter and resume to FL23ResumeComm@mail.house.gov with the subject line “Digital Director/Press Assistant.” Please save cover letter and resume in a single file (pdf preferred) and name the file “Last name, First name.” This office is an equal opportunity employer; we do not discriminate on the basis of race, sex, color, age, religion, disability, national origin, uniformed status, sexual orientation, or gender identity or expression.
The office of Representative Debbie Wasserman Schultz is seeking an experienced Legislative Director/Counsel to oversee and support the Member’s legislative priorities and all other relevant legislative and policy work.
Responsibilities include advising the Member on all matters in the issue portfolio and advancing legislative proposals; analyzing legislation and drafting vote recommendations and talking points for floor and committee proceedings; staffing the Member in relevant meetings; representing the Member before constituents and stakeholders; and supervising the legislative staff. The ideal candidate will have a law or advanced degree; significant foreign policy and Jewish Community experience; experience advising a Member of Congress, experience managing staff ; experience advancing policy proposals; excellent written and verbal communication skills; and enjoy working in a fast-paced, collaborative environment. Prior work in another Congressional or Senate office with Florida ties is a plus. Interested parties should e-mail a cover letter and resume to FL23Resume@mail.house.gov with the subject line “Legislative Director/Counsel.” Please save cover letter and resume in a single file (pdf preferred) and name the file “Last name, First name.” This office is an equal opportunity employer; we do not discriminate on the basis of race, sex, color, age, religion, disability, national origin, uniformed status, sexual orientation, or gender identity or expression.
 MEM-507-18
 Page 4 of 33

MEM-506-18
The Energy & Commerce Committee, Democratic Staff seeks dedicated, organized and enthusiastic candidates to join the Communications and Technology Subcommittee staff as Professional Staff Member or Counsel. The jurisdiction of the subcommittee includes traditional and emerging communications technologies generally and as they relate to emergency and public safety communications, consumer protection, cybersecurity, privacy, and data security. The subcommittee oversees the Federal Communications Commission, the National Telecommunications and Information Administration, the Office of Emergency Communications in the Department of Homeland Security, and all aspects of the above-referenced jurisdiction related to the Department of Homeland Security.
The position requires the handling of substantive legislative and administrative tasks, including staffing hearings and markups, conducting oversight, and drafting legislation. Qualified candidates must have strong writing, analytical, legislative, and organizational skills; a proven ability to perform under pressure while juggling multiple tasks with competing priorities; a willingness to work long hours and weekends; and sound political judgment. Candidates should have experience working with relevant public interest groups, the FCC, Congress, and industry. Law degree preferred but not required.
All applicants will be considered without regard to race, color, national origin, religion, sex (including marital or parental status), gender identity, disability, or age. Women, minority, and veteran candidates are highly encouraged to apply. Please submit a cover letter, resume, writing sample, and at least two professional references to ecdjobs@mail.house.gov using the subject line C&T PSM/Counsel Candidate.
The Energy & Commerce Committee, Democratic Staff seeks dedicated, organized and enthusiastic candidates to join the Communications and Technology Subcommittee staff as Professional Staff Member or Counsel. The jurisdiction of the subcommittee includes traditional and emerging communications technologies generally and as they relate to emergency and public safety communications, consumer protection, cybersecurity, privacy, and data security. The subcommittee oversees the Federal Communications Commission, the National Telecommunications and Information Administration, the Office of Emergency Communications in the Department
 MEM-505-18
Page 5 of 33

 MEM-504-18
of Homeland Security, and all aspects of the above-referenced jurisdiction related to the Department of Homeland Security.
The position requires the handling of substantive legislative and administrative tasks, including staffing hearings and markups, conducting oversight, and drafting legislation. Qualified candidates must have strong writing, analytical, legislative, and organizational skills; a proven ability to perform under pressure while juggling multiple tasks with competing priorities; a willingness to work long hours and weekends; and sound political judgment. Candidates should have experience working with relevant public interest groups, the FCC, Congress, and industry. Law degree preferred but not required.
All applicants will be considered without regard to race, color, national origin, religion, sex (including marital or parental status), gender identity, disability, or age. Women, minority, and veteran candidates are highly encouraged to apply. Please submit a cover letter, resume, writing sample, and at least two professional references to ecdjobs@mail.house.gov using the subject line C&T PSM/Counsel Candidate.
Events Coordinator/Constituent Liaison: Senior Democratic Member of Congress seeks an energetic, organized, creative, self-starter to join the team of her very active and visible constituent services staff.
The Events Coordinator is also a caseworker who helps constituents with federal issues but spends a good part of the time managing and directing very diverse city-wide and neighborhood events that relate to the Congresswoman’s congressional and constituent responsibilities, including staying on top of everyday events in the Member’s district that keep the community connected to the Member’s work. The Events Coordinator takes the lead in our frequent Norton-In-Your Neighborhood meetings with constituents and in developing major events, among them, the Small Business Fair and Job Fair.
Candidate must be able to handle multiple tasks. The office prizes staff able to think outside the box and work independently while also being available to assist in co-worker projects where necessary or requested. Prior community or event planning experience is desirable. The ideal candidate will have a bachelor’s degree, excellent writing and communication skills, experience interacting with the public and leadership qualities. Candidate must be a
Page 6 of 33

 MEM-499-18
resident of the District of Columbia or willing to move immediately to DC if hired.
Interested applicants should send a resume, cover letter and references to
dc00.nortonresume@mail.house.gov.
This position is open until filled. Salary: based on skill and experience level.
A Maryland Democrat seeks a high-energy, highly-organized, and detail- oriented Constituent Service Representative for his District Office.
PRIMARY RESPONSIBILITIES:
●Provide casework assistance to constituents in a timely and efficient manner; proactively follow up on all open cases until a resolution is reached.
●Answer casework correspondence and verbal communications with constituents.
●Assess local and casework related issues for problems requiring possible legislative action; make recommendations to the District Director.
●Act as liaison with federal, district, and local government agencies, political officials, and other community organizations to form effective relationships for the Member.
●Serve as the official representative for the Member at community events in the District.
●Provide logistical support for scheduled district meetings and events for the Member.
QUALIFICATIONS:
●Thoroughness and careful attention to detail.
●Ability to work well under pressure while juggling multiple tasks with competing priorities.
●Ability to exercise discretion and independent judgment in fulfillment of casework responsibilities.
●Thorough knowledge of agencies and casework processes.
●Strong oral and written communication skills.
●Availability to work long hours, including nights and weekends, if needed. ●Ability to work cooperatively and courteously with others.
●Maryland ties are a plus.
To apply, please email a resume and cover letter to md06.jobs@gmail.com with “Constituent Service Representative” in the subject line. No phone calls or walk ins.
 Page 7 of 33

MEM-498-18
A Maryland Democrat seeks a high-energy, highly-organized, and detail- oriented Field Representative for his District Office.
PRIMARY RESPONSIBILITIES:
●Serve as the official representative for the Member in the community.
●Act as liaison with federal, district, and local government agencies, political officials, and other community organizations to form effective relationships for the Member.
●Monitor and update the Member and District Director on district and local issues of importance.
●Staff and provide logistical support for scheduled district meetings and events for the Member.
●Assess local and casework related issues for problems requiring possible legislative action; make recommendations to the District Director.
●Answer casework correspondence and verbal communications with constituents.
●Provide casework assistance to constituents in a timely and efficient manner; proactively follow up on all open cases until a resolution is reached.
QUALIFICATIONS:
●Thoroughness and careful attention to detail.
●Ability to work well under pressure while juggling multiple tasks with competing priorities.
●Ability to exercise discretion and independent judgment in fulfillment of casework responsibilities.
●Availability to work long hours, including nights and weekends, if needed. ●Ability to work cooperatively and courteously with others.
●Strong oral and written communication skills.
●Thorough knowledge of legislative process.
●Knowledge of all issues and events in the district in which the Member is involved.
●Maryland ties are a plus.
Page 8 of 33

To apply, please email a resume and cover letter to md06.jobs@gmail.com with “Field Representative” in the subject line. No phone calls or walk ins.
 MEM-494-18
Democratic Member is seeking an Alabama-based press secretary with strong written communications skills to handle day-to-day press relations, draft talking points and statements, and implement a comprehensive press strategy. This position reports directly to the Representative’s Capitol Hill- based Communications Director and the Alabama-based District Director. Responsibilities include, but are not limited to, writing speeches and talking points; proofreading content for clarity and grammar, drafting proclamations recognizing constituents and district events; responding to press inquiries; writing and placing op-eds; overseeing and expanding the Member’s social media presence; creating and distributing e-newsletters; and assisting in the planning and execution of district events. Qualified candidates are detail- oriented, have strong proofreading skills and a knowledge of grammar usage, are innovative and self-motivated, and are able to work cooperatively in a team setting. This is not an entry-level position and the ideal candidate has experience in the political or media landscape. Interested candidates should email a cover letter, resume, and brief writing sample to AL07.Resumes@mail.house.gov with “District Press Secretary” in the subject line.
The Office of Congressional Ethics (OCE), an independent, non-partisan investigative entity established by the United States House of Representatives, seeks an attorney with 1-3 years experience to serve as Investigative Counsel. The Investigative Counsel reports to the Staff Director and Chief Counsel and will be responsible for conducting sensitive inquiries into allegations of possible violations of ethical standards of conduct by current Members, Officers and Staff of the House of Representatives and advising the Staff Director and Chief Counsel on legal and policy matters.
Core Responsibilities:
•Review information received by OCE, discern possible violations, and identify facts requiring further investigation
•Plan, organize and conduct investigations regarding allegations and advise the Staff Director and Chief Counsel regarding appropriate evaluation of
 MEM-491-18
Page 9 of 33

cases
•Advise the Staff Director and Chief Counsel on legal issues in matters under investigation and on broader legal and policy issues involved in the operations of OCE
Qualifications:
•Experience auditing large sets of data and providing detailed analysis •Advanced proficiency in development and use of electronic databases, and other
computer skills including knowledge of current information technology tools related to investigations
•Investigative experience in high-profile and sensitive matters; experience with investigations involving public officials is desirable but not required •Strong legal judgment
•Demonstrated ability to conduct and direct complex legal research and present the results in a clear, precise and persuasive manner
•Thoroughness and careful attention to detail
•Strong oral and written communication skills
•Ability to:
owork independently or as part of an investigative team
omanage multiple tasks and projects
owork well under pressure and tight time deadlines
oexercise discretion and independent judgment
Duties:
•Reviewing large sets of data across multiple databases in order to analyze, develop, and provide detailed reports of findings
•Identifying information to substantiate or disprove allegations and assess the likely sources of that information
•Collecting and reviewing documents, electronic media and physical evidence •Interviewing witnesses and subjects
•Preparing memoranda of interviews and reports of investigations •Performing other duties as assigned
Requirements:
•Ability to pass Security Background Investigation to obtain Top Secret clearance
•Graduation from an ABA accredited law school and active bar membership
Applicant Instructions:
Please send cover letter and resume (electronic submissions preferred) to:
Omar S. Ashmawy
Staff Director and Chief Counsel
Page 10 of 33

 MEM-490-18
Office of Congressional Ethics
United States House of Representatives P.O. Box 895
Washington, DC 20515-0895 OCEJOB@mail.house.gov
House Democratic Committee seeks a staffer to work on issues related to federal small business procurement policy. Expertise in Small Business Administration programs, particularly the 8(a) Business Development program and HUBZone program, is required. Candidate must be an outstanding writer, have a demonstrated capacity to generate new ideas, and the proven ability to analyze legislation. This is not an entry level position. A graduate degree is strongly preferred. Exceptional writing and analytical skills are a must. Prior Hill, federal agency, private sector or policy think tank experience is preferred. The office is an equal opportunity employer and encourages candidates from diverse backgrounds to apply. Please send cover letter and resume to hsbcdems@gmail.com with the position name in the subject line.
The Office of Congresswoman Linda Sánchez is seeking to immediately fill a full-time job opening for a Caseworker/ Field Representative based in her District Office.
Position Description
Caseworker: Casework responsibilities involve assisting constituents of the 38th Congressional District resolve problems with federal agencies or find the appropriate state or local contact for non-federal issues. The candidate should be persistent and detail-orientated, and put a priority on facilitating resolutions and expediting priority requests. Knowledge of federal and California state government agencies and experience in customer service will be highly regarded.
Field Representative: Field Representatives are primarily charged with (but not limited to) maintaining, strengthening, and establishing new relationships with local community stakeholders, non-profit organizations, and local elected officials in the 38th Congressional District. This position represents the Member of Congress in assigned areas and keeps the Member of Congress informed on all happenings in those areas. In addition to community
  MEM-489-18
Page 11 of 33

outreach efforts, the Field Representative will be responsible for managing projects and largescale public events.
Minimum Qualifications/Education Required
- Candidate should have graduated from an accredited four-year college or university with a bachelor’s degree.
- Candidate must have a thorough understanding of government agencies and structure (county, state, and federal).
- Strong written, communication, analytical, and organizational skills; an ability to relate well with individuals of diverse backgrounds; impeccable customer service manners; and superior public speaking skills.
- Good computer skills, including proficiency and experience with Microsoft Word, Excel,Outlook, Publisher and Power Point.
- Must be able to work efficiently and effectively as a member of a team, be able to meet strict deadlines, balance multiple projects simultaneously, and work under pressure.
- Candidates should demonstrate a positive attitude, commitment to excellence, upbeat demeanor, flexibility, and sense of humor.
- Candidates should expect weekend, some holidays, and after-hours assignments.
- Salary will depend on the experience of the applicant. Employees will receive health care insurance, 401(k)-style retirement benefits, and other federal employee benefits.
To Apply
Interested applicants should submit their resume and cover letter via email to:
CA38Jobs@mail.house.gov. Please indicate the title of the position in the subject line. No phone
calls or walk-ins accepted.
The Office of the Honorable Linda Sánchez is an equal opportunity employer. All applicants will be considered without regard to
race, color, national origin, religion, sex (including marital or parental status), military status, disability, or age. Pursuant to
current appropriations law, to be employed by a House office in a paid position in the continental United States an individual
must: (a) be a U.S. citizen; (b) be lawfully admitted for permanent residence and seeking citizenship as outlined in 8 U.S.C. §
1324b(a)(3)(B); (c) be admitted as a refugee under 8 U.S.C. § 1157 or granted asylum under 8 U.S.C. § 1158, and have filed a
declaration of intention to become a lawful permanent resident and then a citizen when eligible; or (d) owe allegiance to the U.S.
(i.e., qualify as a non-citizen U.S. national under federal law). Employment is at-will.
 Page 12 of 33

MEM-488-18
Senior Democratic Member seeks a Legislative Assistant in his Washington, D.C. office to develop and plan legislative initiatives and monitor legislative developments on the House floor on assigned issues.
The ideal candidate will be suited to: Track legislation and other developments in his/her assigned issue areas; monitor legislative developments within relevant committees; plan and coordinate co- sponsorship and support of other legislation; monitor legislation on the House floor, provide the Member with information on each vote within their assigned issue areas; draft talking points; perform special projects assigned by the Member, the Chief of Staff, or the Legislative Director; meet with constituent/interest groups.
Please submit a cover letter, resume, and a writing sample to cahilljob8@gmail.com with the position name in the subject line.
Senior Democratic Member seeks a Scheduler/Executive Assistant in his Washington, D.C. office. Duties will include responding to scheduling requests and invitations in a timely and professional manner, working closely with the appropriate staff to gather all information and advance materials, coordinate the Member’s travel and working closely with the Member to manage the Congressman’s schedule. Successful candidates must possess exceptional organizational skills and attention to detail, be able to multi-task, and work in a fast-paced and dynamic office environment. Capitol Hill experience is preferred.
Interested candidates should email and cover letter and resume to cahilljob8@gmail.com with the position name in the subject line.
New York Democrat seeking Legislative Assistant
Seeking a Legislative Assistant to develop and plan legislative initiatives and monitor legislative developments within Committees and on the House floor on assigned issues.
o Tracks legislation and other developments in his or her assigned issue areas and briefs the Member for floor work, work in the district, and outside House- related activities;
 MEM-487-18
 MEM-484-18
Page 13 of 33

 MEM-483-18
o Monitors legislative developments within relevant committees;
o Plans and coordinates co-sponsorship and support of other legislation;
o Monitors legislation on the House floor, providing the Member with information on each vote;
o Writes Floor speeches for the Member;
o If assigned to issues pending before a specific committee, prepares for and attends committee meetings and hearings with or without the Member (i.e., keeps in contact with committee staff and meets with interest groups and constituents with interests in such meetings);
o Acts as a liaison with committee and agency staffs;
o Performs special projects assigned by the Member or Chief of Staff/Legislative Director;
o Meets with constituents and interest groups;
o Provides information on and generates ideas for press, mass mailings, and newsletters;
o Works well under pressure and handles stress;
o Works a flexible schedule including long hours, nights and weekends; and o Performs other duties as assigned.
Three years of congressional staff experience is preferred and/or some period of related experience or training in legislation or equivalent is beneficial. Ties to New York preferred, Upstate New York ties and knowledge beneficial.
Background in committee work preferred, legislative work in the areas of defense, homeland security, agriculture, and healthcare is beneficial.
A bachelor’s degree is required for this position, advanced degree beneficial. Please include resume, writing sample, and three references when replying to nyresume2@gmail.com please put title of position applying for in the subject line of the email.
New York Democrat seeking Legislative Correspondent
The Legislative Correspondent will process and answer all incoming constituent mail, working with the legislative staff to craft appropriate responses in a timely manner. He/ She will track relevant legislation as assigned, following its progress through committee, House floor, Senate and conference committee.
Completion of a four-year college education is preferred for this position. A minimum of one year of experience is required including congressional internship experience.
Excellent writing and proofreading skills.
Proficiency in Microsoft office suite and any CMS systems preferred
Ties to Northeast preferred, with experience in New York beneficial.
Please include resume, writing sample, and three references when replying to
Page 14 of 33

nyresume2@gmail.com please put title of position applying for in the subject line of the email.
 MEM-482-18
House Committee seeks Security Manager to manage classified and sensitive information, briefings, hearings, meetings, security clearances for Members and staff, and Committee SCIF, as well as work effectively with the House Security Office. The ideal candidate will have a TS/SCI clearance with Hill experience. Candidates must have excellent writing and communication skills, be organized and detail-oriented, be able to handle multiple projects simultaneously in a demanding work environment, and be able to interface effectively with Members and staff. Interested candidates should email a cover letter and resume to OversightJobs@mail.house.gov with “Security Manager” in the subject line.
House Committee on Veterans' Affairs Incoming Majority (Democratic) Staff seeks Communications Director to serve as spokesperson and primary communications advisor to the incoming Democratic Chairman. Qualified candidates will have significant on-the-record press experience, a demonstrated understanding of veterans’ issues, superior written communications skills, and a demonstrated ability to craft and execute a strategic communications plan. The office is an equal opportunity employer and encourages women, minorities, and LGBTQ candidates to apply. Veterans are also strongly encouraged to apply. Please submit cover letter and resume to hvactransition@gmail.com with “Communications Director” in the subject line.
Position Summary:
- The Communications Director will serve as the spokesperson and primary communications advisor to the incoming Democratic Chairman. They will be responsible for managing the execution of the committee’s strategic communications plan and overseeing day-to-day press activities, which include responding to media inquiries, booking the Chairman for interviews, pitching news stories to media outlets, working with policy leads to develop core messaging and talking points, and producing press releases, speeches, and op-eds that are at or near finished product. The Communications Director
 MEM-481-18
 Page 15 of 33

will also oversee other Committee press staff.
Essential Job Functions:
-Craft and execute the committee’s strategic communications plan and core message
-Speak to the media on the record, while maintaining a good working relationships with veterans reporters, and pitch members of the press promoting the Chairman’s agenda
- Remain abreast of current legislative and non-legislative issues about which the Chairman may be questioned
-Evaluate current events and news reports across the country for their impact on the Chairman
-Provide ideas and advice on the optics of the Chairman’s actions and legislative activities
-Produce press releases, media advisories, briefing materials, talking points, op-eds, and speeches
-Work closely with Chairman’s personal office staff to get official press statements out the door
-Be innovative, think outside of the box for messaging opportunities, be willing and capable of engaging new media (YouTube, video news platforms like NowThis, podcasts, etc.) as well as traditional press
-Be able to see a thorough press roll out of legislation or high profile committee hearings through completion (including traditional press releases, digital messaging, and story placements)
-Develop proactive press events in conjunction with legislative staff to convey the Chairman’s message and engage key constituencies
-Staff the Chairman at press events
-Oversee the collection and tracking of press clips
-Track communications goals
-Manage communications budget
-Support staff in developing their own communications skills
-Oversee the Press Assistant and Digital Assistant
Qualifications:
-3-4+ years’ experience as a Communications Director, Press Secretary, or similar public relations role
-Ability to engage with stakeholders/VSOs to get the Chairman’s/Committee message out there and keep the public informed and work hand in hand with policy team to move legislative priorities forward.
-Experience crafting and executing an effective, fast-paced communications strategy
-Previous on-the-record press experience
-Superior writing, editing, and proofing skills
-Demonstrated ability to dissect complex topics and make them relevant to a wide audience
-Previous military service and/or strong familiarity with veterans’ issues
Page 16 of 33

MEM-480-18
-Willing to execute day-to-day tasks and work successfully within a team -Ability to work in a fast-paced environment, prioritize tasks, and adapt quickly and easily for rapid response
House Committee seeks experienced Deputy Chief Clerk to manage electronic records and help coordinate logistics for Committee business, including hearings and business meetings. The clerk will also proofread, format, and edit memos, reports, transcripts, and correspondence, draft and send briefing notices, schedule meetings, and manage incoming/outgoing mail. Candidates must have excellent writing and editing skills, be organized and detail-oriented, and be able to handle multiple projects simultaneously in a demanding work environment while interfacing effectively with Members and staff. The ideal candidate will have prior clerking experience and will be able to stand in for Chief Clerk in her absence. Clerks with a TS/SCI clearance are highly encouraged to apply. Interested candidates should e-mail a cover letter and resume to OversightJobs@mail.house.gov with “Deputy Chief Clerk Position” in the subject line.
SENIOR LEGISLATIVE ASSISTANT: Senior Member on the House Committee on Transportation & Infrastructure is seeking qualified candidates to staff the Member’s committee assignment in addition to managing a diverse legislative issue portfolio. Candidates should be accomplished at drafting, advancing, and analyzing legislation, monitoring legislative developments, conducting research, and drafting vote recommendations. Ideal candidates will have strong organizational and time management skills, excellent written and verbal communication skills, and a positive attitude. Paramount is a solid knowledge of the legislative process as well as an ability to work under pressure and meet deadlines in an unpredictable work environment, all while keeping a sense of humor. This is not an entry-level legislative position. 2-3 years of Hill experience strongly preferred. Mid- South ties are a plus but not required. Women and minority candidates are strongly encouraged to apply. Interested individuals should e-mail a resume and 2 recent writing samples (no longer than 2 pages each) to tn09jobs18@mail.house.gov with the following subject line: [First name] [Last Name] – Senior Legislative Assistant. Please be aware this office has a dog. No phone calls, faxes, or walk-ins, please.
 MEM-479-18
 Page 17 of 33

MEM-476-18
New Jersey Representative-Elect seeks Constituent Services Representative to join his NJ03 office. The Constituent Services Representative is a field representative and caseworker on behalf of the Congressman that acts as a liaison to various federal, state and local agencies, assesses problems and finds solutions in a professional manner and screens and refers cases, as appropriate. Ideal candidates will have experience managing casework, be exceptionally well-organized and attentive to detail, have strong oral and written communication skills, excel at time management and be able to maintain good working relationships with the Congressman, staff and constituents. This is not an entry-level position.
Please send resume to nj03resume@gmail.com with the position name in the subject line. The office is an equal opportunity employer and encourages candidates from diverse backgrounds to apply. Phone calls and drop-ins not accepted.
New Jersey Representative-Elect seeks District Director to join his NJ03 office. The District Director is a supervisory position that oversees and manages all district office staff, represents the Congressman in public and private settings, meets with local leaders, elected officials, business and constituent groups, travels regularly throughout the district to keep abreast of local issues and maintains close communications with the Washington, D.C. office. Ideal candidates will have prior political experience in Burlington and Ocean Counties, a thorough understanding of the role of a Congressional office as a liaison to various federal, state and local agencies, experience planning and executing public events and prior experience managing staff. This is not an entry-level position.
Please send resume and cover letter to nj03resume@gmail.com with the position name in the subject line. The office is an equal opportunity employer and encourages candidates from diverse backgrounds to apply. Phone calls and drop-ins not accepted.
 MEM-475-18
 Page 18 of 33

MEM-474-18
New Jersey Representative-Elect seeks Legislative Director to join his D.C. office. The Legislative Director provides policy background and advice to the Member on all legislative areas, manages the legislative staff, helps develop policy positions, prepare for Committee hearings, execute legislative strategy, monitor floor activity and coordinate responses to all legislative mail. Ideal candidates will have prior Hill experience doing policy work, possess strong- writing and organizational skills, work well with others, understand the legislative process and be comfortable working under pressure and on tight deadlines. New Jersey ties are a plus. This is not an entry-level position.
Please send resume and writing sample to nj03resume@gmail.com with the position name in the subject line. The office is an equal opportunity employer and encourages candidates from diverse backgrounds to apply. Phone calls and drop-ins not accepted.
New Jersey Representative-Elect seeks Scheduler to join his D.C. office. The Scheduler manages day-to-day operations of the front office including answering phones, sorting mail, greeting visitors, processing flag and tour requests, drafting correspondence and managing interns. Ideal candidates will have some professional experience, be friendly, very detail-oriented with good time-management skills and able to work in a fast-paced environment. Prior campaign or Hill internship experience preferred. New Jersey ties are a plus. This is an entry-level position.
Please send resume to nj03resume@gmail.com with the position name in the subject line. The office is an equal opportunity employer and encourages candidates from diverse backgrounds to apply. Phone calls and drop-ins not accepted.
New Jersey Representative-Elect seeks Staff Assistant to join his D.C. office. The Staff Assistant manages day-to-day operations of the front office including answering phones, sorting mail, greeting visitors, processing flag and tour requests, drafting correspondence and managing interns. Ideal candidates will have some professional experience, be friendly, very detail- oriented with good time-management skills and able to work in a fast-paced environment. Prior campaign or Hill internship experience preferred. New Jersey ties are a plus. This is an entry-level position.
 MEM-473-18
 MEM-472-18
Page 19 of 33

 MEM-471-18
Please send resume to nj03resume@gmail.com with the position name in the subject line. The office is an equal opportunity employer and encourages candidates from diverse backgrounds to apply. Phone calls and drop-ins not accepted.
New Jersey Representative-Elect seeks experienced Press Secretary to join his D.C. office. The Press Secretary is responsible for developing and executing a media and digital strategy and must have strong writing skills including experience drafting press releases, talking points and op-eds; managing social media and web content; creating and executing press events; and on-the-record experience including pitching stories and working closely with reporters. New Jersey ties are a plus. This is not an entry-level position.
Please send resume and writing sample to nj03resume@gmail.com with the position name in the subject line. The office is an equal opportunity employer and encourages candidates from diverse backgrounds to apply. Phone calls and drop-ins not accepted.
Congressman Elijah E. Cummings seeks applicants for professional staff to manage legislative portfolios on the Committee on Oversight and Government Reform. Candidates should be entrepreneurial self-starters who can translate investigative findings into policy reforms and shepherd legislation through all stages of the legislative process, including drafting, committee and floor consideration, and conference procedures. Advanced degree preferred. Several years of Hill experience and expertise in postal policy, acquisition policy, government management, information technology policy and systems, or regulatory affairs preferred. To apply, send cover letter, resume, references, and writing sample to Oversightjobs@mail.house.gov. Please note “Legislative Positions” in the subject line of the email.
 MEM-468-18
 Page 20 of 33

MEM-465-18
LEGISLATIVE ASSISTANT: Northeast Democrat seeks legislative staffer to handle diverse policy portfolio. Candidates should be accomplished at drafting, advancing, and analyzing legislation, monitoring legislative developments, conducting research, and drafting vote recommendations. Ideal candidates will have strong organizational and time management skills; excellent written and verbal communication skills; positive attitude and disposition suited to the work environment; solid knowledge of the legislative process; and an ability to work under pressure and meet deadlines in an unpredictable work environment. This is not an entry-level legislative position. New Jersey ties are a plus but not required. Women and minority candidates are strongly encouraged to apply. Interested parties should e-mail a cover letter and resume to NJ10resumes@gmail.com with the following subject line: First name Last Name - Legislative Assistant. No phone calls, faxes, or walk-ins, please.
Rep. Elijah E. Cummings is seeking a detail-oriented communications professional to join the staff of Oversight and Government Reform Committee as Deputy Press Secretary. The ideal candidate should be a strong writer, a proactive team player, experienced with local and regional media markets, and able to multi-task in a fast-paced environment. This position reports directly to the Communications Director.
Key Responsibilities
•Assist with press releases, statements, talking points, and other key press documents.
•Monitor press coverage and identify opportunities to disseminate our message to local and regional media markets.
•Build and maintain relationships with key local and regional reporters. •Monitor the press inbox and phone line for media inquiries.
•Manage press for multiple subcommittees.
•Assist with creating digital products for social channels.
 MEM-462-18
Page 21 of 33

 MEM-460-18
•Compile and distribute local and national press clips. •Conduct extensive research.
•Create and maintain press lists.
•Maintain archives on multiple subject matters. •Other duties as assigned.
Minimum Qualifications
•A Bachelor’s degree in Journalism, English, Public Relations, or a closely related field preferred.
•A minimum of two years of media relations and/or social media coordination experience.
•Experience with local and regional media markets.
•A strong ability to research and analyze information.
•A strong ability to perform multiple tasks accurately and efficiently in a fast- paced environment.
•Previous Hill experience a plus.
To Apply
Submit a cover letter and resume to oversightpress@mail.house.gov with Deputy Press Secretary in the subject line. Applications will be accepted until the position is filled. Please, no drop-by applications or phone calls.
Press Assistant
The Energy and Commerce Committee Democratic Staff seeks a motivated and hardworking communications professional to join fast-paced communications team as a press assistant. Responsibilities include drafting news releases, social media posts, op-eds and talking points; designing graphics for both social media and web content; monitoring social media for trending topics; maintaining and updating press lists; and compiling daily press clips. Qualified candidates must have excellent written and oral communication skills, a proven ability to perform under pressure while juggling multiple tasks and sound political judgment. Prior Hill or campaign communications experience, as well as professional social media and digital experience (including graphic design and photo and video editing), is preferred. Women and minority candidates are strongly encouraged to apply. Qualified candidates should submit a cover letter, resume and two writing samples to ecdjobs@mail.house.gov. Please no walk ins or phone calls.
 Page 22 of 33

MEM-459-18
Press Secretary
The Energy and Commerce Committee Democratic Staff seeks a motivated and hardworking communications professional to join fast-paced communications team to manage communications for our Energy and Environment subcommittees. Responsibilities include writing communications materials (news releases, statements, op-eds, and talking points); managing press inquiries; maintaining strong relationships with reporters who cover the committee; and coordinating with the communications staff of committee members. Qualified candidates must have excellent written and oral communication skills; the ability to comprehend and summarize complex legislation quickly; a proven ability to perform under pressure while juggling multiple tasks; and sound political judgment. Candidates should have at least 3 years of experience in a relevant field. Women and minority candidates are strongly encouraged to apply. Prior Hill, energy/environmental communications, or campaign experience is preferred. Qualified candidates should submit a cover letter, resume and three writing samples to ecdjobs@mail.house.gov. Please no walk-ins or phone calls.
Democratic full committee office seeks staff assistant. This individual will be responsible for answering phones, sorting mail, greeting visitors, and other duties as assigned. Interested applicants should possess an outgoing personality, have the ability to multi-task, and possess strong organizational skills. Proficiency in Spanish is required. The office is an equal opportunity employer and encourages candidates from diverse backgrounds to apply. Please send cover letter and resume to hsbcdems@gmail.com with the position name in the subject line.
The Committee on Education and the Workforce, Democratic Staff is currently seeking a Deputy Clerk to assist the Chief Clerk in the 116th Congress. Duties include, but are not limited to archiving and records keeping, notices and circulations, official filings, editing letters and reports, hearing, markup and conference logistics and proceeding, bill drops and floor logistics, redlines, updates to the website, managing intern and fellowship program, maintaining the documents room, updating and maintaining the Committee Calendar and all other duties as assigned. Candidates should possess exceptional organizational skills, be comfortable with public speaking, and have excellent writing and research skills. The Deputy clerk will be required to assume all clerking duties in the absence of the Chief Clerk. Previous congressional experience is highly encouraged. Salary commensurate with experience. Interested applicants should email their cover letter, resume and writing sample to jobs_ewdems@mail.house.gov. To ensure proper identification, please put “DEPUTY CLERK APPLICATION” in the subject line.
 MEM-457-18
 MEM-456-18
 Page 23 of 33

MEM-454-18
House Committee on Judiciary Democrats seek a motivated, creative, digital- savvy strategist to serve as Digital Media Manager. Responsibilities include:
·Developing the Committee’s social media strategy; ·Drafting social media posts;
·Maintaining and updating the website;
·Creating graphics;
·Creating videos;
·Compiling and distributing news clips; ·And working on special projects.
Candidates must have strong writing skills, experience working in digital media, and the ability to work under tight deadlines. Please send a writing and graphic sample, along with a resume and cover letter to HouseJudDemsJob@mail.house.gov. Minorities, women, and LGBTQ persons are strongly encouraged to apply. This is not an entry level position.
New York Congressman is seeking an experienced press secretary to join his DC office. The press secretary is responsible for developing and executing a media strategy, which includes writing press releases, talking points, and op- eds, while also managing the Member's social media pages, web site, pitching story ideas and working closely with reporters. Must have on-the-record experience and strong writing skills. Candidates with NY ties a plus. This is not an entry level position.
Please send resume and writing sample to ny03.resumes@gmail.com. Phone calls and drop-ins not accepted.
 MEM-448-18
 Page 24 of 33

MEM-443-18
Senior Energy and Commerce Democrat seeks a Climate Change and Environment Legislative Assistant. The primary responsibilities for this position will be leading the Member’s existing climate initiatives, identifying new areas for legislative action, and coordinating with other Members and outside stakeholders. Additional duties will be based on experience and include other environmental and natural resources priorities.
This is not an entry level position. Significant experience working on climate policy is required and previous Hill experience is preferred. The ideal candidate will be creative and proactive, possess a strong work ethic, and be able to have fun while maintaining a busy schedule. The office is an equal opportunity employer and encourages candidates from diverse backgrounds to apply. Interested applicants should send a resume, cover letter, and writing sample to seniordemclimatejob@gmail.com.
The Office of Rep. Justin Amash (MI) is seeking a bright, creative, and hardworking staff assistant to join our Washington, DC-based team.
The staff assistant will be responsible for answering phones, processing mail, assisting with constituent requests for information, coordinating tours, drafting correspondence, and other administrative duties and projects as needed. The person also will handle some light press assistant duties, including compiling press clips, monitoring media, drafting e-newsletters and press releases, updating the website, and fielding some media inquiries.
The successful applicant will be personable, organized, and committed to individual liberty, economic freedom, the Rule of Law, and the Constitution. The applicant must possess excellent communication and time-management skills, the ability to exercise sound, independent judgment, and the ability to work cooperatively and courteously with others.
Applicants must have a BA or equivalent. Hill experience is not required.
To apply, please send a résumé, cover letter, and two writing samples to applydc@amash.com. Please include "staff assistant applicant" in the subject line. No walk-in applicants or phone interviews.
 MEM-439-18
 Page 25 of 33

MEM-438-18
Senior Democratic Member seeks a Communications Director to lead a fast- paced press shop. The ideal candidate must be a talented writer, capable of producing speeches, op-eds, floor statements, press responses, briefing memoranda, and talking points under tight timelines. The Communications Director will also manage the Member’s national media profile and coordinate with the Digital Media Manager to implement a robust digital media strategy.
An understanding of the legislative process, an ability to quickly grasp and distill policy issues, and excellent oral and written communications skills are required. The successful candidate will also be a team player who work well with others. This is not an entry-level position. Candidates should have previous Capitol Hill experience and a proven record of securing national press coverage for their boss’ work.
The office is an equal opportunity employer and encourages candidates from diverse backgrounds to apply. Interested applicants should send a resume, cover letter, and writing sample to seniordemcommsjob@gmail.com.
TITLE: Legislative Director
REPORTS TO: Member and the Chief of Staff
CORE RESPONSIBILITIES:
•to advise the Member on all legislative areas;
•to assist in development of policy positions and legislative initiatives; and •to manage and supervise the office's legislative staff.
MINIMUM QUALIFICATIONS:
•at least 3 years of legislative experience;
•at least 1 years of management experience;
•strong academic credentials;
•strong leadership and organizational skills; •excellent oral and written communication skills; •ability to work well under pressure;
•thorough knowledge of the legislative process; and •availability to work long hours and at night.
PREFFERED QUALIFICATIONS
•at least 5 years of legislative experience
•at least 2 years of management experience
•completion of an advanced degree
•experience in and/or knowledge of New York state government and politics; particularly upstate New York
DUTIES:
•ensures that the legislative staff is properly focused on the Member's legislative goals;
•works to formulate positions on legislative issues;
 MEM-437-18
Page 26 of 33

 MEM-436-18
•monitors legislative activity on the House floor and handles long-term and short-term legislative planning for the Member;
•oversees the progression of bills with which the Member is involved as they move from Committee to the floor;
•recommends strategies and tactics on bills and positions; • assigns legislative staff areas of responsibility;
•trains and supervises legislative staff;
•schedules and directs legislative staff meetings;
•meets with groups of key constituents or other office visitors, as necessary; •recommends co-sponsorships of legislation to the Member;
•writes and reviews legislative memos;
•hires legislative staff, with approval of the Chief of Staff/Administrative Assistant and the Member, when necessary;
•oversees activities of the office in the absence of the Chief of Staff/Administrative Assistant;
•maintains up-to-date status reports on all legislation affecting the district, legislation in which the Member is a principal sponsor, or legislation which the Member is a cosponsor;
•monitors and reports on floor action to the Member and the Chief of Staff/Administrative Assistant;
•coordinates responses to all legislative mail;
•assists organizations and constituents in the district with federal matters; and •performs other duties as assigned.
Please respond with position you are applying for in the subject line with resume and writing sample to nyresume2@gmail.com
TITLE: Staff Assistant REPORTS TO: Chief of Staff
CORE RESPONSIBILITIES:
•to answer the telephones;
•to greet visitors to the office;
•to answer constituent requests for general information, tours, and other inquiries;
•to monitor delivery and pickup of materials;
•to maintain front office; and
•to assist with various administrative and legislative duties. •occasionally driving the member to and from events
QUALIFICATIONS:
•minimum of 1 year office experience; congressional internship experience preferred
•professional telephone manner;
Page 27 of 33

 MEM-430-18
•proficiency in word processing;
•excellent organizational and proofreading skills;
•ability to use photocopier, facsimile machine and other office equipment; •ability to work cooperatively and courteously with others; and •availability to work long hours, if necessary.
•valid drivers license
DUTIES:
•answers and screens telephone calls for the Member and other staff members and takes messages;
•greets and screens visitors;
•assists persons who have appointments with the Member or other staff members. Works closely with the Member's Scheduler to ensure that the Member's appointments are on time and that the Scheduler is aware of the visitors' arrival;
•responds to constituent requests for flags, tours and other information; •maintains handout literature regarding the district and the House;
•signs for deliveries and forwards all materials delivered to the office to appropriate staff members in a timely manner;
•maintains the office answering machine or voice mail;
•ensures that requests for assistance are directed to the appropriate staff member in a timely manner;
•writes down visitor opinions, including full name, address, and all relevant information;
•logs in mail;
•tracks library books from the Library of Congress;
•performs general typing and administrative assignments;
•sends, receives, and distributes materials via the facsimile machine; and •performs other administrative and legislative duties as assigned.
Please respond with position you are applying for in the subject line with resume and writing sample to nyresume2@gmail.com
A Southern Democrat seeks a Communications Director to manage an active communications operation. Successful candidates will have superb written and verbal communication skills, be comfortable multi-tasking, have excellent attention to detail, and work well under pressure. Primary responsibilities include (but not limited to) managing press releases, speeches, op-eds, and letters to the editor, and other written material for the Member, managing an active social media presence, managing e-newsletters, and graphic design. The Communications Director will work closely with the Press Assistant and other press team members to finalize press/communication products and strategy. The Communications Director will staff the member during press events, media interviews, and other events
Page 28 of 33

as needed. Candidates must be available nights and weekends as situations require. This is not an entry-level position, experience is required. The office is an equal opportunity employer and diverse candidates are encouraged to apply at nchousejobs@gmail.com.
 MEM-428-18
The House Committee on Small Business (Democratic staff) seeks a staffer to work on issues related to Small Business Administration Entrepreneurial Development programs. Expertise with SBA programs, including Small Business Development Centers, SCORE, Women’s Business Centers, and Veteran’s Business Outreach Centers, is required. Candidate must be an outstanding writer, have a demonstrated capacity to generate new ideas, and the proven ability to analyze legislation. The ideal candidate will have strong communication, writing, and research skills. A graduate degree is strongly preferred. The office is an equal opportunity employer and encourages candidates from diverse backgrounds to apply. Please send cover letter and resume to hsbcdems@gmail.com with the position name in the subject line.
Senior Democrat seeks Legislative Assistant, or Senior Legislative Assistant depending on qualifications, to handle work on the Financial Services Committee and other issues. Candidates should have substantial experience with financial services issues and substantial Congressional experience. The successful applicant will possess strong writing and oral communication skills, work well with others, be comfortable in a fast-paced environment, and understand the legislative process. To apply, please e-mail a cover letter, resume, and three writing samples to financeservicesla@gmail.com. No phone calls or drop-ins please.
 MEM-422-18
 Page 29 of 33

MEM-419-18
Democratic Committee staff seek energetic and entrepreneurial professional to join an active communications office. Duties include but are not limited to: drafting press materials including releases and op-eds; cultivating relationships with the national and trade media; coordinating press conferences and media events; and working with legislative staff to communicate the committee’s policy priorities to local and national audiences. Ideal candidate will have experience working in communications, including working on Capitol Hill, or in government or a campaign environment. Strong writing skills essential. Title and salary commensurate with experience. Position reports directly to office’s Communications Director and consults regularly with Committee’s Deputy Staff Director. The office is an equal opportunity employer and encourages candidates from diverse backgrounds to apply. Please send cover letter, resume and brief writing sample to pressjob1923@gmail.com.
The Committee on Oversight and Government Reform is the principal investigative body for the U.S. House of Representatives. Ranking Member Elijah Cummings seeks to fill a Counsel position on the Democratic staff.
The ideal candidate will be an attorney with several years of investigative or litigation experience. Responsibilities include depositions, transcribed interviews, briefings, and congressional hearings. Candidates with diverse backgrounds and experiences are strongly encouraged to apply. Candidates must have superior attention to detail, work well under pressure, be self- motivated, and possess excellent written and oral communication skills.
Please send a resume and cover letter to oversightjobs@mail.house.gov, with “Counsel” in the subject line. No unsolicited calls, emails, or drop-ins, please.
House Small Business Committee Democrats seek an Economic Policy Staffer to manage a broad policy portfolio including, tax, health, retirement, and other economic issues. Core responsibilities include developing and advancing legislation, planning events on key policy priorities, coordinating hearings, staffing Member, and drafting reports. Exceptional writing and analytical skills are a must. Prior Hill, federal agency, private sector or policy think tank experience is preferred. An advanced degree is a plus. The office is an equal opportunity employer and encourages candidates from diverse backgrounds to apply. Please send cover letter and resume to hsbcdems@gmail.com with the position name in the subject line.
The House Small Business Committee (Democratic staff) seeks a staffer to work on issues related to small business technology, telecommunications, and
 MEM-411-18
 MEM-405-18
 MEM-404-18
Page 30 of 33

 MEM-403-18
trade policy. Candidate must be an outstanding writer, have a demonstrated capacity to generate new ideas, and the proven ability to analyze legislation. This is not an entry level position. A graduate degree is strongly preferred. Exceptional writing and analytical skills are a must. Prior Hill, federal agency, private sector or policy think tank experience is preferred. The office is an equal opportunity employer and encourages candidates from diverse backgrounds to apply. Please send cover letter and resume to hsbcdems@gmail.com with the position name in the subject line.
House Small Business Committee (Democratic Staff) is looking for a proactive, experienced oversight and regulatory counsel. Responsibilities include planning and conducting congressional oversight and advising in policy matters related to oversight of issues within the committee’s jurisdiction. Additional duties include reviewing and monitoring regulatory issues across the federal government as it pertains to small businesses and drafting comments and official correspondence as necessary. Candidates must possess relevant legal experience, excellent research and writing skills, and strong analytical and communication skills. Must also be a team player and able to work well under pressure and with quick deadlines. Experience with congressional oversight and regulations preferred; Hill experience is a plus. J.D. is required; please no recent graduates. This is not an entry level position. The office is an equal opportunity employer and encourages candidates from diverse backgrounds to apply. Please send cover letter and resume to hsbcdems@gmail.com with the position name in the subject line.
The House Committee on Small Business (Democratic staff) seeks a Policy Director to assist in the daily operations and management of policy staff and assist in coordinating committee activities, such as hearings and roundtables. This position involves day-to-day management responsibilities and requires significant management experience. Candidate must be an outstanding writer, have a demonstrated capacity to generate new ideas, the proven ability to work under pressure and tight deadlines, and sound judgment necessary to evaluate matters that arise before the committee. Only candidates with experience and a comprehensive knowledge in the substantive policy areas within the Committee’s jurisdiction will be considered. This is not an entry level position. Previous hill experience is required and an advanced degree is a plus. The office is an equal opportunity employer and encourages candidates from diverse backgrounds to apply. Please send cover letter and resume to hsbcdems@gmail.com with the position name in the subject line.
 MEM-402-18
 Page 31 of 33

       Page 32 of 33

Page 33 of 33
