    MEM-148-14
To Subscribe or Unsubscribe to the Vacancy Listserv visit:
http://www.house.gov/content/jobs/
Job Line: 202-226-4504
MEMBER AND COMMITTEE VACANCY LISTING
Week of March 3, 2014
Congresswoman Renee Ellmers seeks Caseworker/Field Representative for District Office in North Carolina. Applicants must be motivated to serve the 2nd Congressional District of North Carolina and possess a strong work ethic. The Caseworker/Field Representative monitors and updates the Congressman and District Office staff on district and local issues. This position acts as a liaison to federal, district, and local agencies for the Congresswoman and constituents and answers casework correspondence and verbal communications with constituents. Duties also include answering phones and assisting walk-in constituents. Proficiency in Microsoft Office is required, ability to work cooperatively and courteously with others; ability to use good judgment in responding to inquiries and requests; and flexibility in assisting with daily tasks and projects. Experience with, and understanding of U.S. Military and Department of Veterans Affairs structure, the procedures, and policies is preferred. Submit cover letter and resume to Pat.Fitzgerald@mail.house.gov.
The Congressional Research Service, a legislative branch agency within the Library of Congress, is seeking to fill several policy analyst positions across
House Vacancy Announcement and Placement Service (HVAPS)
B-235 Longworth House Office Building Washington, D.C. 20515 202-226-5836
Vacancy Bulletins are available for pick-up in
Longworth HOB - B-227 (CAO First Call Customer Service Center) or in the CAO Human Resources Office - Ford HOB 102.
 LOC-001-14
Page 1 of 3

 MEM-136-14
three of its research divisions.
The Congressional Research Service (CRS) works exclusively for the United States Congress, providing policy and legal analysis to committees and Members of both the House and Senate, regardless of party affiliation. In supporting congressional public policy analysis and information needs, CRS covers the full spectrum of issues before the U.S. Congress. Its highest priority is to ensure that Congress has 24/7 access to the nation’s best thinking on legislative issues.
Applications are now being accepted for the following positions:
 Analyst in Telecommunications Policy
 Analyst in Agriculture Economics
 Analyst/Specialist in Health Care Financing and Insurance
 Analyst in Financial Accounting
 Analyst in Intelligence and National Security
CRS is the public policy research arm of the United States Congress and is fully committed to workforce diversity.
Interested applicants must apply online at http://www.loc.gov/crsinfo.
Freshman Democratic Member of Congress seeks a motivated and detail- oriented Press Secretary. Candidates must possess strong writing skills, creativity, a good sense of humor, strong political judgment, the flexibility to work quickly and carefully under tight deadlines, and the ability to work collaboratively with both DC and district staff to grasp and communicate legislative and local priorities.
Responsibilities include coordinating day-to-day press operations; responding to media inquiries and interview requests; pro-actively pitching stories; organizing earned media events in DC and district; writing press releases, advisories, talking points, op-eds, e-newsletter and speeches; and managing website and social media platforms. The Press Secretary also helps manage a press assistant/special projects coordinator. Prior on-the-record experience, speech writing and Capitol Hill experience strongly preferred.
Qualified candidates should send a resume and cover letter to NM01.Resumes@mail.house.gov with “Press Secretary” in the subject line. No phone calls, faxes or drop-ins, please.
Legislative Correspondent:
Senior Midwest Democrat seeks a Legislative Correspondent to handle issue- specific constituent communications and legislative research. Responsibilities include, but are not limited to, drafting constituent correspondence, tracking
 MEM-127-14
Page 2 of 3

 MEM-125-14
legislation, meeting with constituents and interest groups, briefing the Congressman, and generally supporting the legislative and front office operations. Candidate must be highly dependable, flexible, and have superior organizational and writing skills. Knowledge of the legislative process and Indiana ties a plus. Please send a cover letter, resume, and a short writing sample to in01.resume@mail.house.gov. No calls, faxes, or drop-ins please.
COMMUNICATIONS ASSISTANT— Congressman Dan Kildee (MI-05) is seeking a Communications Assistant in Washington, D.C., to assist with the Member’s external communications efforts. Responsibilities will include drafting media advisories and press releases; collating daily press clips and morning headlines; creating content for the Member’s social media accounts; developing graphic design and drafting constituent mail and managing the constituent mail program.
The ideal candidate will be creative, have excellent written and oral communication skills, strongly proficient with digital and social media platforms, energetic and a detail-oriented team player able to multi-task and produce high-quality work on tight deadlines. Graphic and/or video editing skills are highly preferred. Michiganders are strongly encouraged to apply.
Please e-mail resume, cover letter and two writing samples (no more than 1- page each) to michigan05jobs@gmail.com (subject line should read: Communications Assistant Application). No telephone calls, emails or walk- ins, please.
Democratic Congressional committee seeks experienced tax attorney to advise on tax policy, brief Members and write Committee materials on budget implications of federal tax policies, and work with Congressional and outside experts on revenue options. Requires knowledge of corporate and individual tax policy, strong analytical and quantitative skills, strong written and oral communication skills, attention to detail, and the ability to work effectively under tight deadlines. Hill experience preferred. Email resume, two brief writing samples, and cover letter with subject line “revenue analyst” to revenue.analyst@mail.house.gov -- no phone calls or walk-ins.
 MEM-123-14
 Page 3 of 3
