 House Vacancy Announcement and Placement Service (HVAPS)
B-235 Longworth House Office Building Washington, D.C. 20515 202-226-5836
Vacancy Bulletins are available for pick-up in
in the CAO Human Resources Office - Ford HOB 102.
To Subscribe or Unsubscribe to the Vacancy Listserv visit:
 http://www.house.gov/content/jobs/
Job Line: 202-226-4504
MEMBER AND COMMITTEE VACANCY LISTING
Week of September 23, 2019
  MEM-460-19
The Office of Congresswoman Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez Seeks Staff Assistant in DC Office. Responsibilities include welcoming office visitors; processing flag and tour requests; organizing Member correspondence and incoming mail and phone messages; logging constituent mail and working with the Legislative Correspondent to respond to inquiries; managing and executing the intern program; staffing and driving the Member to events and other duties as assigned.
  MEM-458-19
The ideal candidate will have a solution-oriented personality, a great sense of humor, and the ability to manage a vast but essential portfolio.
Prior congressional experience, familiarity with Fireside, Spanish language skills, and ties to New York's 14th Congressional District are strongly preferred.
All applicants must fill out our online application. Please click here airtable.com/shrE5NCa1g1PR5pXC to access the form! Submission deadline: Friday, September 27th at 5PM
Salary: $52,000 per year
Member of Congress seeks an energetic and self-motivated individual to serve as a District Representative in an active Congressional district office. Duties
Page 1 of 12

 MEM-457-19
include representing the Member of Congress in the community, maintaining positive relationships with constituents, other local elected officials, and business and community leaders and organizations. Additionally, this individual is responsible for handling constituent casework in their assigned issue areas, which includes answering casework correspondence, meeting with constituents, communicating with constituents, and serving as a liaison with federal and local agencies.
Candidates must be able to work quickly in a high pressure environment, meet very tight deadlines, and have exceptional writing and organizational skills. Fluency in Spanish and Southern California ties are a plus but not required. Must be available, as necessary, to work evenings and/or weekend hours.
Please send cover letter, resume, and a short writing sample to: Nina Moussavi, District Director, Nina.Moussavi@mail.house.gov.
This office is an equal opportunity employer and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability, age, or protected veteran status.
Financial Disclosure Counsel (Washington, DC) -- The Committee on Ethics seeks an attorney for the position of counsel in the Financial Disclosure office. The Committee’s financial disclosure counsel are responsible for reviewing financial statements and providing legal advice on a high volume of financial disclosure issues, education and training to Members of Congress and their staff through frequent telephone calls, in-person meetings, and written work product.
This is a non-partisan position which requires the ability to serve all Members of Congress equally and refrain from political or partisan activity. Candidates must possess outstanding analytical and written and oral communication skills, as well as the sound judgment necessary to evaluate the sensitive matters that arise before the Committee. Experience in one or more of the following areas is desirable: government ethics, ethics counseling, accounting, auditing, investment management, taxation, corporate finance, and securities law.
Salary commensurate with experience. Please email resume, cover letter, and short writing sample to ethicsjobs@mail.house.gov. Please include the phrase “FD Counsel” in the subject line.
Congressman David Trone (MD06) is seeking a high-energy, highly- organized, and detail-oriented District Staff Member for his offices in Gaithersburg and Frederick, MD.
 MEM-456-19
Page 2 of 12

 MEM-451-19
PRIMARY RESPONSIBILITIES:
●Serve as the official representative for the Member in the community.
●Act as liaison with federal, district, and local government agencies, political officials, and other community organizations to form effective relationships for the Member.
●Monitor and update the Member and District Director on district and local issues of importance.
●Staff and provide logistical support for scheduled district meetings and events for the Member.
●Assess local and casework related issues for problems requiring possible legislative action; make recommendations to the District Director.
●Answer casework correspondence and verbal communications with constituents.
●Provide casework assistance to constituents in a timely and efficient manner; proactively follow up on all open cases until a resolution is reached. QUALIFICATIONS:
●Thoroughness and careful attention to detail.
●Ability to work well under pressure while juggling multiple tasks with competing priorities.
●Ability to exercise discretion and independent judgment in fulfillment of casework responsibilities.
●Availability to work long hours, including nights and weekends, if needed. ●Ability to work cooperatively and courteously with others.
●Strong oral and written communication skills.
●Thorough knowledge of legislative process.
●Knowledge of all issues and events in the district in which the Member is involved.
●Maryland ties are a plus.
To apply, please email a resume and cover letter to md06.jobs@gmail.com with “District Staff” in the subject line. No phone calls or walk ins.
The House Judiciary Committee Democratic Staff seeks a Parliamentarian to advise the Chairman during Judiciary Committee proceedings. Responsibilities include assisting in all aspects of preparation for Committee hearings and markups; staffing hearings and serving as a resource to all Members of the Committee; ensuring all legislative materials for markups and floor consideration are properly prepared and comply with House rules and procedures; and working closely with the Chief Clerk to ensure all notice deadlines and reporting requirements are met.
Qualified candidates must have a detailed understanding of House rules and procedures; excellent written and oral communication skills; exceptional organizational skills; a proven ability to perform under pressure; and sound judgment.
Page 3 of 12

 MEM-450-19
The Judiciary Committee is committed to, and benefits from, a diverse staff, and candidates of all backgrounds are encouraged to apply. Qualified candidates should submit a cover letter, resume and writing sample to Job.Jdem@mail.house.gov. Please no walk-ins or phone calls.
Deputy Press Secretary-The House Judiciary Committee Democratic Staff seeks a motivated and hardworking communications professional to join a fast-paced communications team to help manage communications for the full committee and subcommittees.
Responsibilities include drafting communications materials (news releases, statements, talking points, etc.); managing public notices for the Committee and Subcommittee’s work, helping with press inquiries; maintaining media directories of reporters who cover the committee; and coordinating with the Committee’s communications team and staff of committee members.
Qualified candidates must have excellent written and oral communication skills; the ability to comprehend and summarize complex legislation quickly; a proven ability to perform under pressure while juggling multiple tasks; and sound political judgment. Candidates should have at least 2 years of relevant experience. Prior Hill or campaign experience, as well as familiarity with immigration issues is preferred.
The Judiciary Committee is committed to, and benefits from, a diverse staff, and candidates of all backgrounds are encouraged to apply. Qualified candidates should submit a cover letter, resume and three writing samples to Job.Jdem@mail.house.gov. Please no walk-ins or phone calls.
Lead Orange County District Representative for California’s 49th Congressional District
Description: The staffer in this position is responsible for running the Congressman’s Orange County office and leading all Orange County efforts for the district. Among other duties, this team member represents the Member of Congress during local meetings and events and acts as a liaison between the Member of Congress and his constituents and federal, district, and local agencies. Responsibilities include: constituent casework; planning and staffing in-district events, meetings, and site visits; and working closely with the Oceanside District Office and Washington, DC staff on local and assigned policy issues and areas.
Qualifications: Applicants should have a thorough knowledge of California’s 49th district (particularly the Orange County portion), a positive, service- oriented attitude, strong organizational skills, proficiency at prioritizing and managing multiple projects at one time, a capacity to work both
 MEM-448-19
Page 4 of 12

 MEM-444-19
independently and as part of a team, and strong written and oral communications. Preference may be given to residents of the 49th District.
We are an equal opportunity employer and encourage all qualified applicants to apply, including women, people of color, and members of the LGBTQIA community.
To Apply: Please send resume, cover letter, and two writing samples to
ca49.applications@mail.house.gov
Congressman Denny Heck (WA-10) seeks an organized, passionate, team- oriented Staff Assistant for the Washington DC office. Responsibilities include: managing the front office, coordinating tour and flag requests, overseeing the DC internship program, and providing additional office support as needed. While this is an entry-level position, candidates should have excellent oral and written communication skills, great attention to detail, strong time management skills, and a desire to work collaboratively. Washington State ties are preferred.
Qualified applicants should submit a cover letter, resume, and references to Heck.Resumes@mail.house.gov using “Staff Assistant” and their name in the subject line. Please no drop-ins or calls.
The office is an equal opportunity employer. Veterans, women, and minority candidates are strongly encouraged to apply.
The office of Congresswoman Tulsi Gabbard seeks a district based Field Representative/Caseworker in Honolulu, HI with strong organizational and communication skills.
Responsibilities include helping constituents navigate the services provided by the federal government when they need assistance. This position manages constituent casework, participates in community projects and events. Responsibilities also include monitoring and updating the Congresswoman and Chief of Staff on district and local issues. This person acts as a liaison to community groups for the local Hawaii office.
We are seeking applicants to join our fun, team-oriented, hard-working office. The ideal candidate will possess a can-do attitude and will be solutions oriented. He or she will also be an independent worker, a self-starter and will possess the capacity to produce high quality work on short deadlines. He or she will also have a demonstrated ability to communicate effectively with colleagues and superiors in a dynamic work environment.
This is not an entry level position. The selected applicant with be expected to operate in a fast-paced office and requires dedication, close attention to detail
 MEM-444-19
Page 5 of 12

 MEM-442-19
and the ability to think outside the box. Non-traditional work hours, occasional travel are required. Veteran applications are welcome!
Please do not call or drop in to the office, qualified applicants may email a cover letter, resume and two writing samples with “Caseworker” in the email title to: hi02jobs@gmail.com
Congressman Denny Heck (WA-10) seeks an experienced Military Legislative Assistant to manage his work on the House Permanent Select Committee on Intelligence and oversee a portfolio including defense, veterans, and related appropriations. This portfolio is subject to change. This is not an entry-level position. Strong knowledge of defense issues, the NDAA process, and a minimum of two years of substantive legislative experience are required.
Candidates should be team-oriented and share a passion for constituent services. Excellent writing and verbal communication skills are essential. Preference will be given to candidates with an active TS security clearance and Washington State ties.
Responsibilities include drafting hearing statements and questions, working with committee staff, developing legislation, providing vote recommendations and cultivating relationships with organizations, constituents, and other stakeholders including Joint Base Lewis-McChord.
The office considers all applicants without regard to race, color, national origin, religion, sex, gender identity, disability or age. Veterans, women and minority candidates are encouraged to apply.
Qualified applicants should submit a cover letter, resume, and references to Heck.Resumes@mail.house.gov using “MLA” and their name in the subject line. Please no drop-ins or calls.
The Office of Congressman TJ Cox is seeking a full time Press Secretary including additional responsibilities supporting the office mail program. An ideal candidate should be an excellent writer in English and Spanish, and will be responsible for drafting press releases, speeches, and social media content; handling press inquiries; editing audio and video; and helping with creative messaging projects. Mail program responsibilities include supporting the legislative correspondent in drafting materials for office’s mail program with a quick turnaround, researching legislative issues, and drafting constituent correspondence.
Ideal candidates should be highly organized, an excellent writer, energetic, a team player capable of thriving in a fast-paced and rapidly changing environment and have an understanding of the legislative process. Since the
 MEM-440-19
Page 6 of 12

  MEM-437-19
role is significantly focused on communications, an ideal candidate will also have an interest in generating creative outlets for communicating to the Central Valley of California and moving up in the communications world. California ties and Hill experience are preferred; bilingual in Spanish a requirement.
Qualified candidates should submit a cover letter, resume and writing samples to this form: http://bit.ly/TJC_PressSec by 9/30. Direct questions to CA21hiring@gmail.com. No phone calls or drop-ins please. The office is an equal opportunity employer and does not discriminate on the basis of race, national origin, citizenship status, religion, age, disability status, veteran status, sexual orientation, gender identity, or gender expression.
SKILLS AND KNOWLEDGE REQUIRED:
•Bilingual in Spanish – strong Spanish writing skills;
•Familiarity in using cloud-based tools to organize important information; •Knowledge of the legislative process;
•Knowledge of the office procedures that apply to legislative correspondents; •Strong organizational, research, writing and communication skills; •Thoroughness and attention to detail;
•Ability to perform essential job functions above;
•Ability to work cooperatively and courteously with others;
•Temperament to communicate with a variety of personalities in a tactful, pleasant, and professional manner;
•Knowledge of office computer applications; and
•Proficiency in word processing
The Office of Congressman Jimmy Gomez (CA34) seeks an organized, passionate, team-oriented Staff Assistant and Driver for the Washington DC office. Responsibilities include: managing the front office, coordinating tour and flag requests, managing DC internship program, driving the Congressman to and from events, and providing additional office support as needed. While this is an entry-level position, candidates should have excellent oral and written communication skills, great attention to detail, strong time management skills, and an ability to work under pressure to meet tight deadlines. A valid driver’s license, daily access to an automobile and a good driving record are a necessity.
Please send resume and two writing samples to Gomez.Jobs@mail.house.gov with “Staff Assistant” in the subject line. No calls or drop-ins please. Equal Employment Opportunity Employer.
The Office of Congressman Jimmy Gomez (CA34) seeks an organized, passionate, team-oriented Staff Assistant for the Los Angeles office. Responsibilities include: managing the front office, coordinating tour and flag
 MEM-436-19
Page 7 of 12

 MEM-435-19
requests, managing LA internship program, and providing additional office support as needed. While this is an entry-level position, candidates should have excellent oral and written communication skills, great attention to detail, strong time management skills, and an ability to work under pressure to meet tight deadlines.
Please send resume and two writing samples to Gomez.Jobs@mail.house.gov with “Staff Assistant” in the subject line. No calls or drop-ins please. Equal Employment Opportunity Employer.
LEGISLATIVE ASSISTANT – Congresswoman Pramila Jayapal (WA-07), Co-Chair of the Congressional Progressive Caucus, seeks an experienced and enthusiastic Legislative Assistant to cover her work on the House Judiciary Committee, including immigration, constitutional issues, criminal justice, and civil rights and civil liberties. The ideal candidate will have 3-5 years of experience, ideally 2-3 on the Hill, as well as a solid grasp of House procedures and a deep understanding of immigration policy. This is not an entry level position. Candidates with graduate training in law, public policy, or social science are preferred.
Excellent writing, verbal and organizational skills are essential along with the ability to be a self-starter while working in a fast paced environment. Job responsibilities will include drafting legislation, writing hearing statements and legislative memos, and preparing briefing materials.
Equal Employment Opportunity Employer. Women, people of color, new Americans, LGBTQ+ individuals, people with disabilities, and members of other underrepresented communities are strongly encouraged to apply. State and/or district ties are a plus.
Qualified candidates should include in their application: resume, cover letter, and references. Please send applications to jobs.pramila@mail.house.gov with “Legislative Assistant” in the subject line. No calls or drop-ins please.
The House Rules Committee Majority is looking for a talented, creative, and motivated Social Media Manager to join a proactive communications team. Responsibilities include crafting social media posts; designing graphics, GIFs, videos, and other web content; monitoring the committee’s digital channels; updating the website; and compiling daily press clips.
Candidates will ideally have at least 1 year of digital experience, preferably on a campaign or on Capitol Hill, as well as excellent writing and organizational skills and the ability to work under tight deadlines. Experience designing graphics and editing photos and video is required. Fluency in Adobe Creative Suite is preferred.
 MEM-429-19
Page 8 of 12

  MEM-428-19
Must be comfortable working collaboratively to execute a broad communications strategy. This position reports to the Communications Director. The office is an equal opportunity employer and diverse candidates, those with untraditional backgrounds, women, and LGBTQ persons are strongly encouraged to apply.
Qualified candidates should submit a resume, writing sample, and three social content/graphic design samples to DemRules.Jobs@mail.house.gov with “Social Media Manager” in the subject line. No phone calls or drop-bys, please.
Email: cademhouseoffice@gmail.com Position Available: Senior Staff Office/Location: California
Closing Date: Until filled
Salary Level/Range: Commensurate with experience Proposed Starting Date: Immediate
Job Summary:
Qualified candidates should have a minimum of 2 years’ experience managing a team, possess excellent oral and written communications skills, highly organized, meet deadlines, and manage multiple projects. A flexible schedule and ability to travel throughout the district is required.
Equal opportunity employer.
Interested applicants should submit a cover letter, resume, and writing sample to cademhouseoffice@gmail.com please include Senior Staff in the subject line.
Investigator (Washington, DC) -- The Committee on Ethics seeks an experienced investigative professional for an investigator position. The Committee’s investigator is responsible for assisting the Committee in all aspects of its investigative work, including researching and reviewing public data sources, forensic research, document review, data collection and analysis, preparing for and participating in witness interviews, and drafting and editing Committee documents.
This is a nonpartisan position which requires the ability to assist with impartial investigations and refrain from political or partisan activity. Candidates must possess outstanding organizational, research, and analytical skills, as well as the sound judgment necessary to evaluate the sensitive matters that arise before the Committee. Experience in one or more of the following areas is desirable: government ethics, criminal law, civil litigation, administrative investigations and adjudications, depositions, or financial accounting. Experience with document review/management platforms and/or online research services (Lexis/Nexis, Westlaw, CLEAR) also preferred.
  MEM-426-19
Page 9 of 12

 MEM-425-19
Salary commensurate with experience. Please email resume, cover letter, and a short writing sample to ethicsjobs@mail.house.gov. Please include the phrase “Investigator” in the subject line.
Midwest Republican Member is seeking an experienced Communications Director to implement a strategic media plan in a fast-paced and results- driven environment. Candidates should have experience with the various media tools available, including: social media, video creation, website, e- newsletters and surveys, talking points/speechwriting, press releases, on-the- record experience and interview prep, and op-ed preparation.
This is not an entry level position. Qualified applicants should send submit their resume, cover letter, and two writing samples to communicationsdirectoropening@gmail.com
The Office of U.S. Representative Pramila Jayapal (WA-07) seeks an experienced, creative and highly motivated Communications Director to serve on the Congresswoman’s senior team.
The Communications Director will:
• Serve as the primary spokesperson for the Congresswoman;
• Develop and maintain strong relationships with reporters, editors, producers, bookers and social media influencers;
• Proactively engage in media outreach, including pitching and fielding press inquiries;
• Manage the development of press releases, speeches and op-eds;
• Oversee an ambitious digital communications program;
• Supervise a Press Secretary and Digital Strategist;
• Prepare and staff the Congresswoman for press events and interviews; and
• Work collaboratively with the District Office to ensure strong local media engagement.
The ideal candidate will be a strong writer and seasoned manager who can think strategically, work collaboratively, and manage an ambitious communications program in a fast-paced setting under tight deadlines. This is a senior position, and will be compensated accordingly.
Women, people of color, LGBTQ+ individuals, new Americans, people with disabilities, and members of other underrepresented communities are strongly encouraged to apply. State and/or district ties are a plus.
Qualified candidates should include in their application: resume, cover letter, three writing samples (including one speech) and three references.
Please send applications to jobs.pramila@mail.house.gov with “Communications Director” in the subject line. No calls or drop-ins please.
 MEM-423-19
 Page 10 of 12

MEM-422-19
The House Committee on Energy and Commerce Democratic Staff (majority) seeks an enthusiastic, motivated, and highly-organized staff assistant for fast- paced committee office.
Responsibilities include tasks associated with a front office such as receptionist duties, answering phones, greeting visitors, ensuring that office and meeting rooms are kept in order; supporting staff in preparations for committee events such as hearings, markups, meetings, and events; delivering documents and obtaining signatures on letters; training and supervising interns; handling and sorting incoming mail, maintaining both digital and paper records and files, maintaining office supplies and mastering basic equipment operations; assisting other staff with research, work product, web content, special projects, and other duties as assigned.
Qualified applicants must possess excellent written and oral communication skills, attention to detail, professionalism, superior time management skills, and an ability to work collaboratively. Hill experience preferred but not required. Please submit a cover letter, resume, and a short writing sample to ecdjobs@mail.house.gov
Constituent Liaison: Senior Democratic Member of Congress seeks a bilingual English/Spanish speaker who is an energetic, organized, creative, self-starter to join the District Office of her very active and visible constituent services staff.
Constituent Services staff assists the Member in responding to constituent issues and problems with federal agencies, staying on top of everyday events in the Member’s district, and keeping the community connected to the Member’s work. Importantly, constituent services staff also assist with neighborhood events and visits community groups in the district.
Candidate must be able to work with patience and skill in resolving the problems of constituents and in handling multiple tasks and issues effectively while making sure federal agencies respond in a timely manner and assuring our office responds promptly to constituent requests and concerns while meeting deadlines. A successful candidate will be able to communicate fluently in Spanish and English, work independently, and think outside the box about various constituent issues and community events. Prior community or casework experience is helpful.
The ideal candidate will have significant experience interacting with the public, excellent writing and communication skills and a working knowledge or strong interest in the District of Columbia and its local government. Candidate must possess a bachelor’s degree and be, or be willing to become, a resident of the District of Columbia.
 MEM-419-19
Page 11 of 12

 MEM-419-19
Interested applicants should send a cover letter, resume, two writing samples and references to: dc00.nortonresume@mail.house.gov
Senior Democratic Member seeks Policy Advisor to serve in personal office and on Committee staff. Position will develop and implement legislative initiatives, conduct oversight and investigations, write floor speeches and committee statements, and handle meetings with constituents and interest groups on behalf of Member.
Portfolio will include financial services, housing, education, small business and tax issues. Prior Hill experience is strongly preferred. Law degree is strongly preferred but will consider other advanced degrees with significant Hill experience.
To apply, please email a cover letter and resume with the words “Policy Advisor” in the subject line to job_09@live.com. Please paste your cover letter in the body of the email – do not send letter as an attachment.
The Office of Rep. Justin Amash (MI-03) is seeking a bright, creative, and self-motivated legislative counsel to join our Washington, DC-based policy team.
The legislative counsel will draft legislation, analyze bills, and meet with constituents concerning policy matters, among other duties. The person will be expected to handle a diverse portfolio of policy issues.
The successful applicant will be a libertarian or classical liberal in the tradition of F.A. Hayek, Henry Hazlitt, and Frédéric Bastiat. The applicant must demonstrate a strong commitment to individual liberty, economic freedom, the Rule of Law, and the Constitution.
The person also must be an excellent writer and clear thinker willing to take on the most serious impediments to a freer, more prosperous America. An individual who prefers staid and steady work or who avoids challenges (and the occasional failure) may be more comfortable elsewhere.
Applicants must have a JD or equivalent. Two years of relevant policy experience is preferred, although Hill experience is not required.
To apply, please send a résumé, cover letter, and two writing samples to applydc@amash.com. Please include "legislative counsel applicant" in the subject line. No walk-in applicants or phone interviews.
 MEM-252-19
 Page 12 of 12
