 House Vacancy Announcement and Placement Service (HVAPS)
B-235 Longworth House Office Building Washington, D.C. 20515 202-226-5836
Vacancy Bulletins are available for pick-up in
Longworth HOB - B-227 (CAO First Call Customer Service Center) or in the CAO Human Resources Office - Ford HOB 102.
   MEM-023-18
To Subscribe or Unsubscribe to the Vacancy Listserv visit:
http://www.house.gov/content/jobs/
Job Line: 202-226-4504
MEMBER AND COMMITTEE VACANCY LISTING
Week of January 16, 2018
Rep. Anthony Brown (MD-04) seeks hardworking, intellectually curious and creative thinker for Legislative Director position. Primary responsibilities include developing, implementing and successfully advancing the office’s legislative agenda while handling policy portfolio in a fast-paced
office. Qualified candidates should have significant Hill experience, previous managerial experience, strong organizational skills and knowledge of legislative procedure. If you enjoy working in a fast-paced, multi-tasking, deadline-oriented dynamic environment, then you should apply. JD or advanced degree in policy and Maryland ties are a plus. Women and minority applicants encouraged to apply. Please send cover letter and resume to: md.jobposting@mail.house.gov with “Legislative Director” in the subject line. No calls or walk-ins, please.
Maryland Democratic Congressman is seeking a Deputy Press Secretary/Digital Manager to work closely with the Communications Director.
  MEM-019-18
Page 1 of 6

 MEM-018-18
Responsibilities include managing social media channels and sharpening Congressman’s digital voice; planning and pitching press events and responding to press inquiries; compiling press clips and media monitoring; writing press advisories, releases and speeches; updating website; taking photographs and making compelling graphics and multimedia content; and helping to develop and execute overall communication strategies.
Ideal candidate will have strong written and verbal skills, be able to work demanding hours in a fast-paced environment, take initiative and display creativity, work well with a team and multi-task, be detail oriented and organized, and have a positive attitude and a sense of humor. Maryland ties, previous congressional or campaign experience, and photography and graphic design skills preferred.
Interested applicants should submit a cover letter describing their fit for the role, resume and if available writing or multimedia samples to md.jobposting@mail.house.gov with “Deputy Press Secretary/Digital Manager” in the subject line. No phone calls or drop-ins, please.
The office of Congresswoman Tulsi Gabbard seeks a Scheduler/Executive Assistant with strong organizational, communication, and writing skills.
Responsibilities will include maintaining the Member’s schedule for the Washington D.C. office; organizing, evaluating and tracking invitations and scheduling requests; and coordinating travel arrangements. In addition, the scheduler/assistant will be responsible for coordinating/drafting the Member’s personal correspondence, arranging and/or providing surface transportation for the Member in DC, coordinating with staff, and other tasks as assigned by the Chief of Staff.
We are seeking applicants to join our fun, team-oriented, and hard-working office. The ideal candidate will possess a can-do attitude, pay high attention to detail, and be solution oriented. He or she will also be an independent worker, a self-starter, and will possess the capacity to produce high quality work on short deadlines. He or she will also have a demonstrated ability to communicate effectively with colleagues and superiors in a dynamic work environment.
This is not an entry level position. The selected applicant will be expected to operate in a fast-paced office and requires dedication and the ability to think outside the box. Opportunities to assist in other legislative areas are also available. Non-traditional work hours, occasional travel are required. Veteran applications are welcome!
  Page 2 of 6

MEM-016-18
Please do not call or drop by to the office, qualified applicants may email a
cover letter, resume and two writing samples with “Scheduler” in the email title to: hi02jobs@gmail.com..
    Maryland Democratic Congressman looking for Constituent Engagement Officer (CEO) to serve as the grassroots extension of the member in his district located in the DC suburbs. They are his “eye and ears” for issues on the ground. They are a consistent presence at events in the district, develops and maintains relationships with local government officials and community leaders. They always reflect well on the member with their responsiveness, professionalism and courteousness. CEOs also provide excellent constituent service through the management of casework in assigned issue areas and work with federal and local agencies to ensure constituents receive a response to their inquiry. They may also be assigned to short-term or special projects, including planning events, authoring correspondence and other related duties. CEOs are hard-working and dedicated team players, committed to the goals of the office and to improving the lives of the residents of the district.
CORE RESPONSIBILITIES:
 • to serve as a local representative for the member in defined geographic areas, which are subject to change based on the needs of the office;
• to manage casework within an assigned portfolio;
• to monitor and update the Member and District Director on district
and local issues;
  MEM-014-18
Interested candidates should submit their resume as soon as possible
to md.jobposting@mail.house.gov. Applications are accepted on a rolling basis.
Southern California Democrat is seeking a Press Assistant to work closely with the Communications Director to elevate the Member’s communications operation.
Duties will include compiling daily press clips, monitoring social media, producing graphics and videos, maintaining the website, managing press lists, meticulously proofreading, and drafting/fact-checking written materials, including briefing memos, social media posts, press statements, newsletters, and talking points.
The ideal candidate will be organized, detail-oriented, have superior writing and proofreading skills, be able to work long hours in a fast-paced and demanding setting, exhibit situational awareness and discretion, have the ability to multi-task without sacrificing quality, work well with a team, be proactive yet humble, and have a sense of humor. Spanish fluency, Southern
Page 3 of 6

 MEM-013-18
California ties, previous congressional or campaign experience, and photography/videography/graphic design skills preferred.
Qualified candidates should submit a cover letter describing their fit for the role, resume, short writing sample, and if available, graphic/video samples, to CA26PressJob@gmail.com with just “Press Assistant" in the subject line. No phone calls, faxes, or drop-ins, please.
Conservative southeastern office is hiring a legislative
correspondent. Responsibilities include a small issue portfolio, responding to constituent mail, overseeing a top-tier 499 program, maintaining organization and records for legislative team, as well as hiring and training interns. Successful candidates need not have Hill experience, but will need to demonstrate reasonable knowledge of public policy and movement conservative philosophy, excellence in writing, skillful argument development, and a commitment to achievement on Capitol Hill. If interested, send resume and various writing samples to southeastcongress2018@gmail.com.
The Majority staff of the House Committee on Homeland Security is seeking a Professional Staff Member. Requirements include:
• Extensive knowledge of the Department of Homeland Security including, but not limited to:
 Acquisition and procurement policy and practices  Financial and Information technology management  Departmental workforce
Previous Hill experience is preferred. Please email a resume and writing sample to resumes.CHS@mail.house.gov.
Congressman Ted Lieu has an immediate opening for a Caseworker in his Los Angeles District Office. Primary responsibilities include assisting constituents with federal casework, assisting the Casework Supervisor with casework outreach, intake and processing. The Caseworker would also attend community events and conduct casework outreach directly with constituents. Caseworkers meet frequently with constituents and liaise with federal agencies, and help organize outreach events for the Congressman’s office.
The successful applicant should have experience working on federal casework, must have a positive attitude and the ability to work and set priorities in a fast-paced and challenging environment. Strong writing and verbal communications skills are essential. At least one year of experience working for an elected official or community-based organization is strongly
 MEM-008-18
 MEM-003-18
Page 4 of 6

 MEM-001-18
preferred. A valid California Driver License and automobile are required. Bilingual skills are a plus.
The position is full-time with federal benefits. Congressman Lieu’s primary district office is located in Central Los Angeles.
If interested, please send a resume, cover letter, and two short writing samples no later than January 15, 2018 to:
NICOLAS RODRIQUEZ District Director
Congressman Ted Lieu (CA-33) 5055 Wilshire Blvd., Suite 310 Los Angeles, CA 90036 Lieu.Staff@mail.house.gov
Texas Democrat is seeking an experienced Communications Director to plan and execute a proactive and aggressive media and community outreach strategy. Candidates should have excellent writing skills and work well in a fast-paced collaborative environment. Applicant should also have an extensive social media background. Texas ties and knowledge of TX media and political landscape are a plus and management experience is preferred. This is not an entry-level position. Qualified applicants should submit a resume, cover letter, and two writing samples, including a press release to TXResumeInbox@mail.house.gov.
Senior Democratic House member and Committee Ranking Member seeks Legislative Director. Primary responsibilities include developing policy and legislative initiatives and advising Member on all legislative issues. Position will manage long-term and short-term legislative planning; monitor legislative activity on the House floor; supervise all legislative staff in the personal office; ensure effective coordination between the personal office and committee office; and assist with hearing preparation as needed. Position will also manage health policy portfolio. The successful candidate will be a results-oriented problem solver and have a proven track record of developing and advancing legislation. Excellent oral and written communication skills, time-management skills, and the ability to quickly analyze and summarize complex legislative details are essential. Advanced degree and extensive experience on Capitol Hill are required. To apply, please e-mail a cover letter and resume with the words “Legislative Director” in the subject line to job_09@live.com. Please paste the cover letter and resume directly in the body of the email.
The Committee on Natural Resources’ Subcommittee on Oversight and Investigations is seeking to fill a Clerk position on the majority staff. The ideal candidate should have a strong interest in investigations and natural
 MEM-512-17
 MEM-511-17
Page 5 of 6

 MEM-507-17
MEM-316-17
resources issues. Some responsibilities include staffing Subcommittee hearings as well as some Full Committee hearings, sending and receiving Subcommittee correspondence to and from the Executive Branch as well as with outside organizations, and managing the Subcommittee’s administrative needs. Candidates must possess a strong work ethic, attention to detail, desire to learn how to conduct congressional oversight and investigations, and be self-motivated. Prior Hill experience preferred, but not required. Interested candidates should send a resume and cover letter to NaturalResources.Jobs@mail.house.gov, with “O&I Clerk” in the subject line.
U.S. Rep. Lloyd Doggett (D-Texas) seeks a senior legislative aide with a minimum of three years of Hill experience. This is not an entry level position. Excellent written and oral communication skills required. Advanced degree a plus. Spanish ability a plus. Send resume, brief writing sample, and three references to DoggettJobs@mail.house.gov. Use title on your email: Senior LA Position. No drop-ins please.
The Committee on Oversight and Government Reform is the principal investigative body for the U.S. House of Representatives, and Ranking Member Elijah Cummings seeks to fill a Counsel position on the Democratic staff. The ideal candidate will be a junior attorney (fewer than five years of experience) with a background or strong interest in investigations. Responsibilities include depositions, transcribed interviews, briefings, and congressional hearings. Candidates with diverse backgrounds and experiences are strongly encouraged to apply. Candidates must have superior attention to detail, work well under pressure, be self-motivated, and possess excellent written and oral communication skills. Please send a resume and cover letter to oversightjobs@mail.house.gov, with “Counsel” in the subject line.
    Page 6 of 6
