    MEM-273-14
To Subscribe or Unsubscribe to the Vacancy Listserv visit:
http://www.house.gov/content/jobs/
Job Line: 202-226-4504
MEMBER AND COMMITTEE VACANCY LISTING
Week of July 28, 2014
Western Freshman Democratic Member seeks Deputy Chief of Staff in Washington, D.C. office. This dynamic individual will serve as a senior manager working under the direction of the Member and the Chief of
Staff. The Deputy Chief of Staff serves as the Member's point of contact with interest and advocacy groups based in Washington, D.C. Coordinates with legislative team to proactively identify outreach opportunities with Washington, D.C. based groups. Responsible for staffing the Member in select meetings in Washington, D.C. office. Works with Chief of Staff and Legislative Director to strategically identify legislative and policy opportunities for the Member. Individual will have extensive experience working with interest groups on or off Capitol Hill. Please submit cover letter, resume, and brief writing sample to HouseDCOS2014@gmail.com.
Communications Director – Conservative Southern Republican member is seeking a communications director. Candidate must be organized and have initiative. Excellent communication and writing skills required. Duties include implementing traditional/digital media, communications, and public relations strategies for the member. Southern ties and prior Republican
House Vacancy Announcement and Placement Service (HVAPS)
B-235 Longworth House Office Building Washington, D.C. 20515 202-226-5836
Vacancy Bulletins are available for pick-up in
Longworth HOB - B-227 (CAO First Call Customer Service Center) or in the CAO Human Resources Office - Ford HOB 102.
 MEM-272-14
Page 1 of 6

 MEM-253-14
MEM-245-14
Capitol Hill/political experience preferred. Email resume, cover letter and writing sample of no more than 2 pages to commsdirector2014@hotmail.com.
Texas Member is looking for a knowledgeable communications professional, minimum two years’ experience preferred, responsibilities include development and execution of a comprehensive communication plan, manage and coordinate activities, including media contacts for the Congressman and the office with both DC and District press, weekly newsletter, social media background a strong plus. Please send resume and cover letter to Bob.Haueter@mail.house.gov
Long-serving, southern Republican seeks a Legislative Correspondent to manage busy mail operation. Responsibilities include, but are not limited to, managing high volume incoming constituent correspondence, and providing research for and responses to constituent correspondence in a timely
fashion. An ideal candidate should have superior research and writing skills, thoroughness and attention to detail, good organizational skills, and the ability to work in a fast-paced environment. Candidates should also be team-oriented and demonstrate an ability to collaborate effectively. Intranet Quorum and Capitol Hill experience are required. Familiarity with budget and appropriations process a plus. Interested candidates should send resume, cover letter and writing samples to congressionalofficejobs@gmail.com
Long-serving, southern Republican is seeking a Staff Assistant. Duties include, but are not limited to: staffing front office and greeting visitors, answering phones, coordinating and executing flag and tour requests, supervising interns, assisting with mail processing, and helping with other projects as needed. Strong organizational skills and a positive, team-oriented attitude are required. Previous Capitol Hill or internship experience preferred. Interested candidates should send resume and cover letter to congressionalofficejobs@gmail.com
Congressman Dan Kildee seeks an organized, detail oriented and energetic Scheduler/Executive Assistant for a fast-paced, team-oriented Washington, DC office.
Primary duties include structuring and managing the Member’s daily schedule; coordinating the Member’s travel and logistical details of meetings; handling the Member’s personal correspondence; fulfilling various administrative duties including ethics/disclosure compliance; and, working closely with other staff members in the district and in DC. Additionally, the Scheduler/ Executive Assistant will work to ensure smooth overall office operations.
  MEM-244-14
MEM-243-14
   Applicants must have superior organizational skills, strong oral and written communication skills, strong interpersonal skills, be able to multi-task and
Page 2 of 6

 thrive in a fast paced environment, and have poise, patience and a good sense of humor. The successful candidate will be discreet, politically savvy, self- motivated, and very organized with the ability to successfully interact with different personality types. Additionally, the successful candidate must be a strategic thinker who can navigate competing demands to maximize the Member’s time and come to anticipate the Member’s needs.
 MEM-242-14
Please email a resume and cover letter to Michigan05Jobs@gmail.com with “Scheduler/ Executive Assistant” in the subject line. Prior scheduling and administrative experience strongly preferred and Michigan ties a plus. This is not an entry level position and salary will be commensurate with experience.
District Director, Member of Congress (District Office), Fort Worth TX
The District Director will be responsible for serving in a Congressional District Office in Fort Worth to oversee all district operations. This role will include a variety of different responsibilities including supervision of special projects, working with casework staff as needed, representing the member at a variety of different civic engagements on behalf of the Member and throughout the Congressional District.
Qualifications:
5 – 7 years of management experience preferred;
strong academic credentials;
ability to provide necessary organization, leadership and motivation to manage a House office;
excellent oral and written communication skills;
excellent organizational and interpersonal skills;
thorough knowledge of legislative process and of House organization and procedures; and
the ideal candidate would have significant community involvement throughout the Congressional District in Fort Worth.
Duties:
represents the member or assigns appropriate staff to do so in district as
needed;
manages district office operations;
works with the chief of staff and the Member to develop and implement policy objectives, strategies that pertain to the district operations;
plans, assigns and evaluates work of employees in district offices; speaks to local groups when the Member is unavailable;
some weekend and evening engagements will be required; maintains close communications with the Member, the Washington
              Page 3 of 6

        MEM-226-14
office and committee staff as needed;
travels throughout the district at regular intervals to keep abreast of local concerns;
meets with elected officials and representatives of local groups on behalf of the Member;
schedules meetings with federal and district government agencies as necessary;
responds to constituent telephone calls and mail; and
performs other duties as assigned.
Salary:
Commensurate with experience
To Apply:
Interested applicants should e-mail a résumé and cover letter to
TX12DO.Texas@mail.house.gov
Financial Disclosure Counsel (Washington, DC) -- The Committee on Ethics seeks an attorney for the position of counsel in the Financial Disclosure office. The Committee’s financial disclosure counsel are responsible for reviewing and providing guidance on a high volume of financial disclosure issues, education, and training to Members of Congress and their staff through frequent telephone calls, in-person meetings, and written work product. This is a non-partisan position which requires the ability to serve all Members of Congress equally and refrain from political or partisan activity. Candidates must possess outstanding analytical and written and oral communication skills, as well as the sound judgment necessary to evaluate the sensitive matters that arise before the Committee. Experience in one or more of the following areas is desirable: government ethics, ethics counseling, corporate finance, securities law, and criminal law. Salary commensurate with
experience. Please email resume, cover letter, and short writing sample to ethicsjobs@mail.house.gov. Please include the phrase “FD Counsel” in the subject line.
Investigative Counsel (Washington, DC) -- The Committee on Ethics seeks an experienced attorney for an investigative counsel position. The Committee’s investigative counsel are responsible for conducting investigations and adjudicatory and disciplinary proceedings regarding Members and staff of the U.S. House of Representatives. This is a nonpartisan position which requires the ability to conduct impartial investigations and refrain from political or partisan activity. Candidates must possess outstanding analytical and written/oral communications skills, as well as the sound judgment necessary to evaluate the sensitive matters that arise before the Committee. Experience in one or more of the following areas is desirable: government ethics, criminal law, civil litigation, administrative investigations
 MEM-225-14
Page 4 of 6

 MEM-215-14
and adjudications, depositions, and financial accounting. Salary commensurate with experience. Please email resume, cover letter, and short writing sample to ethicsjobs@mail.house.gov. Please include the phrase “Investigative Counsel” in the subject line.
PRESS SECRETARY:
Ohio Republican House Member seeking press secretary to join
staff. Applicants should be self-starting, hard-working and creative. Must have strong writing and verbal skills and be extremely detail oriented. Background and proven track record in booking national TV interviews preferred. Job responsibilities include: booking proactive press for the member, including national TV interviews, as well as writing press releases, columns, speeches, blogs and e-newsletters. Interested applicants should send cover letter, resume and writing sample to oh.ushouse.job@gmail.com.
The Office of Congresswoman Linda Sánchez is seeking to immediately fill a full-time job opening for a Scheduler based in her District Office.
Position Description
The Scheduler position is primarily charged with (but not limited to) managing Member’s official schedule, travel arrangements, personal correspondence, and various administrative duties. Successful candidates will possess strong communication skills, the ability to multitask, attention to detail, political instinct, the ability to prioritize in a fast-paced environment, work cooperatively and courteously with others; and temperament to communicate with a variety of personalities in a tactful, pleasant, and professional manner.
Minimum Qualifications/Education Required
 Office/administrative experience
 Strong organizations skills; attention to detail.
 Good computer skills, including proficiency and experience with Microsoft
Word, Excel, Outlook, Publisher and Power Point.
 Strong communication, analytical, and organization skills; an ability to
relate well with individuals of diverse backgrounds; impeccable customer
service manners; and superior public speaking skills.
 Candidate must have a thorough understanding of government agencies
and structure (county, state, and federal).
 Must be able to work efficiently and effectively as a member of a team, be
able to meet strict deadlines, balance multiple projects simultaneously, and
work under pressure.
 Candidates should demonstrate a positive attitude, commitment to
excellence, upbeat demeanor, flexibility, and sense of humor.
 Candidates should expect frequent weekend, some holidays, and after-
hours assignments.
Page 5 of 6
 MEM-214-14

 MEM-213-14
 Candidate should have graduated from an accredited four-year college or university with a bachelor’s degree.
 Salary will depend on the experience of the applicant. Employees will receive health care insurance, 401(k)-style retirement benefits, and other federal employee benefits.
To Apply
Interested applicants should e-mail résumé (including salary history) and cover letter to CA38Jobs@mail.house.gov. Please indicate in the title of the position you are applying for in the subject line. No phone calls or walk-ins accepted.
Communications Director ---
Senior Member of Congress is seeking a senior communications professional experienced in working on international issues with domestic and international media. Candidate will be working with bipartisan House and Senate members to creatively promote common international goals and messages using the widest variety of communications tools available. This is a high-level position; three to five years of relevant experience and a successful record of working in Washington on international messaging and communications is essential. Interested applicants should e-mail a resume, cover letter, and 2-3 writing samples to congressionalstaffpositions@gmail.com.
Advisor on International Security Issues ---
Senior Member of Congress seeks advisor on security issues — ideal candidate would have security experience including policing, international law enforcement and cooperation, combatting terrorism, border management, and conflict prevention and resolution. The advisor will follow transnational threats, strategic police matters, border security and management, narcotics smuggling and anti-terrorism. Law enforcement or defense-/homeland security-related experience would be an essential asset. The successful candidate will have a strong commitment to public service, strong writing, speaking and analytical skills, be proactive, resourceful, well-organized, and able to meet deadlines. Individuals must be U.S. citizens and have, or be able to obtain, a Top Secret clearance. Overseas travel will be required. Please e- mail a cover letter and resume to congressionalstaffpositions@gmail.com.
 MEM-212-14
 Page 6 of 6
