 House Vacancy Announcement and Placement Service (HVAPS)
B-235 Longworth House Office Building Washington, D.C. 20515 202-226-5836
Vacancy Bulletins are available for pick-up in
Longworth HOB - B-227 (CAO First Call Customer Service Center) or in the CAO Human Resources Office - Ford HOB 102.
   MEM-013-18
To Subscribe or Unsubscribe to the Vacancy Listserv visit:
http://www.house.gov/content/jobs/
Job Line: 202-226-4504
MEMBER AND COMMITTEE VACANCY LISTING
Week of January 8, 2018
Conservative southeastern office is hiring a legislative
correspondent. Responsibilities include a small issue portfolio, responding to constituent mail, overseeing a top-tier 499 program, maintaining organization and records for legislative team, as well as hiring and training interns. Successful candidates need not have Hill experience, but will need to demonstrate reasonable knowledge of public policy and movement conservative philosophy, excellence in writing, skillful argument development, and a commitment to achievement on Capitol Hill. If interested, send resume and various writing samples to southeastcongress2018@gmail.com.
The Majority staff of the House Committee on Homeland Security is seeking a Professional Staff Member. Requirements include:
• Extensive knowledge of the Department of Homeland Security including, but not limited to:
 Acquisition and procurement policy and practices Page 1 of 4
 MEM-008-18

 MEM-003-18
 Financial and Information technology management  Departmental workforce
Previous Hill experience is preferred. Please email a resume and writing sample to resumes.CHS@mail.house.gov.
Congressman Ted Lieu has an immediate opening for a Caseworker in his Los Angeles District Office. Primary responsibilities include assisting constituents with federal casework, assisting the Casework Supervisor with casework outreach, intake and processing. The Caseworker would also attend community events and conduct casework outreach directly with constituents. Caseworkers meet frequently with constituents and liaise with federal agencies, and help organize outreach events for the Congressman’s office.
The successful applicant should have experience working on federal casework, must have a positive attitude and the ability to work and set priorities in a fast-paced and challenging environment. Strong writing and verbal communications skills are essential. At least one year of experience working for an elected official or community-based organization is strongly preferred. A valid California Driver License and automobile are required. Bilingual skills are a plus.
The position is full-time with federal benefits. Congressman Lieu’s primary district office is located in Central Los Angeles.
If interested, please send a resume, cover letter, and two short writing samples no later than January 15, 2018 to:
NICOLAS RODRIQUEZ District Director
Congressman Ted Lieu (CA-33) 5055 Wilshire Blvd., Suite 310 Los Angeles, CA 90036 Lieu.Staff@mail.house.gov
Texas Democrat is seeking an experienced Communications Director to plan and execute a proactive and aggressive media and community outreach strategy. Candidates should have excellent writing skills and work well in a fast-paced collaborative environment. Applicant should also have an extensive social media background. Texas ties and knowledge of TX media and political landscape are a plus and management experience is preferred. This is not an entry-level position. Qualified applicants should submit a resume, cover letter, and two writing samples, including a press release to TXResumeInbox@mail.house.gov.
 MEM-001-18
 Page 2 of 4

MEM-512-17
Senior Democratic House member and Committee Ranking Member seeks Legislative Director. Primary responsibilities include developing policy and legislative initiatives and advising Member on all legislative issues. Position will manage long-term and short-term legislative planning; monitor legislative activity on the House floor; supervise all legislative staff in the personal office; ensure effective coordination between the personal office and committee office; and assist with hearing preparation as needed. Position will also manage health policy portfolio. The successful candidate will be a results-oriented problem solver and have a proven track record of developing and advancing legislation. Excellent oral and written communication skills, time-management skills, and the ability to quickly analyze and summarize complex legislative details are essential. Advanced degree and extensive experience on Capitol Hill are required. To apply, please e-mail a cover letter and resume with the words “Legislative Director” in the subject line to job_09@live.com. Please paste the cover letter and resume directly in the body of the email.
The Committee on Natural Resources’ Subcommittee on Oversight and Investigations is seeking to fill a Clerk position on the majority staff. The ideal candidate should have a strong interest in investigations and natural resources issues. Some responsibilities include staffing Subcommittee hearings as well as some Full Committee hearings, sending and receiving Subcommittee correspondence to and from the Executive Branch as well as with outside organizations, and managing the Subcommittee’s administrative needs. Candidates must possess a strong work ethic, attention to detail, desire to learn how to conduct congressional oversight and investigations, and be self-motivated. Prior Hill experience preferred, but not required. Interested candidates should send a resume and cover letter to NaturalResources.Jobs@mail.house.gov, with “O&I Clerk” in the subject line.
U.S. Rep. Lloyd Doggett (D-Texas) seeks a senior legislative aide with a minimum of three years of Hill experience. This is not an entry level position. Excellent written and oral communication skills required. Advanced degree a plus. Spanish ability a plus. Send resume, brief writing sample, and three references to DoggettJobs@mail.house.gov. Use title on your email: Senior LA Position. No drop-ins please.
Investigative Counsel (Washington, DC) -- The Committee on Ethics seeks an attorney for an investigative counsel position. The Committee’s investigative counsels are responsible for conducting investigations and adjudicatory and disciplinary proceedings regarding Members and staff of the U.S. House of Representatives. This is a nonpartisan position which requires the ability to conduct impartial investigations and refrain from political or partisan activity. Candidates must possess outstanding analytical and written/oral communications skills, as well as the sound judgment necessary to evaluate the sensitive matters that arise before the Committee. Experience
 MEM-511-17
 MEM-507-17
MEM-490-17
 Page 3 of 4

 MEM-316-17
in one or more of the following areas is desirable: government ethics; criminal law; employment law, including the laws governing sexual harassment in the workplace; civil litigation; administrative investigations and adjudications; depositions; and financial accounting. Salary commensurate with experience. Please email resume, cover letter, and short writing sample to ethicsjobs@mail.house.gov. Please include the phrase “Investigative Counsel” in the subject line.
The Committee on Oversight and Government Reform is the principal investigative body for the U.S. House of Representatives, and Ranking Member Elijah Cummings seeks to fill a Counsel position on the Democratic staff. The ideal candidate will be a junior attorney (fewer than five years of experience) with a background or strong interest in investigations. Responsibilities include depositions, transcribed interviews, briefings, and congressional hearings. Candidates with diverse backgrounds and experiences are strongly encouraged to apply. Candidates must have superior attention to detail, work well under pressure, be self-motivated, and possess excellent written and oral communication skills. Please send a resume and cover letter to oversightjobs@mail.house.gov, with “Counsel” in the subject line.
   Page 4 of 4
