  House Vacancy Announcement and Placement Service (HVAPS)
B-235 Longworth House Office Building Washington, D.C. 20515 202-226-5836
Vacancy Bulletins are available for pick-up in
Longworth HOB - B-227 (CAO First Call Customer Service Center) or in the CAO Human Resources Office - Ford HOB 102.
  MEM-455-15
To Subscribe or Unsubscribe to the Vacancy Listserv visit:
http://www.house.gov/content/jobs/
Job Line: 202-226-4504
MEMBER AND COMMITTEE VACANCY LISTING
Week of January 4, 2016
Ranking Member Louise Slaughter (NY-25) seeks a Legislative
Director. Responsibilities include developing and overseeing the Congresswoman’s legislative agenda, managing a large legislative staff, editing written material, and handling a legislative portfolio, including health and pro-choice issues. Candidates should have at least five years of legislative experience, a deep understanding of legislative process, a passion for public policy, strong writing and communications skills, experience working with external stakeholders, and the ability to work collaboratively. Women and minorities are encouraged to apply. Interested applicants should submit a cover letter and resume to employ@mail.house.gov.
U.S. Member of Congress in New York seeking a Staff Assistant for the D.C. Office. Individuals should demonstrate strong interpersonal skills and ability to manage multiple tasks, possess strong computing skills, and have a solid work ethic. Responsibilities include, but are not limited to, answering and screening telephone calls, organizing and managing the front office, greeting constituents and visitors, preparing and coordinating requests for
 MEM-454-15
Page 1 of 7

 MEM-453-15
tours, congressional proclamations and other recognitions, monitoring deliveries, tracking and managing office supplies and materials, assisting staff with projects, research and assignments. Must be proficient in Microsoft Word, Outlook and Excel and experience with communications or graphic design is desired but not required.
Qualified applicants should send a cover letter, and resume to ResumeNY@mail.house.gov Please be sure to put STAFF ASSISTANT in the subject line.
PLEASE NO WALK-INS OR PHONE CALLS
U.S. Member of Congress in New York seeking a District Caseworker. Congressional District Office is seeking a full time Caseworker. A highly motivated and experienced candidate will be responsible for helping navigate constituents through governmental services, particularly in the policy/issue areas of: immigration, veterans’ affairs, social security, housing, and assessing casework and community outreach activities for matters affecting or warranting potential legislative action.
The successful candidate must possess previous experience in immigration laws, outreach, organizing and case management. Prior experience working for federal, state or local unit of government is a plus. Ideal candidate must have excellent oral and written skills, the ability to work independently and as part of a team, highly organized, self-motivated and able to perform in a fast pace environment. Bilingual/multilingual is a plus. Valid driver’s license desired. Availability for Evening and Weekend assignments is required.
Salary commensurate with experience
Please e-mail resume and cover letter to ResumeNY@mail.house.gov. Please be sure to put CASEWORKER in the subject line.
PLEASE NO WALK-INS OR PHONE CALLS
U.S. Member of Congress in New York seeking a District Representative. Seeking a team player capable of representing the Member and the office of the Congressional district within his/her designated area. Duties for this position include, but are not limited to community outreach activities and public speaking; responding to constituent case work through correspondence, meeting with constituents, as well as, with local businesses, merchants associations, community-based organizations and agencies to assist in navigating the services provided by the federal government. Organizing and participating in community projects and events. Working with the District Director to develop and execute outreach strategies for the district.
Serve as liaison to Community Boards, Precincts Councils and Block
 MEM-452-15
Page 2 of 7

 MEM-451-15
Associations. Attend and speak at meetings and/or events on the Member’s behalf.
Must have extraordinary interpersonal skills, be constituent service oriented, exhibit a professional demeanor and work ethic and have excellent writing skills. Bilingual a plus. We are seeking a highly motivated and organized individual, who is detail-oriented and able to work well under pressure. Valid driver’s license desired. Availability for Evening and Weekend assignments is required.
Salary commensurate with experience.
Please send resume and cover letter to ResumeNY@mail.house.gov Please be
sure to put DISTRICT REPRESENTATIVE in the subject line.
PLEASE NO WALK-INS OR PHONE CALLS
U.S. Member of Congress in New York seeking a Communications Director to develop and implement aggressive communications strategy with local and national media. Ideal applicant is a quick and clean writer, detail-oriented, able to juggle numerous tasks successfully and best under tight deadlines. Responsibilities include writing press releases, speeches, op-eds, talking points, franked mail pieces and newsletters; coordinating interviews with reporters, set up press events and press conferences, developing relationships with the media; implementing district outreach activities (as it relates to press); responding to media inquiries and coordinating the office’s online and social media operations. Requires strong written and oral communication skills, creativity, and the ability to work well with legislative and district office staff. An ideal candidate will possess a minimum of 3-5 years of communications experience, a demonstrated understanding of federal politics and policy and a desire to work in a fast-paced and fluid
environment. Bilingual a plus. Valid driver’s license desired. Availability for Evening and Weekend assignments is required.
Qualified applicants should send a cover letter, resume and three writing samples to ResumeNY@mail.house.gov. Please be sure to put COMMUNICATIONS DIRECTOR in the subject line.
PLEASE NO WALK-INS OR PHONE CALLS
The office of Congressman Brendan Boyle is seeking a Constituent Services
Representative in his Norristown district office beginning in January 2016.
General responsibilities will include working with constituents and federal agencies on individual and community-based issues, answering constituent phone calls, sorting mail, maintaining office files and supply inventories, as well as other administrative tasks as needed.
 MEM-449-15
Page 3 of 7

 MEM-448-15
Successful candidates will have excellent written and oral communication skills, be team oriented and comfortable working both independently and as part of a group. Candidates should be self-starters, able to take and listen to direction and should display a willingness to continuously learn new skills.
Candidates with fluency or strong verbal and written proficiency in Spanish are strongly preferred, and strong working knowledge of or connection with Montgomery County and the 13th congressional district is a plus. Interested candidates should send your resume and cover letter to pa13jobs@gmail.com. Please list “Constituent Services Representative” in the subject line.
The district office of Congressman Brendan Boyle is looking for a Special Assistant/Constituent Service Representative to help coordinate the Member’s in-district events and other logistics, in addition to working with the constituents of the 13th congressional district.
Successful candidates will possess strong oral and written communication skills and a temperament to communicate with a variety of personalities in a tactful, pleasant, and professional manner at all times.
Assistant Duties include (but are not limited to):
 Transporting the Member to in-district and regional events as needed
and ensuring the member is keeping to his schedule at all times.
 Ensuring that the Member has necessary event related materials,
talking points, and other items as needed.
 Coordinating event photo records, taking pictures at events of the
Member.
 Ensuring that the member has all nonspecific event materials available
at all times (business cards, office information).
 Possessing the ability to exercise discretion and independent judgment
with respect to prioritization as related to the member’s schedule and
itinerary within specific events.
 Other miscellaneous tasks as needed.
Office/Constituent Service Duties include (but are not limited to):
 Working with constituents in the district office to resolve or address
issues with various federal agencies or other community problems.
 Answering phones and interacting with constituents via email and
written correspondence.
 Working with other district staff to maintain office filing system.
 Other administrative tasks as needed.
Thoroughness and careful attention to detail, full-time availability, flexible scheduling (including working evenings and weekends on an as-needed basis), ownership of a car and having a valid driver’s license are all required.
Page 4 of 7

 MEM-445-15
Successful applicants will be able to work in a fast paced environment and be able to improvise in a variety of settings. Previous experience working legislative or government affairs is a plus. Candidates with a strong working knowledge of the City of Philadelphia, Montgomery County, personal connections or residency in the 13th congressional district and familiarity with local transportation are strongly preferred. Interested candidates should send your resume and cover letter to pa13jobs@gmail.com. Please list “Special Assistant” in the subject line.
Senior Democratic Member of Congress seeks an energetic, organized, creative, self-starter to join the team of her very active and visible constituent services staff. The Events Coordinator is also a caseworker who helps constituents with federal issues but spends part of the time managing and directing very diverse city-wide and neighborhood events that relate to the Congresswoman’s congressional and constituent responsibilities, including staying on top of everyday events in the Member’s district that keep the community connected to the Member’s work. The Events Coordinator takes the lead to develop major events, among them, the Tax Fair, Small Business Fair, Job Fair, and Black History Month events.
Candidate must be able to handle multiple tasks. The office prizes staff able to think outside the box and work independently while also being available to assist in co-worker projects where necessary or requested. Prior community or event planning experience is desirable. The ideal candidate will have a bachelor’s degree, excellent writing and communication skills, experience interacting with the public and leadership qualities. Candidate must be a resident of the District of Columbia or willing to move immediately to DC if hired.
Interested applicants should send a resume, cover letter and references to: (202) 225-1129 (fax) or to dc00.nortonresume@mail.house.gov. NO PHONE CALLS PLEASE!
This position is open until filled. Salary: based on skill and experience level.
Office of Congressman Paul D. Tonko (NY-20) seeks an enthusiastic, motivated, and highly organized Staff Assistant for the Washington, DC office. Responsibilities include managing front office operations, processing tour and flag requests, overseeing intern program, providing assistance to Office Manager and legislative team, and a wide variety of other tasks. Applicant must have a great sense of humor, strong writing skills, the ability to learn quickly, and a solid team mentality. Finally, a valid driver’s license with daily access to a vehicle and good driving record are preferred.
This is an entry level position. Women, minorities and those with ties to New York’s Capital Region are encouraged to apply. Interested individuals should
 MEM-444-15
Page 5 of 7

 MEM-440-15
email a cover letter, resume, and a short writing sample to ny20resumes@mail.house.gov with “Team Tonko” in the subject line. No phone calls or drop-bys, please.
Congressman French Hill (AR-02) is seeking a Staff Assistant in his Washington, D.C. office beginning immediately. General responsibilities include greeting constituents, answering constituent phone calls, opening and sorting mail, guiding U.S. Capitol building tours, processing flag requests, organizing supplies and inventory, and assisting staff with administrative and legislative tasks.
Candidates will have a positive attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Social media and other communications experience a strong plus. Successful candidates will be self- starters, take and listen to direction, and be able to work both independently and as part of a team.
Applicants should have working knowledge of current events and policy topics as well as a willingness to assist with daily office tasks. Arkansas ties strongly preferred. Those interested please send your resume and cover letter to ar02.applications@mail.house.gov.
Committee on Ethics has an opening for a Staff Assistant. Duties include: answering telephones; assisting with the tracking and processing of committee correspondence; providing administrative support in setting up committee meetings; and entering data and navigating databases with accuracy. This is a non-partisan position which requires the ability to serve all Members of Congress equally and refrain from political or partisan activity. Applicants must have excellent organizational skills and a professional telephone manner; good computer skills; proficiency in Microsoft Word and Excel; ability to work cooperatively and courteously with others; ability to use good judgment in responding to inquiries and requests; and flexibility in assisting with daily tasks and projects.
Please email cover letter and resume with “Staff Assistant” in the subject line to ethicsjobs@mail.house.gov. NO PHONE CALLS PLEASE
Senior Democrat seeks motivated, detail-oriented, and energetic individual with excellent oral and written communication skills for a Staff Assistant position in the Washington, DC office. Individuals should demonstrate strong interpersonal skills, be comfortable with managing multiple tasks, and have a strong work ethic. Responsibilities include managing the front office, answering and screening telephone calls, greeting visitors, coordinating tour requests for visiting constituents, managing flag requests, supervising and coordinating the intern program, and assisting staff. Capitol Hill experience preferred. Women and minorities are encouraged to apply. Email cover letter and resume to employ@mail.house.gov.
 MEM-438-15
 MEM-430-15
 Page 6 of 7

MEM-418-15
Congressman Dan Kildee (MI-05) is seeking a Communications Assistant in Washington, D.C., to assist with the Member’s external communications efforts. Responsibilities will include drafting media advisories and press releases; collating daily press clips and morning headlines; creating content for the Member’s social media accounts; graphic design projects; drafting constituent mail and managing the constituent mail program.
The ideal candidate will be creative, have excellent written and oral communication skills, be strongly proficient with digital and social media platforms, be an energetic and a detail-oriented team player able to multi-task and produce high-quality work on tight deadlines. Graphic and/or video editing skills are highly preferred. Michiganders are strongly encouraged to apply.
Please e-mail resume, cover letter and two writing samples (no more than 1- page each) to michigan05jobs@gmail.com (subject line should read: Communications Assistant Application). No telephone calls, emails or walk- ins, please.
New England Democrat seeks an enthusiastic, motivated, and highly- organized Staff Assistant for Washington, DC office. Responsibilities include managing front office operations, overseeing intern program, serving as confidential assistant to Chief of Staff and Member, driving Member to meetings and appointments, supporting Member’s daily activities, providing assistance to scheduling and legislative teams, and other tasks as assigned. Access to a vehicle and a clean driving record is required. New England ties preferred. Applicants should submit cover letter, resume, and brief writing sample to hill.jobs@mail.house.gov. No phone calls or drop-bys.
 MEM-368-15
 Page 7 of 7
