  House Vacancy Announcement and Placement Service (HVAPS)
B-235 Longworth House Office Building Washington, D.C. 20515 202-226-5836
Vacancy Bulletins are available for pick-up in
Longworth HOB - B-227 (CAO First Call Customer Service Center) or in the CAO Human Resources Office - Ford HOB 102.
  MEM-074-16
To Subscribe or Unsubscribe to the Vacancy Listserv visit:
http://www.house.gov/content/jobs/
Job Line: 202-226-4504
MEMBER AND COMMITTEE VACANCY LISTING
Week of February 22, 2016
Senior Texas Democrat seeks a Legislative Assistant to handle a diverse portfolio of issues including science, technology, research, education, energy, and agriculture. Staffer must be able to handle multiple projects simultaneously in a demanding office environment; must have superior written and oral communications skills; and must be able to interface effectively with the committee staff. Ideal candidate will have prior Capitol Hill or legislative policy experience. This is not a entry-level position. Must send resume with cover letter in order to be considered for this position to txdemjobs@gmail.com. No phone calls or walk-ins please.
The Energy and Commerce Committee Democratic Staff seeks an organized and enthusiastic Outreach and Member Services Coordinator. Responsibilities include planning and executing outreach and member meetings on key issues before the committee, drafting notifications and communications so members, staff and outside organizations are aware of the committee’s actions, and handling administrative tasks to support both the Staff Director and the Director of Communications, Outreach and Member
 MEM-071-16
Page 1 of 9

 MEM-069-16
Services. Qualified candidates must have administrative experience, strong writing and organizational skills , a proven ability to perform under pressure while juggling multiple tasks, and sound political judgment. Women and minority candidates are strongly encouraged to apply. This is not an entry level position, and candidates must have at least two years of relevant experience in a paid position. Please submit a cover letter, resume and a short writing sample to ecdjobs@mail.house.gov. Please no walk-ins or phone calls.
Senior Democratic Member seeks Legislative Assistant. Position will develop and implement legislative initiatives, and monitor legislative developments within Committees and on the House floor; write floor speeches and committee statements; assist with committee investigations, and handle meetings with constituents and interest groups on behalf of Member. Portfolio will include education, veterans’ affairs, DOD, related Appropriations bills, and special projects as assigned. Candidate must be a self-starter and a creative thinker, and must demonstrate attention to detail and exceptional writing ability, and have experience with the legislative process, preferably in a Congressional office. An advanced degree in a related field is also required (JD, MA, etc.).
To apply, please e-mail a cover letter and resume with the words “Legislative Assistant” in the subject line to job_09@live.com. Please paste the cover letter in the body of the email. Do not send the cover letter as an attachment.
New England Democrat seeks an enthusiastic, motivated, and highly- organized Staff Assistant for Washington, DC office. Responsibilities include managing front office operations, overseeing intern program, serving as confidential assistant to Chief of Staff and Member, driving Member to meetings and appointments, supporting Member’s daily activities, providing assistance to scheduling and legislative teams, and other tasks as assigned. Access to a vehicle and a clean driving record is required. New England ties preferred. Applicants should submit cover letter, resume, and brief writing sample to hill.jobs@mail.house.gov. Please include Staff Assistant in the subject line. No phone calls or drop-bys.
Midwestern Democratic Member seeks an energetic, highly organized and detail-oriented Scheduler for the Washington, D.C. and District
Offices. Responsibilities include maintaining the Member’s daily and long- term schedules, coordinating all travel arrangements, and assisting the Member with meeting requests and changes to the calendar. The Scheduler is responsible for communicating and directing D.C. and State staff on the materials needed for meetings/events and the execution of the daily office schedule. Individuals applying for this position should be prepared to have flexible work hours and be able to adapt to a fast-paced and constantly changing environment. Valid Driver’s License and American-made car
 MEM-065-16
 MEM-059-16
Page 2 of 9

 MEM-051-16
strongly preferred. Interested applicants should send a resume and cover letter to mi.schedulerposting@gmail.com. No walk-ins, please.
The Republican staff of the House Committee on Veterans’ Affairs is seeking a full-time press assistant and digital manager in its Washington office. Responsibilities include but are not limited to compiling and monitoring press clips, drafting talking points, press releases, speeches and op-eds, managing the committee website and updating social media. The ideal candidate will possess strong written and verbal communication skills, the ability to work in a fast-paced environment, professionalism and a good sense of humor. Interested candidates should send their cover letter, resume, references and writing samples to curt.cashour@mail.house.gov with “press assistant” in the subject line. No walk-ins please.
Congressman Raul Ruiz, M.D. of California seeks a Caseworker for his district offices. Successful candidates will have previous experience in social work, familiarity with federal agencies, excellent written and oral communication skills, be team-oriented, and comfortable working both independently and as part of a team. Prior experience working for federal, state, or local government is a plus. Candidates with fluency or strong verbal and written proficiency in Spanish are strongly preferred. Strong knowledge or connection with Riverside County and California’s 36th Congressional District is a plus. Availability for evening and weekend assignments is required.
Caseworkers in the Office of Congressman Ruiz assist constituents by navigating complex casework through federal agencies in areas such as veterans’ affairs, social security, housing, immigration. Caseworkers also assess casework and community activities for matters warranting legislative action.
Interested candidates should send their resume and cover letter to Octavio.Gonzalez@mail.house.gov. Please write “Caseworker” in the subject line of your email message.
PLEASE NO WALK-INS OR PHONE CALLS.
The Democratic staff of the U.S Congress Joint Economic Committee (JEC) is seeking an economist/policy analyst with substantive experience in applied microeconomics and public policy research. Duties include working collaboratively with JEC staff on a wide variety of U.S. economic policy issues; researching, writing and editing reports on various federal policies and legislative proposals; proposing ideas for new research topics on issues relevant to current public policy debates; aggregating and analyzing economic data; researching, writing and editing briefing documents for Congressional hearings; advising the Ranking Member and the Staff Director on economic
 MEM-050-16
 MEM-048-16
Page 3 of 9

 MEM-047-16
issues; communicating with House and Senate Committees, federal agencies and think tanks. Basic qualifications: advanced degree in Economics or Public Policy required; Ph.D. level preferred; 2+ years of professional experience in research and data analysis, including applied microeconomics and public policy. Other qualifications: proficiency with STATA and U.S. Census microdata; strong background in applied econometrics; excellent writing skills, with the ability to convey complex policy issues to non-economists; significant understanding of the American political system; Washington experience preferred. To apply, please submit a cover letter and resume to dems@jec.senate.gov with subject line “Economist/Policy Analyst position.” Applicants who are called for an interview will be asked to submit writing samples and a list of references. Position available immediately. Applications will be considered on a rolling basis. Salary commensurate with experience. The Joint Economic Committee is an equal opportunity employer and does not discriminate on the basis of race, color, gender, age, religion, disability, national origin, uniformed service, genetic information, sexual orientation, or gender identity or expression.
Southern Republican office seeking a Press Secretary to implement a comprehensive communications strategy. Responsibilities include working with Legislative team to proactively move message, prepare Member for media events including developing a standard messaging sheet, proactive in identifying new media opportunities, draft press releases, media advisories, newspaper columns, and content for website. Also must be able to implement social media strategy including Facebook, Twitter accounts and website and compile, file and email out media clips. Please e-mail resume to TN08.HouseJobs@mail.house.gov.
Senior Appropriations Democrat seeks candidates for the position of Communications Director for a fast-paced and highly engaged office. The successful candidate will have excellent written and verbal skills, the proven ability to manage multiple communications projects, and the ability to exercise discretion and independent judgment in the representation of the Member’s position on policy issues. S/he will be responsible for coordinating with the legislative team to develop, manage and organize all communications activities, including writing press releases, op-eds, mail pieces, talking points, organizing press events, maintaining the official website, implementing social media strategy, maintaining press database, writing e-newsletters & coordinating Tele-town halls. Duties will also include briefing the Member for interviews, writing and implementing PSAs, interacting with the press as the Member’s principal spokesperson and coordinating the Member’s overall press relations. Position may include limited legislative portfolio. The ideal candidate will have Hill experience, a depth of legislative and policy knowledge including that of the appropriations process, and Ohio connections a benefit. Candidates must be able to work extended hours and under time pressure, while maintaining a positive attitude and demeanor. Please submit
 MEM-044-16
Page 4 of 9

 MEM-042-16
resume, cover letter, two writing samples, and salary requirements to Midwestern.Resume@mail.house.gov. No walk-ins or phone calls.
Southern Republican Member seeks Communications Director to manage and coordinate all communications activities, including media contacts for the Member and the office. Previous Hill experience preferred. Candidate must have strong writing, editing, and oral communication skills. Will act as the formal spokesperson and media liaison for the Member. Knowledge of social media including website maintenance required. Applicants will develop and implement media and communications strategy for the Member and must have an understanding of print and broadcast media. Position will also be responsible for a legislative portfolio.
Email Resume and Cover Letter to: HouseCommsDir@gmail.com
Senior Democrat seeks Communications Director to manage legislative and local press priorities. The applicant must be a hard worker who possesses excellent written, verbal and interpersonal skills. The ideal candidate has Hill and political experience. Qualified applicants should send a cover letter and resume to employ@mail.house.gov.
Northeast Republican in the House seeks a hard-working Press Secretary/Communications Director in Washington, D.C. office to implement a dynamic communications strategy. Duties include performing day-to-day operations of an active press office; managing the website and all social media accounts; developing and generating content for press releases, e-newsletters, talking points, speeches, columns, advertisements, and franked mail; and building press relations with local, regional, and DC press. Candidates must have excellent writing skills, demonstrated abilities in digital media and communication, and previous Hill or campaign experience. Candidates must be able to execute a media and communications plan in line with the unique priorities of the Congressman and views of the district. Send resume, writing sample, cover letter, and salary range to PressRez@gmail.com.
Senior Member of Congress seeks General Counsel – the ideal candidate would have experience in a wide range of legal and administrative, legislative, and ethics issues relevant to a small government agency. Relevant policy experience and advanced degree(s) valued over Capitol Hill or political work. The successful candidate will have a strong commitment to public service, strong writing, speaking and analytical skills, be proactive, resourceful, well-organized, and able to meet deadlines. Individuals must be U.S. citizens and have, or be able to obtain, a Top Secret Clearance. Overseas travel will be required. Please e-mail a cover letter and resume to cscepositions115@gmail.com.
 MEM-029-16
MEM-027-16
  MEM-021-16
 Page 5 of 9

MEM-020-16
Commission on Security and Cooperation in Europe seeks a Global Security/ Political Military Affairs Policy Advisor – Ideal candidate would have experience in areas including: transnational security threats; arms control; monitoring compliance with international instruments; and working with international organizations with a security dimension such as OSCE and NATO. Area studies expertise in Europe and Eurasia is also a plus. Relevant policy experience and advanced degree(s) valued over Capitol Hill or political work. The successful candidate will have a strong commitment to public service, strong writing, speaking and analytical skills, be proactive, resourceful, well-organized, and able to meet deadlines. Individuals must be U.S. citizens and have, or be able to obtain, a Top Secret Clearance. Overseas travel will be required. Please e-mail a cover letter and resume to cscepositions115@gmail.com.
Commission on Security and Cooperation in Europe seeks Middle-Eastern Policy Advisor – the ideal candidate would have extensive and broad experience as a Middle East expert with experience in formulating policies to deal with political movements, security issues, and human rights challenges in the Middle East. Area studies expertise in the Middle East is also a plus as is deep knowledge of Arab cultures and fluency in Arabic language. Relevant policy experience and advanced degree(s) valued over Capitol Hill or political work. The successful candidate will have a strong commitment to public service, strong writing, speaking and analytical skills, be proactive, resourceful, well-organized, and able to meet deadlines. Individuals must be U.S. citizens and have, or be able to obtain, a Top Secret Clearance. Overseas travel will be required. Please e-mail a cover letter and resume to cscepositions115@gmail.com.
Commission on Security and Cooperation in Europe seeks a Russian Policy Advisor – the ideal candidate would have extensive and broad expertise as a Russia expert with experience in formulating policies to deal with both security and human rights challenges posed by Russia. Specific expertise on Russia’s interaction with international organizations such as the OSCE and international instruments such as the Conventional Forces in Europe (CFE) treaty and the Open Skies Agreement are a plus. Area studies expertise in Eurasia is also a plus as is proficiency in Russian and other Eurasian languages. Relevant policy experience and advanced degree(s) valued over Capitol Hill or political work. The successful candidate will have a strong commitment to public service, strong writing, speaking and analytical skills, be proactive, resourceful, well-organized, and able to meet deadlines. Individuals must be U.S. citizens and have, or be able to obtain, a Top Secret Clearance. Overseas travel will be required. Please e-mail a cover letter and resume to cscepositions115@gmail.com.
U.S. Member of Congress in New York seeking a District Caseworker. Congressional District Office is seeking a full time Caseworker. A highly
 MEM-019-16
 MEM-018-16
 MEM-453-15
Page 6 of 9

 MEM-452-15
motivated and experienced candidate will be responsible for helping navigate constituents through governmental services, particularly in the policy/issue areas of: immigration, veterans’ affairs, social security, housing, and assessing casework and community outreach activities for matters affecting or warranting potential legislative action.
The successful candidate must possess previous experience in immigration laws, outreach, organizing and case management. Prior experience working for federal, state or local unit of government is a plus. Ideal candidate must have excellent oral and written skills, the ability to work independently and as part of a team, highly organized, self-motivated and able to perform in a fast pace environment. Bilingual/multilingual is a plus. Valid driver’s license desired. Availability for Evening and Weekend assignments is required.
Salary commensurate with experience
Please e-mail resume and cover letter to ResumeNY@mail.house.gov. Please be sure to put CASEWORKER in the subject line.
PLEASE NO WALK-INS OR PHONE CALLS
U.S. Member of Congress in New York seeking a District Representative. Seeking a team player capable of representing the Member and the office of the Congressional district within his/her designated area. Duties for this position include, but are not limited to community outreach activities and public speaking; responding to constituent case work through correspondence, meeting with constituents, as well as, with local businesses, merchants associations, community-based organizations and agencies to assist in navigating the services provided by the federal government. Organizing and participating in community projects and events. Working with the District Director to develop and execute outreach strategies for the district.
Serve as liaison to Community Boards, Precincts Councils and Block Associations. Attend and speak at meetings and/or events on the Member’s behalf.
Must have extraordinary interpersonal skills, be constituent service oriented, exhibit a professional demeanor and work ethic and have excellent writing skills. Bilingual a plus. We are seeking a highly motivated and organized individual, who is detail-oriented and able to work well under pressure. Valid driver’s license desired. Availability for Evening and Weekend assignments is required.
Salary commensurate with experience.
Please send resume and cover letter to ResumeNY@mail.house.gov Please be
sure to put DISTRICT REPRESENTATIVE in the subject line. Page 7 of 9
 
MEM-449-15
PLEASE NO WALK-INS OR PHONE CALLS.
The office of Congressman Brendan Boyle is seeking a Constituent Services
Representative in his Norristown district office beginning in January 2016.
General responsibilities will include working with constituents and federal agencies on individual and community-based issues, answering constituent phone calls, sorting mail, maintaining office files and supply inventories, as well as other administrative tasks as needed.
Successful candidates will have excellent written and oral communication skills, be team oriented and comfortable working both independently and as part of a group. Candidates should be self-starters, able to take and listen to direction and should display a willingness to continuously learn new skills.
Candidates with fluency or strong verbal and written proficiency in Spanish are strongly preferred, and strong working knowledge of or connection with Montgomery County and the 13th congressional district is a plus. Interested candidates should send your resume and cover letter to pa13jobs@gmail.com. Please list “Constituent Services Representative” in the subject line.
The district office of Congressman Brendan Boyle is looking for a Special Assistant/Constituent Service Representative to help coordinate the Member’s in-district events and other logistics, in addition to working with the constituents of the 13th congressional district.
Successful candidates will possess strong oral and written communication skills and a temperament to communicate with a variety of personalities in a tactful, pleasant, and professional manner at all times.
Assistant Duties include (but are not limited to):
 Transporting the Member to in-district and regional events as needed
and ensuring the member is keeping to his schedule at all times.
 Ensuring that the Member has necessary event related materials,
talking points, and other items as needed.
 Coordinating event photo records, taking pictures at events of the
Member.
 Ensuring that the member has all nonspecific event materials available
at all times (business cards, office information).
 Possessing the ability to exercise discretion and independent judgment
with respect to prioritization as related to the member’s schedule and
itinerary within specific events.
 Other miscellaneous tasks as needed.
Office/Constituent Service Duties include (but are not limited to):
 Working with constituents in the district office to resolve or address
 MEM-448-15
Page 8 of 9

 MEM-440-15
issues with various federal agencies or other community problems.
 Answering phones and interacting with constituents via email and
written correspondence.
 Working with other district staff to maintain office filing system.
 Other administrative tasks as needed.
Thoroughness and careful attention to detail, full-time availability, flexible scheduling (including working evenings and weekends on an as-needed basis), ownership of a car and having a valid driver’s license are all required. Successful applicants will be able to work in a fast paced environment and be able to improvise in a variety of settings. Previous experience working legislative or government affairs is a plus. Candidates with a strong working knowledge of the City of Philadelphia, Montgomery County, personal connections or residency in the 13th congressional district and familiarity with local transportation are strongly preferred. Interested candidates should send your resume and cover letter to pa13jobs@gmail.com. Please list “Special Assistant” in the subject line.
Congressman French Hill (AR-02) is seeking a Staff Assistant in his Washington, D.C. office beginning immediately. General responsibilities include greeting constituents, answering constituent phone calls, opening and sorting mail, guiding U.S. Capitol building tours, processing flag requests, organizing supplies and inventory, and assisting staff with administrative and legislative tasks.
Candidates will have a positive attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Social media and other communications experience a strong plus. Successful candidates will be self- starters, take and listen to direction, and be able to work both independently and as part of a team.
Applicants should have working knowledge of current events and policy topics as well as a willingness to assist with daily office tasks. Arkansas ties strongly preferred. Those interested please send your resume and cover letter to ar02.applications@mail.house.gov.
 Page 9 of 9
