 ________________________________________________________________________
House Vacancy Announcement and Placement Service (HVAPS)
B-235 Longworth House Office Building Washington, D.C. 20515 202-226-5836
Vacancy Bulletins are available for pick-up in
Longworth HOB - B-227 (CAO First Call Customer Service Center) or in the CAO Human Resources Office - Ford HOB 102
To Subscribe or Unsubscribe to the Vacancy Listserv visit:
http://www.house.gov/content/jobs/
Job Line: 202-226-4504 ______________________________________________________________________________
 MEM-168-14
INTERNSHIP VACANCY LISTING
Week of March 24, 2014
Illinois Representative John Shimkus is looking for current college students for a Congressional internship. These internships are available now on either a full-time or part-time basis. Qualified candidates will be highly organized, prompt, responsible, and ready to work in a fast paced environment. Strong oral and communication skills are a must. Daily duties will include assisting staff, answering phones, organizing mail, giving tours of the Capitol Building, and attending hearings and briefings for legislative staff. Interns will gain valuable Capitol Hill experience and further their understanding of the legislative process. Illinois ties are preferred but not necessary. All interested applicants should e-mail their resume and/or cover letter to midwestinternship@gmail.com
The DC and District office of Congressman John Conyers, Jr., representing Michigan’s 13th district, is looking for current college students to serve as part-time or full-time interns for summer 2014. This is an opportunity to learn about the inner-workings of a
 MEM-167-14
Page 1 of 9

 MEM-166-14
congressional office on the Hill in a fast-paced work environment.
The internship provides access to briefings and interesting events related to a wide range of important issues. Interns will be responsible for:
 Assisting with congressional projects,
 Drafting constituent correspondence,
 Preparing staff for briefings,
 Researching topics for floor speeches,
 Evaluating legislation,
 Answering calls,
 Sorting mail,
 Giving Capitol tours,
 And tracking constituent casework.
All interns will be given the opportunity to research a topic of your choice and submit your findings with policy recommendations to the staff.
Interested applicants should e-mail a cover letter, resume and two professional references to yvesner.zamar@mail.house.gov with the Subject: Congressional Internship | Summer 2014. In your cover letter, please address the following:
 Reason that you’re interested in interning for Congressman John Conyers, Jr.
 Issue areas that interest you
 Any relevant experience, coursework, or affiliations, if any
 Specify which office DC (Capitol Hill) or District (Detroit)
 Your availability for Summer 2014
Energetic NY Freshman Democrat is seeking highly motivated candidates for a part-time, unpaid internship in his Washington, DC office to begin immediately. Candidates should possess a professional and courteous demeanor, interest in the legislative process, excellent communication skills, the ability to multi-task, attention to detail, and a sense of humor. Main responsibilities include, but are not limited to, attending Congressional briefings, responding to constituent correspondence, assisting with flag requests, and general office
duties. Candidates with New York ties and previous internship/work experience are strongly encouraged to apply. Please e-mail a resume, cover letter, and a short writing sample to NY.ResumeInbox@mail.house.gov. Equal opportunity employer. No calls or walk-ins please.
Congressman Jerry McNerney (CA-09) is currently accepting applications for internship positions in his Washington D.C. office.
 MEM-165-14
Page 2 of 9

 MEM-164-14
This unpaid internship will provide valuable hands-on experience in a Congressional office and a greater understanding of the legislative process.
Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to, attending Congressional briefings, giving tours of the Capitol, conducting research, responding to constituent inquiries, and processing tour and flag requests. Qualified applicants should possess a professional and courteous demeanor, excellent communication skills, the ability to multi-task, fastidious attention to detail, and interest in the legislative and governmental process.
This is an excellent opportunity for college students and recent graduates seeking Capitol Hill experience. All majors are encouraged to apply. Ties to California’s Ninth Congressional District are preferred, but not required. Interested applicants should email a resume and cover letter to nick.sullivan@mail.house.gov with “CA-09 Internship” in the subject line. Include dates of availability.
A Democratic California Congressman is seeking highly motivated interns to join his Washington, DC office for a part or full time unpaid internship for the summer term (May-August). Candidates should be organized, professional, quick learners, and team players. Strong oral and written communication skills and close attention to detail are important. Main responsibilities include but are not limited to assisting staff with legislative, administrative, and press related projects, writing memos and talking points, attending hearings and meetings, answering constituent phone calls, leading tours of the US Capitol, assisting with scheduling, sorting and distributing mail, and managing tour and flag requests. Candidates with California ties and previous internship/work experience are strongly encouraged to apply. Please e-mail a resume and cover letter to Intern.Resume@mail.house.gov.
The Washington, DC office of Congresswoman Carolyn McCarthy (NY-04) is currently seeking interns for the 2014 summer semester. Qualified candidates must possess an interest in the legislative process, excellent writing and communication skills, and a desire to work in the fast-paced environment of Capitol Hill. Ideal candidates will be professional, dependable, highly-motivated, and adept at multi-tasking.
Responsibilities will include – but are not limited to – communicating with constituents via phone, drafting constituent correspondence, performing research requests, leading tours of the U.S. Capitol, and administrative work. Interns will also work closely with staff and have the opportunity to attend briefings, hearings, and other events on Capitol Hill.
 MEM-163-14
Page 3 of 9

 MEM-162-14
Students or recent graduates with ties to New York State – especially the Fourth Congressional District and Long Island – are encouraged to apply. Full- and part-time candidates will be considered. The internship is unpaid.
To apply, please send a cover letter which includes your weekly availability, a résumé, and a short 1-2 page writing sample to Marcus Garza at Marcus.Garza@mail.house.gov with “summer 2014 internship” in the subject line.
The Office of Congressman McClintock (CA-04) is seeking full or part-time summer interns for his Washington, D.C. office. Applicants should possess conservative values, as well as strong written and verbal communication skills. Interns will gain first-hand experience in the operation and management of a Congressional office. Internship duties include attending Congressional hearings, leading U.S. Capitol tours, answering phones, managing constituent mail database, drafting constituent correspondence, and assisting legislative staff with research.
Those with ties to California are encouraged to apply. Interested applicants should send their resume, availability, and a brief cover letter summarizing their interest in working for Congressman McClintock to Rachel.Long@mail.house.gov. Please use “2014 Summer Internship” in the subject line. No phone calls, drop-ins, or faxes please.
Congressman Alcee L. Hastings (D-FL) is seeking a highly-motivated, self-starting and detail-orientated individual to begin immediately in his internship program. Opportunities include answering phones, processing mail, drafting constituent correspondence letters, researching legislative issues, attending congressional hearings/briefings/seminars, and assisting in administrative operations. The internship is unpaid. Work may qualify for academic credit, depending on the requisites of the college or university.
Please e-mail your cover letter, resume and a short writing sample to Christian Sy at christian.sy@mail.house.gov
The office of Congressman Jeff Denham (CA-10) seeks a motivated, organized, reliable and detail-oriented college student or recent graduate for a full- or part-time paid press internship in Washington, D.C. The press intern will assist the communications director in drafting statements and releases, creating graphics, compiling daily clips, preparing remarks and implementing social media strategies. Press intern may also assist other staff with various tasks, including answering phones, conducting tours and doing legislative research.
 MEM-161-14
 MEM-160-14
Page 4 of 9

 MEM-159-14
Ideal candidate will have a thorough knowledge of AP style, strong writing skills and graphic design experience. Familiarity with Spanish language preferred but not required.
Please send your resume, cover letter and a brief writing sample to
Jordan.langdon@mail.house.gov.
Congressman Blaine Luetkemeyer (MO-03) is looking for unpaid summer interns for his Washington D.C. office, available to start in May and lasting through August. Applicants should possess conservative values, be personable, and have strong writing
skills. Duties include performing administrative tasks, attending Congressional hearings, leading Capitol tours for constituents, and helping legislative staff with research on important projects. Interns will also have the opportunity to work on issues that interest him or her. This position is great for Capitol Hill experience. Start and end dates are negotiable and both part/full-time positions are
available. Interested applicants should send resume and brief cover letter summarizing their interest in working for Rep. Luetkemeyer to Lucas.West@mail.house.gov with “Summer Internship” as the subject.
Congressman Jerry McNerney (CA-09) is currently accepting applications for internship positions in his Washington D.C. office. This unpaid internship will provide valuable hands-on experience in a Congressional office and a greater understanding of the legislative process. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to, attending Congressional briefings, giving tours of the Capitol, conducting research, responding to constituent inquiries, and processing tour and flag requests. Qualified applicants should possess a professional and courteous demeanor, excellent communication skills, the ability to multi-task, fastidious attention to detail, and interest in the legislative and governmental process.
This is an excellent opportunity for college students and recent graduates seeking Capitol Hill experience. All majors are encouraged to apply. Ties to California’s Ninth Congressional District are preferred, but not required. Interested applicants should email a resume and cover letter to nick.sullivan@mail.house.gov with “CA-09 Internship” in the subject line. Include dates of availability.
Moderate Democrat from California is currently seeking qualified applicants to join office as unpaid legislative interns and fellows for Spring and Summer 2014 policy to assist with health
policy. Applicants should have a familiarity with the legislative
 MEM-158-14
 MEM-157-14
Page 5 of 9

 MEM-156-14
process and have a desire to learn while being a part of a hardworking team. Ideal candidates will possess strong writing and verbal communication skills, a demonstrated interest in legislative issues, the ability to multi-task and conduct research, and an enthusiastic attitude. Legislative tasks may include, but are not limited to, legislative research, assembling information, memo and legislative writing, and attending hearings, markups, briefings and meetings for the purpose of taking notes. Applicants should be able to start in April/May and commit through July. Internship may lead to paid
opportunities. Interested applicants should email their resume and cover letter to Info.CA35@mail.house.gov.
Congresswoman Suzan DelBene, representing the 1st congressional district of Washington state, seeks interns for her Washington, D.C. office. Interns will work in a fast-paced congressional office, gaining valuable experience and knowledge of the United States
Congress. Intern responsibilities include greeting constituents and handling constituent phone calls, assisting staff with administrative tasks, conducting research, and assisting with constituent correspondence. Interns will have the opportunity to lead tours of the U.S. Capitol as well as attend hearings and briefings for the legislative staff. The ideal candidates will possess exceptional written and oral communication skills, a high degree of professionalism, as well as a strong interest in public service. Washington state ties are a plus, but are not required. To apply, please send a resume and cover letter to internship.delbene@mail.house.gov.
The office of Congresswoman Susan Davis (CA-53) has an immediate opening for interns in Washington, DC on a full or part-time basis. Qualified candidates must be highly motivated, well-organized, detail- oriented, and possess excellent communication skills. The ability to work in teams and use good judgment is critical. Duties will include helping staff with correspondence and research, greeting guests, answering phones, scheduling tours and assisting with other front- office duties. Interns will also be able to work on projects and attend briefings based on their policy interests. Proficiency in Microsoft Office is required. All interested applicants should send a cover letter, resume, and writing sample to CA53DCInternApp@mail.house.gov.
The Committee on Education and the Workforce, Democrats is currently seeking graduate and legal interns and fellows, for summer 2014, to work with labor policy staff. Legislative tasks may include, but are not limited to, legislative research, assembling information, assisting staff in hearing and markup preparation and execution, memo and legislative writing, and attending other hearings, markups, briefings and meetings for the purpose of taking notes. Applicants should be
 MEM-155-14
 MEM-154-14
Page 6 of 9

  MEM-153-14
able to start in April/May and commit through July. Interested applicants should email their application materials to jobs_ewdems@mail.house.gov. Please include with your resume, a cover letter, the internship applicant information form and two short, relevant writing samples. Please visit our website at http://democrats.edworkforce.house.gov/about/internships for more information.
Progressive Maryland Democrat seeks qualified interns to join her Washington, D.C. office for an unpaid legislative internship during the Summer 2014 term. Applicants should have a familiarity with the legislative process and have a desire to learn while being a part of a hardworking team. Ideal candidates will possess strong writing and verbal communication skills, a demonstrated interest in legislative issues, the ability to multi-task and conduct research, and an enthusiastic attitude. Interns will have the opportunity to assist staff with legislative and scheduling projects, attend briefings and hearings, draft memos, sort and distribute mail, and give Capitol tours. Candidates with Maryland ties are strongly encouraged to apply. Please email a resume, cover letter stating your availability, and a brief and relevant writing sample (maximum one page) by March 24th to internship.md04@mail.house.gov.
The office of Congressman Raul Labrador (ID-01) is currently seeking unpaid interns in the Washington, D.C. office for summer 2014. Start/stop dates are flexible. Basic intern responsibilities include but are not limited to answering phones, sorting mail, conducting tours of the U.S. Capitol, and assisting staff on various projects. Interns will have the opportunity to attend briefings and hearings of interest and see firsthand how a congressional office operates. Ideal candidates will have excellent research and writing abilities, be able to multi-task and interact well with constituents. College students and recent graduates will be considered. Course credit is available. Interested candidates should direct their resume and cover letter to bekah.demordaunt@mail.house.gov.
A Western Democratic Congressional Office seeks a motivated, organized, and reliable college student or recent graduate wishing to gain Capitol Hill experience for a full/part-time, 10-week, unpaid press internship in Washington, D.C.
The press intern will help create graphics, develop press lists, send clips, prepare speeches, draft statements, and social media content.
Please send a single PDF file containing your resume, cover letter, and a brief writing sample (preferably a press release or speech excerpt)
 MEM-152-14
 MEM-151-14
Page 7 of 9

 MEM-150-14
to NV04internships@gmail.com.
Please include in the body of the email a 3-5 sentence pitch for yourself: Why do you want to work on the Hill? Why should we choose you?
Senior, Progressive, Democratic Member has an opening for a paid Legislative Fellow to assist the legislative staff with education, women, tax, immigration, and veterans’ issues. This is not an entry- level opportunity.
Ideal candidates are strong writers, with the ability to learn quickly, multi-task, and work independently in a fluid environment. In particular, applicants with great interpersonal skills and good humor are welcome. Women and minorities are encouraged to apply.
Please email a cover letter and resume to leg.job@mail.house.gov. Applicants should be available to begin work immediately; no phone calls, faxes, or drop-ins, please.
  Moderate New York Democratic Congressman’s office is seeking a full-time intern or fellow for the Congressman’s Washington, DC office. The position begins immediately.
Qualified candidates will possess an interest in the legislative process, superior writing and communication skills, and the desire to work in a face-paced environment. Only full-time applicants will be considered.
Responsibilities will include managing the front office, communicating with constituents, performing research requests, and administrative work. Our office’s interns and fellows work closely with our staff and should be professional, motivated and adept at multi-tasking.
Preference will be given to applicants from the State of New York.
Please send a cover letter stating your availability and a resume to nydeminternships@gmail.com
 MEM-147-14
MEM-146-14
The office of Congresswoman Renee Ellmers (NC-02) is looking for interns on a full or part-time basis. This internship would be located in the Dunn, NC district office. A qualified candidate is highly motivated, well-organized, responsible, and possesses good oral and written communication skills and computer skills. Duties will include helping staff with correspondence and research, as well as greeting guests, answering phones, and assisting with other front-office
duties. Proficiency in Microsoft Office is required; ability to work Page 8 of 9

 MEM-145-14
cooperatively and courteously with others; ability to use good judgment in responding to requests; and flexibility in assisting with daily tasks and projects. North Carolina ties are preferred. While this is an unpaid internship, the office is happy to assist interns who qualify for academic credit. All interested applicants should send a cover letter and resume to Pat.Fitzgerald@mail.house.gov.
Internships – Congressman Benishek from Michigan’s First District seeks unpaid interns to fill positions for March through May 2014. Main responsibilities include answering phones, processing mail, drafting constituent correspondence letters, researching legislative issues, and attending meetings/hearings as needed. There will also be opportunities to attend receptions and seminars of interest. Candidates should be self-motivated, enthusiastic, flexible, and computer-literate (with a good understanding of MS Office). This is a great opportunity for college students seeking academic credit. Michigan ties are preferred. Please e-mail your cover letter, resume, and references to Samuel Grossman at samuel.grossman@mail.house.gov.
Moderate Democratic Congressman seeks applicants for full- or part- time unpaid congressional internship for Spring 2014 starting immediately. Duties will include conducting legislative research, drafting memos, assisting with front office duties, and performing basic administrative tasks. Candidates must exhibit strong writing and communication skills. San Diego residents or strong ties to California are preferred. Please send a resume, cover letter and writing sample to Internships.CA52@gmail.com with “Spring Congressional Internship” in the subject line.
 MEM-144-14
 Page 9 of 9
