 ________________________________________________________________________
House Vacancy Announcement and Placement Service (HVAPS)
B-235 Longworth House Office Building Washington, D.C. 20515 202-226-5836
Vacancy Bulletins are available for pick-up in
Longworth HOB - B-227 (CAO First Call Customer Service Center) or in the CAO Human Resources Office - Ford HOB 102
To Subscribe or Unsubscribe to the Vacancy Listserv visit:
http://www.house.gov/content/jobs/
Job Line: 202-226-4504 _____________________________________________________________________________
 MEM-271-14
INTERNSHIP VACANCY LISTING
Week of July 28, 2014
A Democratic California Congressman is seeking highly motivated interns to join his Washington, DC office for a part or full time unpaid internship for the autumn term (September-December). Candidates should be organized, professional, quick learners, and team players. Strong oral and written communication skills and close attention to detail are important. Main responsibilities include but are not limited to assisting staff with legislative, administrative, and press related projects, writing memos and talking points, attending hearings and meetings, answering constituent phone calls, leading tours of the US Capitol, assisting with scheduling, sorting and distributing mail, and managing tour and flag requests. Candidates with California ties and previous internship/work experience are strongly encouraged to apply. Please e-mail a resume and cover letter to Intern.Resume@mail.house.gov.
The Washington, DC office of Rep. Mark Sanford (SC-01) seeks applicants for unpaid fulltime internships for the fall semester to begin immediately. Applicants should be able to competently handle
 MEM-270-14
Page 1 of 21

 MEM-269-14
telephone calls, be well-organized, have an eye for detail, possess strong writing skills, be generally knowledgeable of legislative and related issues, and be able to complete tasks as directed. Main duties include answering telephones, logging constituent calls, giving tours of the Capitol to visitors, opening and sorting mail, and assisting with other administrative tasks. Interns will have many opportunities to take on additional responsibilities within the office, at the discretion of staff. Anyone interested should send a resume to Martha@mail.house.gov.
Congresswoman Chellie Pingree (ME-01) is currently seeking full- or part-time interns for the 2014 fall semester in her Washington, DC office. Interns will assist in the day-to-day operations of a DC Congressional office by supporting members of staff with constituent communication, legislative research, and administrative activities. They will also serve as a tour coordinator and occasionally act as a guide of the United States Capitol to Maine constituents visiting Washington.
Qualified candidates will possess an interest in the legislative process, excellent writing and communication skills, strong attention to detail, and a willingness to learn and take on new tasks. The internship is unpaid, though interns will be an essential component to the effectiveness of the office and will be considered an integral member of the team. Maine ties are preferred, but not necessary.
Please send a resume, cover letter, and brief writing sample to evan.johnston@mail.house.gov with the subject line Fall Internship. Applications will be considered on a rolling basis. Please no drop bys or phone calls.
Congressman Steve Israel (D-NY) is seeking unpaid interns for his Washington, DC office for the fall term (August/September - December, full or part time). Intern duties include answering the phone, writing letters, attending legislative briefings, and assisting staff members with special projects. Attention to detail and strong writing and grammar skills are required. Candidates from the 3rd Congressional District of New York are especially encouraged to apply, although all applications will be considered equally regardless of state or district ties. Prospective candidates should apply online and submit a resume and cover letter to repisraelinterns@gmail.com. No phone calls or drop ins, please.
Congressman Alcee L. Hastings (D-FL) is seeking highly-motivated, self-starting, and detail-orientated individuals for his Fall 2014 internship program to begin as early as August 18th. Opportunities include answering phones, processing mail, drafting constituent correspondence letters, researching legislative issues, attending Congressional hearings/briefings/seminars, and assisting in
 MEM-268-14
 MEM-267-14
Page 2 of 21

 MEM-266-14
administrative operations. The internship is unpaid. Work may qualify for academic credit, depending on the requisites of the college or university.
Please e-mail your cover letter, resume, and a short writing sample to Christian Sy at Christian.Sy@mail.house.gov.
The Washington, D.C. office of Congresswoman Louise M. Slaughter (NY-25) is seeking a full-time press intern to work with Congresswoman Slaughter’s communications team. This position is more advanced than a standard Congressional internship, requiring strong writing skills while being an avid consumer of political media.
The press intern will work directly with the Press Secretary and Digital Director to carry out responsibilities including - but not limited to - helping create digital content, developing press lists, collecting and distributing press clips, drafting press releases, and contacting reporters. Special skills such as photography or video editing a plus. Standard schedule begins with aggregating news clips at 8:00 am and ends at 4:00 pm.
While the position is unpaid, the office will work with universities and academic programs to accommodate applicants wishing to earn academic credit. First-hand experience in the congressional office will provide a unique opportunity into the functions of a fast-paced press operation for a senior Democratic member office. It will also offer a unique insight into legislative and parliamentary procedure, as Congresswoman Slaughter is Senior Democrat on the Committee on Rules. The Rules Committee determines the parameters of debate for all major legislation before it can be considered on the House Floor, including which amendments can be offered.
Applicants should e-mail a cover letter, resume, and a one-to-three page writing sample, and if applicable, a portfolio sample to Jack Spasiano at NY25.InternApplications@mail.house.gov Please do not hesitate to contact Jack at 202-225-3615 with any questions.
Senior Democratic Congressman Brad Sherman (CA-30) seeks highly motivated, full and part-time interns for Fall 2014. Interns are responsible for both administrative and legislative duties. Legislative support includes preparing materials for hearings, attending hearings and briefings, reaching out to agencies and congressional offices, and researching legislation for the Member and Legislative
Staff. Administrative tasks include answering phones, greeting visitors, leading tours and sorting mail.
Candidates should be professional, possess strong oral and written Page 3 of 21
 MEM-265-14

 MEM-264-14
communication skills, have the ability to multitask, and have a good sense of humor. Ties to California’s 30th Congressional District are a plus but not required. Interested applicants should e-mail a cover letter and resume to luke.stone@mail.house.gov with “CA-30 Internship” as the subject. Please do not hesitate to contact Luke with any questions by sending him an email or calling (202) 225-5911.
Congressman Vern Buchanan (R-FL-16) has full-time and part-time, unpaid internships available for the fall session (August-December) in his Washington, DC office. Qualified candidates should possess excellent organizational and communication skills, should have a positive attitude, and a strong work ethic. Although internships are unpaid, our office is happy to fill out any necessary forms for students to receive credit at their respective college or university.
All interested individuals should submit a cover letter and resume to jillian.gates@mail.house.gov with “2014 Fall Internship” in the subject line.
The Office of Congresswoman Ann McLane Kuster (NH-02) is seeking qualified candidates to intern full time and part time in our Washington, D.C. office starting in August/September 2014. Candidates with ties to the Northeast—especially New Hampshire—are especially encouraged to apply.
Interns will assist the staff with a variety of tasks, including office administration, legislative research, constituent correspondence, and other duties as assigned.
Administration will include daily tasks such as welcoming guests, being aware of the Congresswoman’s and staff schedules, answering phones, constituent tours, mail administration, and other duties. Legislative research and constituent correspondence will include being aware of current and pending legislation, researching legislation for constituent correspondence, attending briefings, and other duties.
Candidates should have excellent writing and communication skills, strong organizational abilities, a good work ethic, an ability to work independently, and a drive to take initiative.
If candidates have any questions or wish to apply, please send a cover letter, resume, writing sample, and references to the ATT of Scott Elias at NH02.Internship@mail.house.gov or call 202-225-5206. Please include “Your Last Name-Internship App” in the subject line and include your availability in your cover letter and/or email.
 MEM-263-14
 Page 4 of 21

MEM-262-14
Congressman Brad Schneider (IL-10) is currently seeking an unpaid intern to start work in August or September in his Washington, D.C. office. Interns perform a variety of front office responsibilities, including answering phones, receiving guests, and providing tours of the Capitol Building. They will also research legislation for the Member and legislative staff, attend hearings and briefings, write memos, and answer constituent letters on various issues before the House. Interns should possess strong research, writing, analytical, and interpersonal skills. Interested candidates should email their resume and cover letter to internshipsIL10@gmail.com.
The Washington, DC office of Congresswoman Louise Slaughter (D- NY) is offering internship opportunities for students and recent graduates starting immediately. First-hand experience in Congresswoman Slaughter’s office will provide interns with an unparalleled knowledge and understanding of the development of public policy and government affairs. Intern responsibilities include drafting letters to constituents, attending committee hearings, writing summary briefs, researching various issues for the legislative staff and assisting with additional office duties.
Interns will receive unique insight into the legislative process and parliamentary procedure as a result of her position as the Ranking Member of the House Rules Committee. The Rules Committee determines the parameters of debate for all major pieces of legislation before it can be considered on the House Floor, including which amendments can be offered.
The internship provides different opportunities with staff to discuss their experiences on the Hill and future employment strategies.
Applicants should e-mail a cover letter, resume, and a one to three page writing sample to Jack Spasiano at NY25.InternApplications@mail.house.gov. Please do not hesitate to contact Jack at (202) 225-3615 with any questions.
The Office of Representative Kevin Brady (TX-08) is currently seeking full-time fall interns for our Washington, D.C. office. Qualified candidates are well organized, with good oral and written communication skills, and possess a strong interest in learning about the political process and congressional affairs. Duties include but are not limited to, answering phones, compiling briefing binders, batching mail, performing legislative research, and attending briefings. Interns interact heavily with constituents so a positive attitude is a must. Applicants must be detail oriented with a strong work ethic and an eagerness to represent the 8th district of Texas. Previous Hill
 MEM-261-14
 MEM-260-14
Page 5 of 21

 MEM-259-14
experience not required. Though start date is flexible, a mid-August start date is ideal. Interested Candidates should send a resume and cover letter to: TX08intern@gmail.com
Fall Intern – The Office of Congressman David Price (NC-04) is seeking qualified candidates to intern in our Washington, D.C. office for the fall semester (September through the end of November.) This unpaid internship will provide valuable hands-on experience in a Congressional office and a greater understanding of the legislative process. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to: attending Congressional briefings, conducting research for staffers, responding to constituent inquiries, operating the phones, sorting the mail, and giving tours of the Capitol.
The internship program is open to college undergraduates, regardless of major, who are attending a DC-area college or who are participating in a semester program in Washington sponsored by a college or university. NC ties are required. Please fill out the application by August 15th and follow the submitting instructions at http://price.house.gov/internships/.
Congresswoman Candice S. Miller (R-MI) seeks legislative interns for the Fall 2014 (September-December) semester. Interns will work in a fast-paced congressional office, gaining valuable exposure and knowledge of the legislative process and the United States Congress. Intern responsibilities include greeting constituents, managing constituent phone calls, and assisting staff with administrative tasks. Interns will also have the opportunity to conduct legislative research, assist with constituent correspondence, and attend legislative briefings, congressional hearings, receptions, and press events.
Interns must have a good attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Successful interns will be able to find information with little assistance, be able to work both independently as well as part of a team environment, and possess a strong attention to detail. Applicants should have working knowledge of current events and policy topics, as well as a willingness to perform a variety of tasks and administrative functions. Michigan ties are strongly preferred; however, candidates from outside the state will be considered. Undergraduate students are strongly encouraged to
apply. This is an unpaid position, but a great opportunity for students seeking academic credit. To apply, please send cover letter, resume and writing sample to MI10Internship@gmail.com .
The Office of Congressman Robert A. Brady (PA-01) seeks interns for fall 2014 (Sept-Dec). Internship responsibilities will include: assisting
 MEM-258-14
 MEM-257-14
Page 6 of 21

 MEM-256-14
with research, processing mail, data entry, reception duties, office errands, and other duties as assigned by Intern Supervisor. Ideal candidate will have strong social skills, good oral and written communication abilities, a willingness to learn, basic knowledge of the political process, and a firm opinion on the best cheesesteak in Philadelphia. Pennsylvania ties preferred. Please send a resume, cover letter, and writing sample to Liz Leibowitz at liz.leibowitz@mail.house.gov. Please no phone calls or drop-ins.
The Office of Congresswoman Elizabeth H. Esty is seeking qualified candidates to intern in our Washington, D.C office. Start date: Immediately through November with flexibility
Interns will assist the staff with a variety of tasks, including office administration, legislative research, constituent correspondence, and other duties as assigned.
Administration will include daily tasks such as welcoming guests, being aware of the Congressman’s and staff’s schedules, answering phones, constituent tours, mail administration, and other duties.
Legislative research and constituent correspondence will include being aware of current and pending legislation, researching legislation for constituent correspondence, attending briefings, and other duties.
Candidates should have excellent writing and communication skills, strong organizational abilities, a good work ethic, an ability to work independently.
Connecticut ties preferred but not required.
Hours will be Monday-Friday 9:00am-6:00pm
If candidates have any questions or wish to apply, please send resume, cover letter, and writing sample to Nakia.Mulley@mail.house.gov
Congresswoman Jaime Herrera Beutler’s office is currently accepting applications for internships in the Washington D.C. and the Vancouver offices. This is a great opportunity for college students, recent graduates, military veterans and others who are interested in an insider’s view of the legislative process and the daily operations of a congressional office.
Typical intern responsibilities in the D.C. office include: leading tours Page 7 of 21
   MEM-255-14

   MEM-254-14
of the U.S. Capitol, fielding calls from constituents, administrative tasks, attending congressional hearings and briefings, and assisting staff in a variety of projects including research, writing and editing.
Intern tasks in the Vancouver office include: fielding calls from constituents, administrative tasks, assisting staff in a variety of projects and events, sorting and delivering mail, and entering data.
All candidates should possess great oral and written communication skills, be highly motivated, demonstrate knowledge of computer applications, maintain a positive attitude and show initiative.
Applicants must be able to make a commitment of at least 10 weeks. Those with Washington state or Pacific Northwest ties are preferred, but all may apply. Internships are unpaid; however, if academic credit can be awarded through your school, the office will be happy to assist in that process.
To apply, please submit the following materials to
Breanna.Deutsch@mail.house.gov:
Do not hesitate to contact the office if you have any questions regarding our internship program.
Nevada Congressman Steven Horsford (NV-04) is currently seeking an intern for the Fall of 2014. Applicants must be at least a high school junior/senior, college student, or recent college graduate wishing to gain legislative experience for a full-time or part-time semester internship to begin in August and/or September 2014. We are seeking motivated, organized, and reliable individuals to assist the district office staff with day-to-day duties. Such duties include assisting the staffers and communications staff, attending congressional outreach events, answering phones, working with the constituents of NV-04, doing legislative research and various other tasks.
The internship is unpaid, and will take place in the Congressman’s District office in Nevada. Interns will gain valuable congressional and office experience and will have access to many unique opportunities. Nevada and District 4 ties are preferred, but not necessary. Please send a resume and cover letter to NV04Internships@gmail.com. Include your anticipated start and end dates and have “DO Internship” as the subject of your email. Please no drop bys, phone calls, or emailing staff members.
Progressive Maryland Democrat seeks qualified interns to join her Page 8 of 21
 MEM-252-14

 MEM-251-14
District office for unpaid Constituent Services and Outreach internships during the Fall 2014 term.
Constituent Service Internship - Constituent Service Interns will work in the District office to assist Constituent Service Representatives. Responsibilities include assisting with constituent files, gathering information from federal agencies, and answering constituent calls. S/he will monitor congressional inquiries through online databases.
Outreach Internship - The Outreach Intern will work in the District office supporting the team with a variety of outreach projects and activities, including event planning, and advocacy communications. The Outreach Intern also conducts project research using the web and traditional sources such as booth set up at events. S/he helps develop several databases and lists of state, local/civic, and federal organizations and government agencies. S/he must monitor local and national media through print, online/blog and television news media. The Outreach Intern also responds to outreach-related initiatives and assists with general outreach efforts.
Ideal candidates for both positions will be detailed oriented, well organized, and able to conduct research. Interns should also possess strong written and verbal communication skills in a professional setting. Undergraduates and recent graduates of any major with ties to Maryland are strongly encouraged to apply. Please email a resume, cover letter stating your availability, and a brief and relevant writing sample (maximum one page) by August 15th to internship.md04@mail.house.gov.
Progressive Maryland Democrat seeks qualified interns to join her Washington, D.C. office for an unpaid legislative internship during the Fall 2014 term. Applicants should have a familiarity with the legislative process and have a desire to learn while being a part of a hardworking team. Ideal candidates will possess strong writing and verbal communication skills, a demonstrated interest in legislative issues, the ability to multi-task and conduct research, and an enthusiastic attitude. Interns will have the opportunity to assist staff with legislative and scheduling projects, attend briefings and hearings, draft memos, sort and distribute mail, and give Capitol tours. Candidates with Maryland ties are strongly encouraged to apply. Please email a resume, cover letter stating your availability, and a brief and relevant writing sample (maximum one page) by August 15th to internship.md04@mail.house.gov.
The office of Congressman Jon Runyan (NJ-03) seeks full-time unpaid interns for the Washington D.C. office for fall 2014. The office would
 MEM-250-14
Page 9 of 21

 MEM-249-14
prefer applicants to have an availability from mid-August through December. Intern responsibilities include answering phones, interacting with constituents, running errands, and administering tours of the Capitol. NJ ties are preferred, but not required, and candidates should lean towards having conservative views. Please email a resume, cover letter, and writing sample to NJ03Internships@gmail.com.
The office of Congressman Keith Ellison seeks unpaid interns to fill positions for August through December 2014.Main responsibilities include answering phones, processing mail, drafting constituent correspondence letters, researching legislative issues, and attending meetings/hearings as needed. There will also be opportunities to attend receptions and seminars of interest. Candidates should be self- motivated, enthusiastic, flexible, and computer-literate (with a good understanding of MS Office). This is a great opportunity for college students seeking academic credit. Minnesota ties strongly preferred. If interested, please send resume, cover letter, and two writing samples to zach.freed@mail.house.gov
Congressman John D. Dingell (D-MI) is seeking full-time Congressional Interns for his Washington, DC office during the fall 2014. This internship position will provide individuals the opportunity to work in a fast-paced Congressional office while receiving hands-on political experience. Duties include answering phones, leading U.S. Capitol tours and assisting staff members with research and special projects. There will also be frequent opportunities to attend legislative hearings of personal interest. The ideal candidate will be motivated, detail orientated and possess strong communication and writing
skills. This is a great opportunity for recent graduates seeking Hill experience. Michigan ties are preferred. Interested applicants should submit a resume and cover letter to kevin.rambosk@mail.house.gov
Legislative Intern- The Office of Congressman Hakeem Jeffries is seeking a highly motivated intern to join his Washington, DC office for a part time unpaid internship this fall. Candidates should possess a professional and courteous demeanor, interest in the legislative process, excellent communication skills, the ability to multi-task, attention to detail, and a sense of humor. Main responsibilities include, but are not limited to, attending Congressional briefings, responding to constituent correspondence, assisting with flag requests, and general office
duties. Candidates with New York ties and previous internship/work experience are strongly encouraged to apply. Please e-mail a resume, cover letter, and a short writing sample to NY.ResumeInbox@mail.house.gov. Equal opportunity employer. No calls or walk-ins please.
 MEM-248-14
 MEM-247-14
 Page 10 of 21

MEM-246-14
MEM-241-14
The Office of Rep. Scott Rigell (VA-02) is seeking politically Conservative unpaid fall interns in their Washington, DC office to begin mid-August or early September. The Office seeks an outgoing, enthusiastic person with at least 3 days/week availability who would like experience working in a Congressional Office. Virginia ties are a plus. Interested persons should submit brief Cover Letter and Resume to VA02internships@gmail.com.
Press Intern – Member of Republican Leadership is seeking an unpaid press intern for the fall semester. This diligent "press" intern should be able to research, write, aggregate content, and think creatively - perfect for someone wanting a taste of the Hill, press work and the digital world. Our interns complete a variety of tasks; everything from writing tweets to shooting video to creating press releases, and even attend network (Fox News, CNN, etc.) tapings. Ideal candidates will have excellent research and writing abilities, be able to multi-task and have some exposure to Adobe Creative products. Email a resume, a cover- letter and a digital portfolio to goppressintern@gmail.com
The Office of Congressman Ami Bera, M.D. is seeking qualified candidates to intern full time in our Washington, D.C. office starting in August 2014. We are interested in candidates of all academic disciplines.
Interns will assist the staff with a variety of tasks, including office administration, legislative research, constituent correspondence, and other duties as assigned.
Administration will include daily tasks such as welcoming guests, being aware of the Congressman’s and staff’s schedules, answering phones, constituent tours, mail administration, and other duties.
Legislative research and constituent correspondence will include being aware of current and pending legislation, researching legislation for constituent correspondence, attending briefings, and other duties.
Candidates should have excellent writing and communication skills, strong organizational abilities, a good work ethic, an ability to work independently, and the drive to take the initiative in a fast-paced environment.
If candidates have any questions or wish to apply, please send resume, writing samples, and references to bera.resume@mail.house.gov
Immediate openings for interns to assist Congressman Petri (R- Wisconsin) and his staff in the overall day-to-day operations of the office by investigating constituent requests and drafting responses, answering telephones, greeting visitors, and guiding tours of the
  MEM-240-14
 MEM-239-14
Page 11 of 21

 MEM-238-14
Capitol. They will also be assigned research projects as
needed. Interns have the opportunity to attend committee hearings and otherwise take advantage of the unique perspective of Capitol Hill. We try to give our interns a firsthand view of the legislative process and we make every effort to provide them with a worthwhile learning experience. This is an excellent opportunity for college students or recent graduates interested in obtaining Capitol Hill experience. These unpaid positions are full or part-time with flexible scheduling available. Email cover letter and resume to Nicole.Christus@mail.house.gov with subject line INTERN APPLICANT.
Republican Member of the House of Representatives from NYC is seeking students/recent grads to join his office for an internship beginning August 18. Candidates should have strong oral and written communication skills, being able to defend the Member’s positions to constituents and outside groups.
Duties include:
- Answering constituent phone calls
- Sorting and batching incoming correspondence
- Assisting legislative staff in drafting constituent outreach letters
- Leading tours of the US Capitol
- Attending hearings and meetings
Candidates should e-mail meaghan.dowdy@mail.house.gov with availability, a cover letter, and resume. No calls or drop-bys.
The Office of Congresswoman Eleanor Holmes Norton (D-DC) is seeking a full-time or part-time intern for the fall of 2014. This is an opportunity to learn about the inner-workings of a congressional office on the Hill in a fast-paced work environment. The internship allows access to briefings and interesting events related to a wide range of important issues. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to, attending Congressional briefings, giving tours of the Capitol, conducting research, responding to constituent inquiries, and processing tour and flag requests. Qualified applicants should possess a professional and courteous demeanor, excellent communication skills, the ability to multi-task, fastidious attention to detail, and interest in the legislative and governmental process. To apply, please send a resume, contact information for three references, writing sample, and cover letter to Jason.spear@mail.house.gov, with the subject Norton
 MEM-237-14
 Page 12 of 21

MEM-236-14
Internship. No phone calls or drop-ins please.
Congressman Blaine Luetkemeyer’s Washington, DC office is looking for energetic and hard-working interns for the fall of 2014. Qualified candidates should have an interest in American government and working in a fast-paced political environment.
All interns are expected to effectively communicate with staff members and constituents. Daily tasks include, but are not limited to; administrative duties, leading tours of the United States Capitol building, communicating with constituents and other offices on Capitol Hill, attending hearings and meetings, writing briefings and memos, conducting research, and experiencing the city of Washington, DC.
All internships are unpaid. However, if your college or university offers credit hours we are happy to complete any necessary evaluations. In addition, housing is not provided but assistance will be offered.
If you are energetic, hard-working, and interested in a position in Rep. Luetkemeyer’s Washington, DC office please contact Claire Trokey at 202-225-2956 or send your resume and a cover letter to Claire.Trokey@mail.house.gov. A phone interview may be required.
The Office of Congresswoman Eleanor Holmes Norton (D-DC) is seeking a full-time or part-time Press and Social Media intern for the fall of 2014. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to compiling press clips, monitoring daily news, drafting talking points and press releases, updating social media and working closely with the communications director. The ideal candidate will have previous experience in public relations or journalism, possess strong written communications skills, ability to work in a fast-paced environment, and professional manner. Please note that the internship is unpaid and housing is not provided, but student can qualify for
academic credit depending on the requirements of the college or university. Interested applicants should e-mail a cover letter, resume, short writing sample (in the form of a speech or press release) and dates of availability with "Norton Internship" in the subject line to Jason.spear@mail.house.gov. No phone calls or drop-ins please.
Congressman Lee Terry is looking for interns in our Washington D.C. and Omaha offices. Internships in our Washington, D.C. and District offices offer students an outstanding opportunity to learn about the legislative process firsthand while working side by side with experienced full-time staff. Many of our interns will attend hearings,
 MEM-235-14
 MEM-234-14
Page 13 of 21

 MEM-232-14
MEM-231-14
prepare legislative reports, research specific issues to respond to constituent inquiries, process incoming mail and data entry, give constituents tours of the Capitol, and perform general office duties.
We are looking for students or recent graduates who possess:
Excellent interpersonal skills
Academic Excellence
Desire to contribute through public service Leadership skills
To apply, please email a cover letter and resume to Andrew Schaus at:
Intern4lee@mail.house.gov
The office of Congressman Ted Poe (TX-2) is seeking interns for the 2014 Fall semester. Texas ties are preferred, but not necessary. Intern will be responsible for answering phones, scheduling and guiding tours and processing flag requests, among other duties. Interested applicants should email a resume and cover letter to Michael Edwards at michael.edwards@mail.house.gov or call 202-225-6565. Start and end dates are flexible.
The office of Congressman Michael McCaul is looking for full time, unpaid summer interns. Internships will start in August 15th and last through the mid-December
Interns in Congressman McCaul's Washington, D.C. office will be responsible for assisting with general office duties (answering phones, passing out mail, distributing faxes), and assisting legislative staff with research and writing. Performing constituent services (scheduling tours, processing flag requests, and legislative correspondence) will also be an integral part of each internship. Interns will be encouraged to attend hearings, briefings, and other Congressional proceedings. Additional duties are available and will be assigned according to an intern’s interest and ability.
Must be highly motivated, self-starter, detail oriented, possess excellent organizational and communication skills, a strong work ethic, a positive attitude and will have the ability to manage multiple tasks on a deadline. Texas ties are preferred but are not required.
Please email resume and cover letter to Brandon.Batch@mail.house.gov with "Congressional Internship" in the email subject line. No phone calls please.
  Page 14 of 21

MEM-229-14
Interns will work in a fast-paced Congressional Office, gaining valuable exposure and knowledge of the legislative process and the United States Congress. Intern responsibilities include greeting constituents, handling constituent phone calls, opening and sorting mail, giving Capitol Tours, and assisting staff with administrative tasks. Interns will also have the opportunity to conduct legislative research, assist with correspondence, as well as attend some Capitol Hill briefings, congressional hearings, and press events. This internship is unpaid.
Interns must have a good attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Successful interns will be able to find information with little assistance, be able to work both independently as well as part of a team environment, and have strong attention to detail. Applicants should have working knowledge of current events and policy topics, as well as an interest in American Government. Wisconsin ties a plus.
Interns must be able to commit to at least two full days per week (9:00 am-6:00 pm). Please submit resume and 2 one page writing samples to Nairobi.cratic@mail.house.gov by August 15th, 2014.
Congresswomen Katherine Clark (MA-05) is seeking full-time and part-time interns for the fall 2014 semester to assist in performing research, processing the mail, data entry, office reception duties and other office errands. Requires good oral and written communication skills; ability to work cooperatively and courteously with others; good organizational skills; and responsible, dependable and willing to learn. Responsibilities include: performing research (CRS, the Library of Congress, or other available resources); sorting and distributing mail; attending committee meetings, briefings, and seminars; logging in letters and constituent requests; answering the telephones; greeting visitors and performing other duties as assigned by the Intern Supervisor.
To apply, please email your resume, cover letter, and a writing sample to RepClarkInternships@mail.house.gov. Your cover letter should include the dates and times that you are available to intern.
U.S. Congressman Erik Paulsen’s office is currently accepting applications for unpaid internships in the District office in Eden Prairie, MN and the office in Washington, D.C. A Congressional internship offers applicants an exciting opportunity to support staff, while learning about the daily operations of the Legislative Branch. Interns will assist the staff with constituent services, communications, administrative tasks, and legislative research.
 MEM-228-14
 MEM-227-14
Page 15 of 21

 MEM-224-14
Congressman Paulsen’s Internship Program is designed primarily for the educational benefit of the participant. Interns working in the District Office have the opportunity to contribute to the office’s interaction with the surrounding community through constituent services, local events, and community meetings. Interns in the Washington, D.C. Office will gain insight into the federal government and the legislative process by working closely with staff, writing memos, assisting with constituent correspondence and press, and attending hearings and briefings. The D.C. Office is also looking for students interested in learning more about press and working as an intern with the Congressman’s press staff.
Candidates should have a strong work ethic, be highly organized and motivated, and possess a positive attitude. This internship is unpaid, but students are encouraged to seek college credit. Qualified applicants should send their cover letter and resume to David Larson at David.Larson@mail.house.gov.
Qualifications
 Sophomore, junior or senior with a strong academic record
 Evidence of effectiveness working independently and a
demonstrated self-starter
 Excellent writing, research and interpersonal skills
The Office of Congresswoman Yvette Clarke is looking for prospective fellows to assist in the Capitol Hill Office for the fall and spring semester. Fellows will work alongside staff members in the Capitol Hill Office such as Shelley Davis, Chief of Staff, and Christina McWilson, Intern/Fellow Coordinator and Scheduler.
Fellows will be hired to fill part-time or full-time positions, which would consist of 4-5 days per weeks. Fellows will be required to work a minimum of 12-15 hours per week. The duration of the fall semester is from August 2014 to December 2014. The duration of the spring semester is from January 2015 to May 2015. This position is open to college students attending one of the local universities, such as Howard University, George Washington University, Georgetown University, and American University.
As a fellow, you will aid in the office as well as gain experience with working in a congressional office. Fellows will be asked to complete daily tasks such as answer phones, record constituent concerns, receive and open packages, sort and deliver mail, as well as greet visitors and offer water. Upon request, fellows will be asked to complete tasks such as attend briefings, write memorandums, draft constituent letter responses, book and give Capitol tours, book White House tours, as
Page 16 of 21

 MEM-223-14
well as order and pick-up supplies. Prospective fellows will be able to begin applying for this position July 2014. All applicants should send a copy of their resumes to NY09DCIntern1@mail.house.gov .
Congressman Jerry McNerney (CA-09) is currently accepting applications for Fall semester internship positions in his Washington D.C. office. This unpaid internship will provide valuable hands-on experience in a Congressional office and a greater understanding of the legislative process. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to, attending Congressional briefings, giving tours of the Capitol, conducting research, responding to constituent inquiries, and processing tour and flag requests. Qualified applicants should possess a professional and courteous demeanor, excellent communication skills, the ability to multi-task, fastidious attention to detail, and interest in the legislative and governmental process.
This is an excellent opportunity for college students and recent graduates seeking Capitol Hill experience. All majors are encouraged to apply. Ties to California’s Ninth Congressional District are preferred, but not required. Interested applicants should email a resume and cover letter to nick.sullivan@mail.house.gov with “CA-09 Internship” in the subject line. Include dates of availability.
Congressman Gregory W. Meeks (NY-05) is accepting applications for legislative internship positions available in his Washington D.C. office for the upcoming Fall term. This unpaid internship will provide an invaluable hands-on experience in a Congressional office and a greater understanding of the legislative process. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to, attending Congressional briefings on behalf of staff, giving tours of the Capitol, conducting research, responding to constituent inquiries, and processing tour and flag requests. Interns will also be given the opportunity to draft memos, write letters, and become a team member in a fast-paced and collegial office. Qualified applicants will possess a professional and courteous demeanor, excellent communication skills, the ability to multi-task, acute attention to detail, and interest in the legislative and governmental process.
This is an excellent opportunity for college students seeking Capitol Hill experience. All majors are encouraged to apply. Ties to New York’s Fifth Congressional District are preferred, but not required. Interested applicants should email a resume, cover letter, and a short writing sample to Jordan.Morris@mail.house.gov with “Your Last Name-Internship App” in the subject line. Please also include dates and times of availability.
 MEM-222-14
 Page 17 of 21

MEM-221-14
Congressman Kurt Schrader (OR-05) is seeking undergraduate and recent post-graduate students for an internship in his Washington, DC, office during the fall semester.
The responsibilities of a Congressional intern primarily focus on helping the Congressman communicate with his 700,000-plus constituents. Interns will assist the team with phones, mail, tours of the U.S. Capitol Building, and related front office duties. Additional tasks, including drafting correspondence, research projects, and attending hearings may be assigned on a case by case basis.
Candidates should possess excellent communication skills (both verbal and written) and an understanding of the functions of the United States Congress. Ideal candidates are positive, energetic, and eager to assist with the legislative and administrative needs of the staff. The internship is unpaid; both full-time and part-time positions are available. Oregon ties are preferred.
Please send a resume, cover letter, and writing sample to Julia Stafford at julia.stafford@mail.house.gov.
Representative Rick Larsen (WA-02) is currently seeking a full-time intern to start the first week of September with a flexible end date. Ideal candidates have excellent writing and research skills, a positive attitude, and a willingness to complete tasks as assigned. Intern responsibilities include researching and writing Congressional correspondence, helping constituents find information and fielding constituent phone calls. This internship also provides the opportunity to work closely with staff members and assist in various
projects. Washington ties are preferred, but are not required. If interested, please send a resume, cover letter and two references to: taylor.paquette@mail.house.gov. Please include “WA-02 Internship” in the subject line.
Ohio Republican seeks full time hard working interns for Fall 2014. Responsibilities include, but aren’t limited to, answering phone calls, assisting with the mail program, providing constituent tours, attending various briefings, providing research for the legislative staff. Qualified candidates will have exceptional writing skills, strong communication skills, ability to work in a fast paced working environment, and have an interest in learning more about the legislative process.
Send a resume and a cover letter to Stephen.Hostelley@mail.house.gov. Ohio candidates are strongly preferred.
 MEM-220-14
 MEM-219-14
 Page 18 of 21

MEM-218-14
Fall Internship Opportunity- Congressman Amodei’s Washington, D.C. Office
A congressional internship on Capitol Hill provides students with the unique opportunity to cultivate research and writing skills while gaining important professional experience. Interns in Congressman Amodei’s office will work closely with staff to learn about the legislative process.
Responsibilities include:
 Answering phones
 Legislative research
 Providing historical tours of the US Capitol for constituents
 Attending committee hearings and briefings
 Assisting staff with special projects
To apply, please send a cover letter and resume to Lauren Currie at
Lauren.Currie@mail.house.gov.
The office of Congressman Raul Labrador (ID-01) is currently seeking unpaid interns in the Washington, D.C. office for fall 2014. Start/stop dates are flexible. Basic intern responsibilities include, but are not limited to, answering phones, sorting mail, conducting tours of the U.S. Capitol, and assisting staff on various projects. Interns will have the opportunity to attend briefings and hearings of interest and see firsthand how a congressional office operates. Ideal candidates will have excellent research and writing abilities, be able to multi-task and interact well with constituents. College students and recent graduates will be considered. Course credit is available. Interested candidates should direct their resume and cover letter
to Alexa.walker@mail.house.gov.
The office of Congressman Buck McKeon (CA-25), Chairman, of the House Armed Services Committee, is seeking unpaid Interns for the Fall 2014 semester. Preference will be given to interns available to start by the beginning of August. Main responsibilities include answering phones, processing mail, drafting constituent correspondence letters, researching legislative issues, and attending meetings/hearings as needed. There will also be opportunities to attend receptions and seminars that interest you. Candidates should be self-motivated, enthusiastic, flexible, and computer-literate. This is a great opportunity for college students seeking academic credit. Applicants must be able to make a minimum commitment of four days a week. California ties a plus, but not required. Please e-mail your cover letter and resume to Zach Fisher at Zach.Fisher@mail.house.gov.
 MEM-217-14
 MEM-216-14
 Page 19 of 21

MEM-210-14
Representative Bill Johnson (OH-06) is currently seeking 2014 fall interns starting in August with flexible end dates. Responsibilities will mostly include, but are not limited to: greeting guests in the front office, answering phones, giving Capitol tours, attending and summarizing hearings and/or briefings for legislative staff, and performing various administrative tasks. Ohio ties are preferred, but are not required. The months of the internship may vary depending on the availability or school schedule of the applicant. If interested, please send a resume and cover letter to: intern.oh06@gmail.com. Please indicate your anticipated start and end dates. Please no phone calls or drop-ins.
Fall 2014 Intern for NY Congresswoman
Congresswoman Carolyn McCarthy (NY-04) is currently seeking interns for the 2014 fall semester in her Washington, DC office. Qualified candidates will possess an interest in the legislative process, excellent writing and communication skills, and a desire to work in the fast-paced environment of Capitol Hill. Ideal candidates will be professional, dependable, highly motivated, and adept at multi-tasking.
Responsibilities will include – but are not limited to – communicating with constituents via phone, drafting constituent correspondence, performing research requests, leading tours of the U.S. Capitol, and administrative work. Interns will also work closely with staff and have the opportunity to attend briefings, hearings, and other events on Capitol Hill.
Students or recent graduates with ties to New York State – especially the Fourth Congressional District and Long Island – are encouraged to apply. Full- and part-time candidates will be considered. The internship is unpaid.
To apply, please send a cover letter stating your availability, a resume, and a short 1-2 page writing sample to Sam Mayper at Sam.Mayper@mail.house.gov with “Fall 2014 internship” in the subject line.
The Democratic Staff of the Committee on Science, Space and Technology is seeking interns for the end of the summer and fall. Interns are asked to work with staff to help prepare for committee hearings and markups. Interns will work on substantive research projects and press matters. Additionally, interns are critical to the daily operation of the office including tasks such as answering phones, greeting visitors, and filing official documents.
 MEM-209-14
 MEM-208-14
Page 20 of 21

Interested applicants should visit the Committee’s website at http://democrats.science.house.gov/contact-us. Please fill out the application provided and send in a resume and two references.
 Page 21 of 21
