 ________________________________________________________________________
House Vacancy Announcement and Placement Service (HVAPS)
B-235 Longworth House Office Building Washington, D.C. 20515 202-226-5836
Vacancy Bulletins are available for pick-up in
Longworth HOB - B-227 (CAO First Call Customer Service Center) or in the CAO Human Resources Office - Ford HOB 102
To Subscribe or Unsubscribe to the Vacancy Listserv visit:
http://www.house.gov/content/jobs/
Job Line: 202-226-4504 _____________________________________________________________________________
 MEM-407-14
INTERNSHIP VACANCY LISTING
Week of December 15, 2014
Representative Rick Larsen (WA-02) is currently seeking a full-time intern to start the first week of January with a flexible end date. Ideal candidates have excellent writing and research skills, a positive attitude, and a willingness to complete tasks as assigned. Intern responsibilities include researching and writing Congressional correspondence, helping constituents find information and fielding constituent phone calls. This internship also provides the opportunity to work closely with staff members and assist in various projects. Washington ties are preferred, but are not required. If interested, please send a resume, cover letter and two references to: taylor.paquette@mail.house.gov. Please include “WA-02 Internship” in the subject line.
Our Washington interns will be exposed to a wide range of activities on Capitol Hill. They will be asked to answer phones, research legislation for the Member and legislative staff, attends hearings and briefings, and answer constituent letters on various issues before the House. Interns will need to be able to communicate professionally, balance multiple tasks at once, and have a teachable attitude. As a result, interns will learn about the legislative process, the various functions of a Congressional office, and the way things work on Capitol Hill. It is an invaluable
 MEM-405-14
Page 1 of 14

MEM-404-14
opportunity for both educational and professional development.
Congressman John Garamendi (CA-03) is seeking a highly motivated intern to join his Washington, DC office from January through April. Candidates should be collegial, professional, quick learners, and phenomenal team players. Strong oral and written communication skills and close attention to detail are imperative. Duties include assisting staff with legislative, administrative, and press related projects, writing memos and talking points, attending hearings and meetings, answering constituent phone calls, leading tours of the US Capitol, assisting with scheduling, sorting and distributing mail, and managing tour and flag requests. Full-time candidates with California ties and previous internship/work experience are strongly encouraged to apply. This is an unpaid internship. Please e-mail a resume, cover letter and dates of availability to Garamendi.Internships@mail.house.gov.
The Office of Congresswoman Chellie Pingree (ME-01) is seeking a full- or part- time intern for our Washington, D.C. office for the spring semester (January- May 2015). Qualified candidates are well organized, have good oral and written communication skills, and possess a strong interest in learning about the political process and congressional affairs. The intern will assist in the day-to-day operations of a DC Congressional office by supporting members of staff with constituent communication, legislative research, and administrative activities. Maine or New England ties are appreciated but not necessary. Applications will be considered on a rolling basis. Interested candidates should send a resume and cover letter detailing availability to our intern coordinator, Evan Johnston, at evan.johnston@mail.house.gov. No calls or walk-ins please.
Representative Rick Larsen (WA-02) is currently seeking a full-time intern to start the first week of January with a flexible end date. Ideal candidates have excellent writing and research skills, a positive attitude, and a willingness to complete tasks as assigned. Intern responsibilities include researching and writing Congressional correspondence, helping constituents find information and fielding constituent phone calls. This internship also provides the opportunity to work closely with staff members and assist in various projects. Washington ties are highly-preferred, but are not required. If interested, please send a resume, cover letter and two references to: taylor.paquette@mail.house.gov. Please include “WA-02 Internship” in the subject line.
The Office of Congressman Gene Green (TX-29) is currently seeking a full-time intern for our Washington, D.C. office for the spring session (January-May 2015). Qualified candidates are well organized, with good oral and written communication skills, and possess a strong interest in learning about the political process and congressional affairs. Duties include but are not limited to, answering phones, compiling briefing binders, performing legislative research, assisting in press work, and attending briefings. This opportunity offers a great opportunity to see the inner workings of a congressional office from a senior member. Applicants must be detail oriented with a strong work ethic and an eagerness to
 MEM-403-14
 MEM-402-14
 MEM-399-14
Page 2 of 14

 MEM-398-14
represent the 29th district of Texas. Also, an intern with Texas ties and Spanish proficiency is preferred but not mandatory. Interested candidates should send a resume and cover letter to our intern coordinator, Kendrick Vela, at Kendrick.Vela@mail.house.gov.
The Washington, DC, office of a Senior Member of the Ways and Means Committee has unpaid Press internship openings to begin immediately. Press interns are expected to work long hours and commit between 3-5 days per week. Internship duties include, but are not limited to compiling and daily clips, drafting press releases and op-eds, proofreading and editing, maintaining press lists, updating Member's communications calendar, website and social media platforms. Intern may also assist with answering phones, incoming and outgoing mail, addressing constituent concerns, and assisting the Legislative/District office staff. Strong writing skills are needed and familiarity with new media and website development is a plus. Priority will be given to those with journalism or communications education/experience. The ideal candidate will be creative, motivated, mature, detail-orientated, and possess the ability to multi-task under high pressure. This is a great opportunity for college students and recent graduates. To apply for the position, please send your cover letter, resume and writing sample addressed to the Comm. Director at ny13intern@gmail.com with the subject: Press Intern.
Congressman Mark Meadows (NC-11) seeks motivated, detail-oriented, personable and organized interns to join his Washington, DC office for the 2015 spring semester. Applicants should have strong conservative values, excellent communication skills, and a committed work ethic. Duties will include, but are not limited to: answering phones, processing mail, researching legislation, drafting correspondence, attending hearings and briefings, giving tours of the Capitol, and assisting front office staff. Applications are considered for this unpaid internship on a rolling basis; preference will be given to candidates who are available to intern full-time. Interested candidates should email a resume and cover letter to Ashley Howes at ashley.howes@mail.house.gov. North Carolina ties are preferred, but not required
A Conservative Republican from Florida is currently seeking un-paid interns for this Washington, D.C. office. Responsibilities will include, but not limited to, handling constituent phone calls, composing correspondence, conducting capitol tours, and attending congressional hearings and briefings. Candidates should be professional, organized, and eager to learn. Florida ties are preferred, but all applicants are encouraged to apply. Please email your cover letter, resume, and availability to FL11internship@gmail.com.
Congressman Jim Renacci (R-OH) seeks full time hard working intern for immediate hire. Responsibilities include, but aren’t limited to, answering phone calls, assisting with the mail program, providing constituent tours, attending various briefings, providing research for the legislative staff. Qualified candidates
 MEM-396-14
 MEM-394-14
MEM-392-14
 Page 3 of 14

 MEM-391-14
will have exceptional writing skills, strong communication skills, ability to work in a fast paced working environment, and have an interest in learning more about the legislative process. Send a resume and a cover letter to Stephen.Hostelley@mail.house.gov. Ohio candidates are strongly preferred.
The Office of Congresswoman Frederica S. Wilson (D-FL-24) seeks full-time and part-time interns for the Spring 2015 semester.
Opportunities will include:
 Working with staff to advance Congresswoman Wilson’s legislative priorities.
 Researching and drafting talking points, press releases, memos, letters, and social media posts.
 Supporting the press team by tracking and compiling press clips, organizing press conferences, and monitoring social media profiles.
 Attending hearings, meetings, and briefings.
 Interacting with constituents, interest groups, and renowned stakeholders.
 Providing administrative support such as answering phones, sorting mail,
leading capitol tours, managing flag requests, and undertaking special projects.
Candidates who reside in Florida’s 24th Congressional District or have ties to Florida are preferred. Candidates should have strong writing, communication, and people skills. Additionally, candidates should be available to serve from January through May/June. Please email a resume, cover letter, writing sample, and dates of availability to Jean.Roseme@Mail.House.Gov by Friday, December 12, 2014. Include “Spring Congressional Internship” in the subject line. This is an unpaid internship.
A Democratic California Congressman is seeking highly motivated interns to join his Washington, D.C. office for a part- or full-time, unpaid internship from December to March, with flexible start and end dates. Candidates should be organized, professional, quick learners, and team players. Strong oral and written communication skills and close attention to detail are important. Main responsibilities include but are not limited to: assisting staff with legislative and press-related projects, writing memos and talking points, attending hearings, and leading tours of the U.S. Capitol. Other responsibilities include: assisting with scheduling, answering phone calls, and processing mail. Candidates with California ties and previous internship/work experience are strongly encouraged to apply. Please e-mail a resume and cover letter to Intern.Resume@mail.house.gov.
Massachusetts Democratic office seeks an undergraduate or graduate level students as well as recent graduates for Winter/Spring 2015 internships. Intern responsibilities include greeting constituents, handling constituent phone calls,
 MEM-390-14
 MEM-388-14
Page 4 of 14

 MEM-387-14
opening and sorting mail, and assisting staff with administrative tasks. Interns will also have the opportunity to conduct legislative research, and assist with correspondence, as well as attend some Capitol Hill briefings, congressional hearings, receptions, and press events. All internships are unpaid, but if your college or university offers credit hours we are more than happy to complete any necessary evaluations. Massachusetts ties and previous internship experience preferred. Interested applicants should send a cover letter, resume, and available hours to NewEnglandResumes@mail.house.gov.
The Democratic Staff of the Committee on Science, Space and Technology is seeking full-time interns starting in January 2015. Interns are asked to work with staff to help prepare for committee hearings and markups. Interns will work on substantive research projects and press matters. Additionally, interns are critical to the daily operation of the office including tasks such as answering phones, greeting visitors, and filing official documents.
Interested applicants should visit the Committee’s website at http://democrats.science.house.gov/contact-us. Please fill out the application provided and send in a resume and two professional references.
The Washington, DC office of Congresswoman Lucille Roybal-Allard is seeking motivated, organized, and reliable individuals to fill internship positions through April/May. Intern responsibilities include, but are not limited to, answering phones, conducting Capitol Tours, sorting incoming mail, attending briefings, conducting legislative research and performing other administrative
tasks. Successful candidates will possess excellent written and oral communication skills, a strong attentiveness to detail, an ability to work in a fast- paced environment, an eagerness to learn about the political process and congressional affairs, as well as full week availability. Spanish-fluency and California ties are a plus. Please send a resume, cover letter, a short writing sample (no longer than one page), and dates of availability to Adam.Sachs@mail.house.gov with “Intern” in the subject line.
The office of Congresswoman Diana DeGette (CO-01) is seeking applications for internships starting in January 2015. As a fast-paced office for an active member of the Democratic leadership, we expect a lot from our interns and pride ourselves on an excellent internship program. Duties include, but are not limited to, answering phones, sorting mail, attending briefings, drafting constituent correspondence, and providing assistance to the legislative staff. Applicants must have excellent writing and communications skills. Interested applicants should email a cover letter and resume to tom.gibson@mail.house.gov with the subject line “Intern Application.”
The office of Congresswoman Diana DeGette (CO-01) is seeking applications for internships starting in January 2015. As a fast-paced office for an active member of the Democratic leadership, we expect a lot from our interns and pride
 MEM-386-14
 MEM-385-14
 MEM-384-14
Page 5 of 14

 MEM-383-14
ourselves on an excellent internship program. Duties include, but are not limited to, answering phones, sorting mail, attending briefings, drafting constituent correspondence, and providing assistance to the legislative staff. Applicants must have excellent writing and communications skills. Interested applicants should email a cover letter and resume to tom.gibson@mail.house.gov with the subject line “Intern Application.”
Congressman Benishek from Michigan’s First District seeks unpaid interns to fill positions for January through May 2015. Main responsibilities include answering phones, processing mail, drafting constituent correspondence letters, researching legislative issues, and attending meetings/hearings as needed. There will also be opportunities to attend receptions and seminars of interest. Candidates should be self-motivated, enthusiastic, flexible, and computer-literate (with a good understanding of MS Office). This is a great opportunity for college students seeking academic credit. Michigan ties are preferred. Please e-mail your cover letter, resume, and references to Samuel Grossman at samuel.grossman@mail.house.gov.
The Office of Congresswoman Eleanor Holmes Norton (D-DC) is seeking a full- time or part-time intern for the Spring of 2015. This is an opportunity to learn about the inner-workings of a congressional office on the Hill in a fast-paced work environment. The internship allows access to briefings and interesting events related to a wide range of important issues. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to, attending Congressional briefings, giving tours of the Capitol, conducting research, responding to constituent inquiries, and processing tour and flag requests. Qualified applicants should possess a professional and courteous demeanor, excellent communication skills, the ability to multi-task, fastidious attention to detail, and interest in the legislative and governmental process. To apply, please send a resume, three references, writing sample, and cover letter to william.washington@mail.house.gov, with the subject ‘Norton Internship’. No phone calls or drop-ins please.
Congressman Gregory W. Meeks (NY-05) is accepting applications for legislative internship positions available in his Washington D.C. office for the upcoming Spring term. This unpaid internship will provide an invaluable hands- on experience in a Congressional office and a greater understanding of the legislative process. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to, attending Congressional briefings on behalf of staff, giving tours of the Capitol, conducting research, responding to constituent inquiries, and processing tour and flag requests. Interns will also be given the opportunity to draft memos, write letters, and become a team member in a fast-paced and collegial office. Qualified applicants will possess a professional and courteous demeanor, excellent communication skills, the ability to multi-task, acute attention to detail, and interest in the legislative and governmental process.
This is an excellent opportunity for college students seeking Capitol Hill Page 6 of 14
 MEM-382-14
 MEM-381-14

 MEM-380-14
experience. All majors are encouraged to apply. Ties to New York’s Fifth Congressional District are preferred, but not required. Interested applicants should email a resume, cover letter, and a short writing sample to Jordan.Morris@mail.house.gov with “Your Last Name-Internship App” in the subject line. Please also include dates and times of availability.
The Office of Congresswoman Eleanor Holmes Norton (D-DC) is seeking a full- time or part-time Press and Social Media intern for the Spring of 2015. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to compiling press clips, monitoring daily news, drafting talking points and press releases, updating social media and working closely with the communications director. The ideal candidate will have previous experience in public relations or journalism, possess strong written communications skills, ability to work in a fast-paced environment, and professional manner. Please note that the internship is unpaid and housing is not provided, but student can qualify for academic credit depending on the requirements of the college or university. Interested applicants should e-mail a cover letter, resume, short writing sample (in the form of a speech or press release) and dates of availability with "Norton Internship" in the subject line to Jason.spear@mail.house.gov. No phone calls or drop-ins please.
The DC office of Congressman Derek Kilmer, hailing from Washington’s 6th district, is looking for personable, diligent full-time or part-time interns to start for winter session (December/January – early spring). This is an opportunity to learn about the inner-workings of a congressional office on the Hill in a fast- paced work environment. The internship allows access to briefings and interesting events related to a wide range of important issues. Responsibilities include assisting with constituent correspondence, producing daily press clips, and leading tours of the Capitol. This is a unique opportunity and prime for students or recent grads who are interested in learning about the legislative process or may eventually want to work for the federal government.
To apply, please send a resume, contact information for two references, and a cover letter outlining your interest in the position to nwcongressionalinternship@gmail.com, and expect a response within a week. Those with Washington state ties strongly encouraged to apply. We look forward to hearing from you!
Nevada Republican seeks an intern for the Spring 2015 semester. Interns will work in a fast-paced Congressional Office, gaining valuable exposure and knowledge of the legislative process and the United States Congress. Intern responsibilities include greeting constituents, handling constituent phone calls, opening and sorting mail, and assisting staff with administrative tasks. Interns will also have the opportunity to conduct legislative research, and assist with correspondence, as well as attend Capitol Hill briefings, congressional hearings, receptions, and press events. Our office is looking for an intern with a positive attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills.
 MEM-379-14
 MEM-377-14
Page 7 of 14

 MEM-376-14
Successful interns will be self-starters, take and listen to direction, and be willing to work both independently as well as part of a team environment. Applicants should have working knowledge of current events and policy topics, as well as a willingness to do assist with daily office tasks. Nevada ties preferred. Interns must be able to commit three full days a week (9:00am-6:00pm) at minimum. Students welcome to apply. Those interested please send resume and cover letter to kelsey.wolfgram@mail.house.gov.
The office of Congressman Bill Johnson (R-OH) is currently seeking highly motivated and organized applicants for a full or part-time unpaid internship for the 2015 spring internship program. Starting dates run from early January with flexible end dates. Candidates should possess interest in the legislative process, excellent communication skills, and attention to detail. Responsibilities will mostly include, but are not limited to: answering phones, leading tours of the U.S. Capitol, attending and summarizing hearings and/or briefings for legislative staff, and performing various administrative tasks. Ohio ties are preferred, but are not required. The months of the internship may vary depending on the availability or school schedule of the applicant. If interested, please send a resume and cover letter to intern.oh06@gmail.com with "2015 Spring Internship" in the subject line. No phone calls or walk-ins will be accepted.
Congresswoman Annie Kuster (NH-2) seeks energetic, motivated, and detail- oriented winter and spring interns for DC office. Responsibilities include, but are not limited to: staffing the front desk area and greeting all office visitors, leading constituents on capitol tours, processing mail, attending hearings and meetings, researching issue areas and writing legislative briefings and memos, and providing general administrative support for staff and the Member. New England ties preferred. All internships are unpaid. Please send cover letter and resume to NH02.Internship@mail.house.gov along with your dates of availability. No phone calls or walk-ins, please.
The Office of Congressman Robert A. Brady (PA-01) seeks interns for Spring 2015 (Jan-May). Internship responsibilities will include: assisting with research, processing mail, data entry, reception duties, office errands, and other duties as assigned by the Intern Supervisor. Ideal candidate will have strong oral and written communication abilities, a willingness to learn, basic knowledge of the political process, and a firm opinion on the best cheesesteak in Philadelphia. Pennsylvania ties preferred. Both full and part time will be considered. Please send a resume, cover letter (including availability), and writing sample to Liz Leibowitz at liz.leibowitz@mail.house.gov. Please no phone calls or drop-ins.
Progressive Maryland Democrat seeks qualified interns to join her District office for unpaid Constituent Services and Outreach internships during the Spring 2015 term (January – April/May).
Constituent Service Internship - Constituent Service Interns will work in the Page 8 of 14
 MEM-375-14
 MEM-374-14
 MEM-373-14

 MEM-372-14
District office to assist Constituent Service Representatives. Responsibilities include assisting with constituent files, gathering information from federal agencies, and answering constituent calls. S/he will monitor congressional inquiries through online databases.
Outreach Internship - The Outreach Intern will work in the District office supporting the team with a variety of outreach projects and activities, including event planning, and advocacy communications. The Outreach Intern also conducts project research using the web and traditional sources such as booth set up at events. S/he helps develop several databases and lists of state, local/civic, and federal organizations and government agencies. S/he must monitor local and national media through print, online/blog and television news media. The Outreach Intern also responds to outreach-related initiatives and assists with general outreach efforts.
Ideal candidates for both positions will be detailed oriented, well organized, and able to conduct research. Interns should also possess strong written and verbal communication skills in a professional setting. Undergraduates and recent graduates of any major with ties to Maryland are strongly encouraged to apply. Please email a resume, cover letter stating your availability, and a brief and relevant writing sample (maximum one page) by November 28th to internship.md04@mail.house.gov.
Progressive Maryland Democrat seeks qualified interns to join her Washington, D.C. office for an unpaid legislative internship during the Spring 2015 term (January – April/May). Applicants should have a familiarity with the legislative process and have a desire to learn while being a part of a hardworking team. Ideal candidates will possess strong writing and verbal communication skills, a demonstrated interest in legislative issues, the ability to multi-task and conduct research, and an enthusiastic attitude. Interns will have the opportunity to assist staff with legislative and scheduling projects, attend briefings and hearings, draft memos, sort and distribute mail, and give Capitol tours. Candidates with Maryland ties are strongly encouraged to apply. Please email a resume, cover letter stating your availability, and a brief and relevant writing sample (maximum one page) by November 28th to internship.md04@mail.house.gov.
The Office of Congressman Michael Capuano (D-MA) is seeking full-time interns to aid our administrative and legislative teams. Responsibilities include: researching legislative issues, attending legislative hearings, answering phone calls, processing constituent mail, giving Capitol tours, and assisting in any other special projects/tasks that may arise. Applicants should be self-motivated, reliable, hardworking, and have strong communication skills. Massachusetts ties preferred, but not required. Previous internship experience is a plus.
Spring 2015 internships start early January and run through the end of the semester (usually the middle of May). Internships are unpaid. Academic credit is
 MEM-367-14
Page 9 of 14

 MEM-365-14
MEM-363-14
available.
Interested candidates should submit a resume, cover letter, and a one-page writing
sample to juliet.albin@mail.house.gov.
Congressman Vern Buchanan (R-FL-16) has full-time and part-time, unpaid internships available for the spring session (January-May) in his Washington, DC office. Qualified candidates should possess excellent organizational and communication skills, should have a positive attitude, and a strong work ethic. Although internships are unpaid, our office is happy to fill out any necessary forms for students to receive credit at their respective college or university. All interested individuals should submit a cover letter and resume to jillian.gates@mail.house.gov with “2015 Spring Internship” in the subject line.
The Washington, DC office of Congresswoman Louise Slaughter (D-NY) is offering internship opportunities for students and recent graduates starting immediately. First-hand experience in Congresswoman Slaughter's office will provide interns with an unparalleled knowledge and understanding of the development of public policy and government affairs. Intern responsibilities include drafting letters to constituents, attending committee hearings, writing summary briefs, researching various issues for the legislative staff and assisting with additional office duties.
Interns will receive unique insight into the legislative process and parliamentary procedure as a result of Congresswoman Slaughter's position as the Ranking Member of the House Rules Committee. The Rules Committee determines the parameters of debate for all major pieces of legislation before it can be considered on the House Floor, including which amendments can be offered.
The internship provides different opportunities with staff to discuss their experiences on the Hill and future employment strategies. Applicants should e- mail a cover letter, resume, and a one to three page writing sample to James Blum at NY25.InternApplications@mail.house.gov. Please do not hesitate to contact James at (202) 225-3615 with any questions.
The Office of Congresswoman Eddie Bernice Johnson is seeking full-time and part-time unpaid interns for the Spring 2015 semester in the member’s Washington D.C. office. Responsibilities will include assisting the administrative and legislative staff with writing, legislative research, constituent services, and attending various briefings and hearings. Candidates should be self-motivated, detail oriented and possess strong oral and written communication skills. This is an excellent opportunity to gain experience on Capitol Hill while learning about the legislative process. Texas ties are preferred, but not required. If you are interested in this internship opportunity, please e-mail a cover letter, resume, references and a writing sample to DCintern.tx30@gmail.com. Please no phone calls or walk-ins.
  MEM-360-14
 Page 10 of 14

MEM-359-14
MEM-358-14
The office of a NY Congressman seeks an unpaid press intern with exceptional writing and editing skills. Duties will include: authoring interesting and creative content for the website on various topics and other tasks as assigned. The intern must be highly motivated and have excellent writing and communication skills. All interested and qualified candidates should email a resume and three writing samples: two previous articles and one hypothetical article about a congressman who has secured a grant for his district. Please submit all inquiries to: pressinterns08@mail.house.gov.
Energetic NY Democrat is seeking a highly motivated legislative intern to join his Washington, DC office for a part time unpaid internship in the Spring. Candidates should possess a professional and courteous demeanor, interest in the legislative process, excellent communication skills, the ability to multi-task, attention to detail, and a sense of humor. Main responsibilities include, but are not limited to, attending Congressional briefings, responding to constituent correspondence, assisting with flag requests, and general office duties. Candidates with New York ties and previous internship/work experience are strongly encouraged to apply. Please e-mail a resume, cover letter, and a short writing sample to NY.ResumeInbox@mail.house.gov. Equal opportunity employer. No calls or walk-ins please.
Congressman Blaine Luetkemeyer (MO-3) is currently seeking interns in his Washington, D.C. office for Spring 2015 (January-May). Interns perform a variety of responsibilities, including answering phones, receiving guests, and providing tours of the Capitol Building. They will also research legislation for the legislative staff, attend hearings and briefings, and answer constituent letters on various issues before the House. Interns should possess strong research, writing, analytical, and interpersonal skills. Moreover, candidates should express an interest in politics and conservative values. All internships are unpaid. However, if your college or university offers credit hours we are happy to complete any necessary evaluations. Interested candidates should contact Claire Trokey and email their resume and cover letter to: claire.trokey@mail.house.gov.
The office of Congressman Albio Sires (NJ-08) seeks motivated, well-organized interns for our Washington, DC office on a full or part-time basis. Excellent writing and communication skills as well as good judgment are essential. Duties will include assisting staff with correspondence and research, attending hearings and briefings, greeting guests, answering phones & other duties as needed. If you are interested, please fax a cover letter, resume, and writing sample to 202-226- 0792.
Midwest Democrat is seeking interns for the spring 2015 semester. Interns will work in a fast-paced Congressional Office, gaining valuable exposure and knowledge of the legislative process and the United States Congress. Interns will have the opportunity to conduct legislative research, assist with correspondence,
  MEM-356-14
 MEM-355-14
MEM-354-14
Page 11 of 14

 MEM-353-14
as well as attend some Capitol Hill briefings, congressional hearings, and press events. Intern responsibilities will also include greeting constituents, handling constituent phone calls, opening and sorting mail, giving Capitol Tours, and assisting staff with administrative tasks. This internship is unpaid.
Qualifications:
Interns must have a good attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Successful interns will be able to find information with little assistance, be able to work both independently as well as part of a team, and have strong attention to detail. Applicants should have working knowledge of current events and policy topics, as well as an interest in American Government, fiscal issues, education and reproductive rights. Wisconsin ties a plus.
Requirements:
Interns must be able to commit to at least two full days per week (9:00 am-6:00 pm). Please submit resume and 2 one page writing samples to Nairobi.cratic@mail.house.gov by December 15th, 2014.
The Office of Congressman John K. Delaney is looking for highly qualified students or recent college graduates to serve as interns in our district offices in Gaithersburg and Hagerstown, MD for the 2015 Spring semester. Interns are an integral part of the team and are given substantial opportunities to learn and grow in a fast-paced and active office. Our district office interns work with us as full- fledged members of our staff and are responsible for assisting other staff with constituent outreach, casework, and office management. As a part of these responsibilities, interns will be asked to answer phones, meet with constituents, write letters, process incoming casework, and research casework issues for field representatives. In addition, interns may be assigned to assist in various constituent casework or work on district-based projects of importance. As a result, interns learn about the constituent services component of every congressional office.
The ideal candidate will be professional, responsible, and friendly. They should be organized, eager to learn, able to work both individually and as part of a team, perform well under pressure, and adapt to rapidly changing situations. Preference will be given to applicants who can work a minimum of 30 hours per week and give a 10-week minimum commitment. Specific start and end dates as well as the weekly schedule are negotiable.
This is an unpaid internship; however, academic credit can be arranged through participating institutions. Interested applicants must send a cover letter and resume to MD06.Internships@mail.house.gov.
Interns will work in a fast-paced Congressional Office, gaining valuable exposure and knowledge of the legislative process and the United States
 MEM-352-14
Page 12 of 14

 MEM-351-14
Congress. Interns will have the opportunity to conduct legislative research, assist with correspondence, as well as attend some Capitol Hill briefings, congressional hearings, and press events. Intern responsibilities will also include greeting constituents, handling constituent phone calls, opening and sorting mail, giving Capitol Tours, and assisting staff with administrative tasks. This internship is unpaid.
Qualifications:
Interns must have a good attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Successful interns will be able to find information with little assistance, be able to work both independently as well as part of a team, and have strong attention to detail. Applicants should have working knowledge of current events and policy topics, as well as an interest in American Government. Wisconsin ties a plus.
Interns must be able to commit to at least two full days per week (9:00 am-6:00 pm). Please submit resume and 2 one page writing samples to Nairobi.cratic@mail.house.gov by December 15th, 2014.
Washington, D.C. — Rep. Xavier Becerra is looking for interns for his Leadership office with availability beginning in January. Responsibilities include (but are not limited to) assisting in preparing Caucus events, answering phones, providing constituency outreach support to Democratic Members of Congress and their staff, conducting research, extracting and formatting large quantities of data, writing detailed memos, attending relevant briefings and meetings, and assisting with team projects. Applicants should be self-starters, motivated, detail- oriented, possess excellent verbal and written communication skills, and be able to problem solve and multi-task. Experience or interest in social media is a plus. Minorities are strongly encouraged to apply.
Applicants must be either college/graduate students receiving academic credit or congressional internship/fellowship program participants. The intern should be prepared to start working in full-time.
Applications will be reviewed on a rolling basis. To apply, please send a cover letter and resume to caucusinternresume@mail.house.gov.
Progressive New England Democrat is seeking highly motivated individuals for unpaid Congressional internship for Spring 2015. Responsibilities include drafting constituent letters, assisting legislative staff with research, assisting with front office duties, and various administrative tasks. Candidates must possess strong writing and communication skills and be able to work 3-5 days per week. Ties to Rhode Island are strongly preferred. To apply, please send resume with references, cover letter, and brief writing sample to RI01Internship@gmail.com.
 MEM-350-14
 Page 13 of 14

MEM-349-14
The Office of Congressman Reid Ribble is seeking qualified candidates to intern full time in our Washington, D.C. office starting in January 2015. We are interested in candidates of all academic disciplines.
Interns will assist the staff with a variety of tasks, including office administration, legislative research, constituent correspondence, and other duties as assigned. Administration will include daily tasks such as welcoming guests, being aware of the Congressman’s and staff’s schedules, answering phones, constituent tours, mail administration, and other duties. Legislative research and constituent correspondence will include being aware of current and pending legislation, researching legislation for constituent correspondence, attending briefings, and other duties.
Candidates should have excellent writing and communication skills, strong organizational abilities, a good work ethic, an ability to work independently, and the drive to take the initiative in a fast-paced environment.
If candidates have any questions or wish to apply, please send resume, writing samples, and references to jeffrey.kuckuck@mail.house.gov.
 Page 14 of 14
