 ________________________________________________________________________
House Vacancy Announcement and Placement Service (HVAPS)
B-235 Longworth House Office Building Washington, D.C. 20515 202-226-5836
Vacancy Bulletins are available for pick-up in
Longworth HOB - B-227 (CAO First Call Customer Service Center) or in the CAO Human Resources Office - Ford HOB 102
To Subscribe or Unsubscribe to the Vacancy Listserv visit:
http://www.house.gov/content/jobs/
Job Line: 202-226-4504 _____________________________________________________________________________
 MEM-218-14
INTERNSHIP VACANCY LISTING
Week of July 7, 2014
Fall Internship Opportunity- Congressman Amodei’s Washington, D.C. Office
A congressional internship on Capitol Hill provides students with the unique opportunity to cultivate research and writing skills while gaining important professional experience. Interns in Congressman Amodei’s office will work closely with staff to learn about the legislative process.
Responsibilities include:
 Answering phones
 Legislative research
 Providing historical tours of the US Capitol for constituents
 Attending committee hearings and briefings
 Assisting staff with special projects
To apply, please send a cover letter and resume to Lauren Currie at
Lauren.Currie@mail.house.gov.
 Page 1 of 6

MEM-217-14
The office of Congressman Raul Labrador (ID-01) is currently seeking unpaid interns in the Washington, D.C. office for fall 2014. Start/stop dates are flexible. Basic intern responsibilities include, but are not limited to, answering phones, sorting mail, conducting tours of the U.S. Capitol, and assisting staff on various projects. Interns will have the opportunity to attend briefings and hearings of interest and see firsthand how a congressional office operates. Ideal candidates will have excellent research and writing abilities, be able to multi-task and interact well with constituents. College students and recent graduates will be considered. Course credit is available. Interested candidates should direct their resume and cover letter
to Alexa.walker@mail.house.gov.
The office of Congressman Buck McKeon (CA-25), Chairman, of the House Armed Services Committee, is seeking unpaid Interns for the Fall 2014 semester. Preference will be given to interns available to start by the beginning of August. Main responsibilities include answering phones, processing mail, drafting constituent correspondence letters, researching legislative issues, and attending meetings/hearings as needed. There will also be opportunities to attend receptions and seminars that interest you. Candidates should be self-motivated, enthusiastic, flexible, and computer-literate. This is a great opportunity for college students seeking academic credit. Applicants must be able to make a minimum commitment of four days a week. California ties a plus, but not required. Please e-mail your cover letter and resume to Zach Fisher at Zach.Fisher@mail.house.gov.
Representative Bill Johnson (OH-06) is currently seeking 2014 fall interns starting in August with flexible end dates. Responsibilities will mostly include, but are not limited to: greeting guests in the front office, answering phones, giving Capitol tours, attending and summarizing hearings and/or briefings for legislative staff, and performing various administrative tasks. Ohio ties are preferred, but are not required. The months of the internship may vary depending on the availability or school schedule of the applicant. If interested, please send a resume and cover letter to: intern.oh06@gmail.com. Please indicate your anticipated start and end dates. Please no phone calls or drop-ins.
Fall 2014 Intern for NY Congresswoman
Congresswoman Carolyn McCarthy (NY-04) is currently seeking interns for the 2014 fall semester in her Washington, DC office. Qualified candidates will possess an interest in the legislative process, excellent writing and communication skills, and a desire to work in the fast-paced environment of Capitol Hill. Ideal candidates will be
 MEM-216-14
 MEM-210-14
 MEM-209-14
Page 2 of 6

 MEM-208-14
professional, dependable, highly motivated, and adept at multi-tasking.
Responsibilities will include – but are not limited to – communicating with constituents via phone, drafting constituent correspondence, performing research requests, leading tours of the U.S. Capitol, and administrative work. Interns will also work closely with staff and have the opportunity to attend briefings, hearings, and other events on Capitol Hill.
Students or recent graduates with ties to New York State – especially the Fourth Congressional District and Long Island – are encouraged to apply. Full- and part-time candidates will be considered. The internship is unpaid.
To apply, please send a cover letter stating your availability, a resume, and a short 1-2 page writing sample to Sam Mayper at Sam.Mayper@mail.house.gov with “Fall 2014 internship” in the subject line.
The Democratic Staff of the Committee on Science, Space and Technology is seeking interns for the end of the summer and fall. Interns are asked to work with staff to help prepare for committee hearings and markups. Interns will work on substantive research projects and press matters. Additionally, interns are critical to the daily operation of the office including tasks such as answering phones, greeting visitors, and filing official documents.
Interested applicants should visit the Committee’s website at http://democrats.science.house.gov/contact-us. Please fill out the application provided and send in a resume and two references.
California Democratic Representative seeks Fall 2014 Intern
Congressman John Garamendi (CA-03) is seeking a highly motivated intern to join his Washington, DC office for the period August through November. Candidates should be collegial, professional, quick learners, and phenomenal team players. Strong oral and written communication skills and close attention to detail are imperative. Duties include assisting staff with legislative, administrative, and press related projects, writing memos and talking points, attending hearings and meetings, answering constituent phone calls, leading tours of the US Capitol, assisting with scheduling, sorting and distributing mail, and managing tour and flag requests. Full-time candidates with California ties and previous internship/work experience are strongly encouraged to apply. Please e-mail a resume, cover letter and dates of availability to Garamendi.Internships@mail.house.gov.
 MEM-206-14
 Page 3 of 6

MEM-205-14
Press Internship - A Western Democratic Congressional Office seeks a motivated, organized, and reliable college student or recent graduate wishing to gain Capitol Hill experience for a full-time, 10-week, unpaid press internship in Washington, D.C. The position is
available immediately. The press intern will help create graphics, develop press lists, send clips, prepare speeches, draft statements, and social media content. Please send a single PDF file containing your resume, cover letter, and a brief writing sample (preferably a press release or speech excerpt) to NV04internships@gmail.com. Please include in the body of the email a 3-5 sentence pitch for yourself: Why do you want to work on the Hill? Why should we choose you?
Nevada Congressman Steven Horsford is seeking current college students or recent college graduates wishing to gain Capitol Hill experience for a full-time or part-time semester internship to begin in August and/or September 2014.
We are seeking motivated, organized, and reliable individuals to assist the legislative and administrative staff with day-to-day duties. Such duties include assisting the legislative and communications staff, attending briefings and hearings, answering phones, drafting constituent correspondence letters, doing legislative research and various other tasks. The internship is unpaid, though interns will gain valuable Hill and office experience and will have access to many unique Hill opportunities. Nevada and District 4 ties are preferred, but not necessary.
Please send a resume and cover letter with anticipated start dates to NV04Internships@gmail.com. Please no drop bys or phone calls.
Democratic Member of Congress seeks a responsible, focused, self- motivated, enthusiastic, and organized Intern. Positions are available starting in August, and applications will be considered on a rolling basis. Duties will include, but are not limited to: answering phones, processing mail, researching issues, drafting correspondence, attending hearings and briefings, and maintaining a professional atmosphere. Strong writing and effective communication skills, as well as the ability to multi-task, are necessary. Although internships are unpaid positions, interns are treated as full participants in the Congressional office. If you are interested, e-mail a cover letter, resume, short writing sample, and contact info for three references to Parker Low at Parker.Low@mail.house.gov.
Congressman C.A. Dutch Ruppersberger is seeking interns for his District Office in Timonium for the Fall school semester. Interns will assist the Congressman and his staff in the overall day-to-day
 MEM-204-14
 MEM-203-14
 MEM-202-14
Page 4 of 6

 MEM-201-14
operations of the office by drafting letters of correspondence, processing mail, answering telephones, greeting visitors, and other duties as needed.
We are a small but fast-paced office and every effort will be made to give interns a worthwhile learning experience. Our internship positions are part-time and unpaid. A minimum time commitment is required. Candidates should be professional, possess strong oral and written communication skills, and have the ability to multitask. Only applicants with Maryland ties will be considered.
Interested applicants should email a cover letter, resume, and a short writing sample by July 31st to David.Heitlinger@mail.house.gov with Fall 2014 Internship in the subject line.
The Washington DC office of Congressman Patrick Meehan is currently accepting applications for the FALL 2014. Intern responsibilities include researching legislation for the Member and legislative staff, attending hearings and briefings, answering phones, day to day office duties, and answering constituent letters on various issues before the House of Representatives. As a result, interns learn about the legislative process and the many other functions of a congressional office. The hours are flexible, but generally run 8:30 AM – 5:30 PM when Congress is in session, and 9:00 AM to 5:00 PM when not in session. Interested applicants should submit a resume and cover letter to MeehanDCIntern@gmail.com. The deadline to apply is July 11, 2014. Ties to Pennsylvania’s 7th Congressional District are preferred, but not required.
Internships – Congressman Benishek from Michigan’s First District seeks unpaid interns to fill positions for September through December 2014. Main responsibilities include answering phones, processing mail, drafting constituent correspondence letters, researching legislative issues, and attending meetings/hearings as needed. There will also be opportunities to attend receptions and seminars of interest. Candidates should be self-motivated, enthusiastic, flexible, and computer-literate (with a good understanding of MS Office). This is a great opportunity for college students seeking academic credit. Michigan ties are preferred. Please e-mail your cover letter, resume, and references to Samuel Grossman at samuel.grossman@mail.house.gov.
The Office of Congresswoman Maxine Waters (CA-43) is seeking a full-time or part-time press and social media intern for the fall of 2014 in her Washington, D.C. office. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to compiling press clips, monitoring daily news, drafting talking points and press releases, updating social media and working
 MEM-200-14
 MEM-199-14
Page 5 of 6

 MEM-197-14
closely with the communications director. The ideal candidate will have previous experience in public relations or journalism, possess strong written communications skills, ability to work in a fast-paced environment, and professional manner. Please note that the internship is unpaid and housing is not provided, but student can qualify for academic credit depending on the requirements of the college or university. Interested applicants should e-mail a cover letter, resume, short writing sample (in the form of a speech or press release) and dates of availability with "Fall Press Intern 2014" in the subject line to latoya.veal@mail.house.gov. No phone calls or drop-ins please.
The office of Congressman Jim Bridenstine (OK-01) is seeking candidates for a full-time, paid internship from August 4 until November 21 in his Washington, D.C. office. Candidates must be politically conservative, highly motivated, detail oriented, and possess strong communication and organizational skills, while having a strong work ethic to complete tasks on a deadline.
Intern duties will include, but are not limited to answering constituent letters on various issues before the House, running errands, researching legislation for the Member and legislative staff, attending hearings and briefings, and answering phones. Interns will learn about the legislative process and the many other functions of a congressional office. First district of Oklahoma ties are preferred, but not required.
To apply, please submit your one page resume and a cover letter to mark.piland@mail.house.gov with the subject line Bridenstine Internship. We will acknowledge receiving your application and contact you if we wish to schedule an interview.
California Congressman Jared Huffman is seeking current college students or recent college graduates wishing to gain Capitol Hill experience for a full-time or part-time semester internship to begin September 1, 2014. We are seeking motivated, organized, and reliable individuals to assist the legislative and administrative staff with day-to- day duties. Such duties include attending briefings and hearings, answering phones, drafting constituent correspondence letters, doing legislative research and various other tasks. The internship is unpaid, though interns will gain valuable Hill and office experience and will have access to many unique Hill opportunities. California and District 2 ties are preferred, but not necessary.
Please send a resume and cover letter
to DCInternship.Huffman@mail.house.gov. Please no drop bys, phone calls, or emailing staff members.
 MEM-195-14
 Page 6 of 6
