 ________________________________________________________________________
House Vacancy Announcement and Placement Service (HVAPS)
B-235 Longworth House Office Building Washington, D.C. 20515 202-226-5836
Vacancy Bulletins are available for pick-up in
Longworth HOB - B-227 (CAO First Call Customer Service Center) or in the CAO Human Resources Office - Ford HOB 102
To Subscribe or Unsubscribe to the Vacancy Listserv visit:
http://www.house.gov/content/jobs/
Job Line: 202-226-4504 _____________________________________________________________________________
 MEM-068-15
INTERNSHIP VACANCY LISTING
Week of February 23, 2015
Congressman John Garamendi (CA-03) is seeking a highly motivated intern to join his Washington, DC office from March through June. Candidates should be collegial, professional, quick learners, and phenomenal team players. Strong oral and written communication skills and close attention to detail are imperative. Duties include assisting staff with legislative, administrative, and press related projects, writing memos and talking points, attending hearings and meetings, answering constituent phone calls, leading tours of the US Capitol, assisting with scheduling, sorting and distributing mail, and managing tour and flag requests. Full-time candidates with California ties and previous internship/work experience are strongly encouraged to apply. This is an unpaid internship. Please e-mail a resume, cover letter and dates of availability to Garamendi.Internships@mail.house.gov.
The Republican office of the Committee on House Administration seeks energetic and self-motivated individuals with an interest in government and public policy, to apply for its full-time Summer 2015 internship program. Working closely with Committee staff, interns will have the opportunity to gain
 MEM-067-15
Page 1 of 12

 MEM-066-15
first-hand knowledge of the inner-workings of a congressional committee and learn about the day-to-day administrative operations of the House of Representatives. Interns are responsible for assisting Committee staff with official proceedings (hearings/markups), oversight, research, assisting with phone inquiries, and providing support to all Committee staff. This is a paid internship. To apply, please send a cover letter, one page resume, and a writing sample to CHARep.Intern@mail.house.gov with “2015 Summer Internship” in the subject line.
Democratic Member of the House seeks an unpaid intern for their DC office. Responsibilities include assisting staff with general office duties, drafting constituent correspondence, attending briefings and hearings, answering phones, researching legislative issues, giving Capitol tours, greeting visitors and performing various other tasks. Candidate should be energetic, enthusiastic and able to thrive in a fast-paced working environment. Strong communication skills are a must. Candidates should have a general understanding of the governmental process, knowledge of North Carolina, and interest in the legislative process. If interested, please send a cover letter, resume, and writing sample via email to: nc12internjobs@gmail.com. Absolutely no phone calls or walk-ins. Minorities, LGBT and women encouraged to apply, North Carolina ties preferred but not required.
Congressman Jim Renacci (R-OH) seeks full time hard working intern for immediate hire. Responsibilities include, but aren’t limited to, answering phone calls, assisting with the mail program, providing constituent tours, attending various briefings, providing research for the legislative staff. Qualified candidates will have exceptional writing skills, strong communication skills, ability to work in a fast paced working environment, and have an interest in learning more about the legislative process. Send a resume and a cover letter to Stephen.Hostelley@mail.house.gov. Ohio candidates are strongly preferred.
The House Committee on Foreign Affairs Subcommittee on Asia and the Pacific seeks interns for the spring 2015 term.
The subcommittee intern is expected to be motivated and entrepreneurial, have strong written and oral communication skills, be detail-oriented, technically savvy, and perform a variety of tasks. The intern will assist with daily subcommittee operations such as research, database maintenance, fact checking, content editing, and proofreading. The intern will also assist with preparation and execution of subcommittee hearings such as conducting research and analysis, scheduling, and organizing documents for staff and members.
Proactive interns will be able to take advantage of this opportunity by participation in hearings, briefings, and meetings, as well as other opportunities to enhance their knowledge of Asia policy and professional life on Capitol Hill. Interns are expected to demonstrate a high level of professionalism and
 MEM-064-15
MEM-063-15
 Page 2 of 12

 MEM-062-15
MEM-061-15
reliability. All internships are unpaid.
Information about the subcommittee’s membership and recent activities can be found at http://foreignaffairs.house.gov/subcommittees/asia-and-pacific.
Interested candidates should send a resume and a cover letter explaining interest in the subcommittee’s work and qualifications for the position to hfac.asia.internship@gmail.com. Applications are due by March 13, 2015.
Democratic Congressman seeks applicants for full- or part-time unpaid press internship for Summer 2015. Duties will include tracking press clips and traffic on social media networks, updating and maintaining press contact lists, maintaining website, and assisting with the office’s day-to-day communications operation. Applicants should have a strong interest in political communications, news media, or journalism. Please send a resume, cover letter and writing sample to md06.internships@mail.house.gov by March 24th with “Summer Press Internship” in the subject line.
Democratic Congressman seeks applicants for full- or part-time unpaid congressional internship for Summer 2015. Duties will include conducting legislative research for staff, drafting memos on hearings and briefings, assisting with front office duties, answer constituent correspondence on matters related to the House, and performing basic administrative tasks. Candidates must exhibit strong writing and communication skills. Maryland residents or strong ties to Maryland are preferred. Please send a resume, cover letter and writing sample to md06.internships@mail.house.gov by March 24th with “Summer Congressional Internship” in the subject line.
The Washington, D.C. office of Representative Buddy Carter (GA-01) is currently seeking applicants for the remainder of the spring semester. Internships are available to qualified college students seeking college credit or recent college graduates. Positions are unpaid and serve to provide professional and educational value to participants as well as an understanding of our federal legislative process. Georgia ties are preferred, but they are not required. Responsibilities include but are not limited to: providing tours of the Capitol, answering phones, helping staff process constituents’ mail and inquiries. Other responsibilities may include assisting staff with legislative research, writing meeting briefings, and attending committee hearings. Candidates should possess an interest in the legislative process, strong communication skills, along with a motivation and organization. If you are interested in being considered for an internship, please send your resume, cover letter, and any relevant writing samples to Hart.Thompson@mail.house.gov. No drop-ins please.
Moderate Southern Democrat seeks applicants for part-time and full-time unpaid congressional internships in Washington, DC. Duties will include conducting legislative research, drafting memos and responses to letters from constituents,
  MEM-060-15
 MEM-057-15
Page 3 of 12

 MEM-056-15
assisting constituents and visitors to the office, assisting with day-to-day operations at the office, answering phones, leading tours of The US Capitol, running errands and performing basic administrative tasks. Candidates should possess superior written and verbal communication skills and an interest in learning the intricacies of the legislative process. Part-time interns will be expected to commit to at least two full day shifts (9:00am to 6:00pm) per week, Monday through Friday. Ties to Florida are preferred, though not required. Interested parties should submit a resume as well as two professional references to FloridaDemResumeRepository@gmail.com.
Congressman Kurt Schrader’s Washington, D.C. office is now accepting internship applications for the spring term. Interns will be responsible for assisting the team with phones, mail, tours, flag-requests, and related front office duties. Additional tasks, including drafting correspondence, research projects, and attending hearings may be assigned on a case by case basis. Undergraduate and post-graduate students are eligible to apply. Positions are unpaid and serve to provide professional and educational value to participants, but students have the opportunity to gain academic credit. Oregon ties are preferred. If interested, please contact our office at Julia.Stafford@mail.house.gov with "Spring Internship" in the subject line. Please include cover letter, resume and a writing sample.
Congressman Ron Kind (WI-03), a member of the House Ways & Means Committee, seeks full or part-time interns to start immediately in his Washington, DC office. Primary responsibilities include issue and legislative research, writing constituent mail, composing statements and press releases, administrative duties, and various other assignments. Washington, DC interns will have the opportunity to attend staff issue briefings and committee hearings to gain firsthand knowledge of how the legislative process works. The position is unpaid and interns are responsible for finding their own housing. Preference is for an individual who can work full-time from now through June but will also consider a flexible part-time schedule. Wisconsin ties are preferred, but not necessary. If interested, please send cover letter and resume to alex.eveland@mail.house.gov.
The Washington, DC office of Congressman Peter DeFazio (OR-04) seeks a highly motivated part-time intern to begin immediately for Winter/Spring 2015. Successful candidates will demonstrate that they are organized, detail-oriented, and professional. Strong written and oral communication skills are essential.
Intern responsibilities will include but are not limited to assisting staff with legislative, administrative, constituent relations, and press activities. Interns will: answer phones; sort, distribute, and respond to constituent mail; lead tours of the US Capitol building; attend hearings and briefings; and assist with legislative research.
 MEM-055-15
 MEM-054-15
Page 4 of 12

 MEM-053-15
Please send a resume, cover letter, and brief writing sample to michael.trujillo@mail.house.gov. Candidates with Oregon ties are strongly encouraged to apply. No phone calls or drop-ins, please.
The office of Congressman Ken Buck (CO-04) is seeking an intern to start immediately. Responsibilities include, but aren’t limited to, answering phone calls, assisting with the mail program, providing constituent tours, drafting correspondence, attending various briefings, providing research for the legislative staff, and assisting front office staff. Applicants should have strong conservative values, exceptional writing skills, strong communication skills, a committed work ethic, and have an interest in learning more about the legislative process. Interested candidates should email their resume to Nicole.Kirsch@mail.house.gov.
The Office of Congresswoman Tulsi Gabbard (HI-02) is seeking a full- or part- time national security intern for our Washington, D.C. office. Candidates should be well organized, have good oral and written communication skills, and possess a strong interest in learning about the legislative process, homeland security, defense, and intelligence issues. The intern will assist in the day-to-day operations of a DC Congressional office by supporting members of staff with constituent communication, and will also assist with legislative research and administrative activities. National security policy experience and Hawaii ties are appreciated but not necessary. Applications will be considered on a rolling basis. Interested candidates should send a resume and cover letter detailing availability to Christine.Wagner@mail.house.gov. No calls or walk-ins please.
Congressman Benishek from Michigan’s First District seeks unpaid interns to fill positions for February through May 2015. Main responsibilities include answering phones, processing mail, drafting constituent correspondence letters, researching legislative issues, and attending meetings/hearings as needed. There will also be opportunities to attend receptions and seminars of interest. Candidates should be self-motivated, enthusiastic, flexible, and computer-literate (with a good understanding of MS Office). This is a great opportunity for college students seeking academic credit. Michigan ties are preferred. Please e-mail your cover letter, resume, and references to Samuel Grossman at samuel.grossman@mail.house.gov.
The DC office of Congressman Derek Kilmer, hailing from Washington’s 6th district, is looking for personable, diligent full or part-time interns to start for the upcoming Spring term. This is an opportunity to learn about the inner-workings of a congressional office on the Hill in a fast-paced work environment. The internship allows access to briefings and interesting events related to a wide range of important issues. Responsibilities include assisting with constituent correspondence, producing daily press clips, and leading tours of the Capitol. This is a unique opportunity and prime for students or recent grads who are interested in learning about the legislative process or may eventually want to
 MEM-051-15
 MEM-050-15
 MEM-047-15
Page 5 of 12

 MEM-046-15
work for the federal government. To apply please send a resume, contact information for two references, and a cover letter outlining your interest in the position to nwcongressionalinternship@gmail.com, and expect a response within a week. Those with Washington state ties strongly encouraged to apply. We look forward to hearing from you!
New York Congressman Jerrold Nadler (D-NY) is seeking unpaid interns for the spring semester, preferably to begin in mid February and finish in late June. Interns will:
• Assist with office administrative tasks including, sorting incoming mail, greeting visitors, and answering the telephone.
• Assist in the preparation of constituent responses.
• Perform legislative research.
• Respond to requests from constituents.
• Attend briefings, hearings, and special events.
• Gain valuable Hill experience and learn about the federal legislative process.
Congressman Jerrold Nadler represents New York's 10th Congressional District, which includes the residents of most of the Upper West Side, Lower Manhattan and sections of Brooklyn. Congressman Nadler serves on the Judiciary Committee and on the Transportation and Infrastructure Committee, where he is the highest ranking member from New York. He is the Ranking member of The Subcommittee on Courts, Intellectual Property, and the Internet.
To Apply:
Please e-mail or fax a resume, brief cover letter, and 1-2 page writing sample to:
Email: Janice.Siegel@mail.house.gov Fax: 202-225-6923
The Office of Congresswoman Eddie Bernice Johnson is seeking unpaid interns to start immediately in the Washington D.C. office. Responsibilities include assisting the administrative and legislative staff with writing, legislative research, constituent services, and attending various briefings and hearings. Candidates should be self-motivated, detail oriented, and possess strong oral and written communication skills. This is an excellent opportunity to gain experience on Capitol Hill while learning about the legislative process. Texas ties are preferred, but not required. If you are interested in this internship opportunity, please e-mail a cover letter, resume, references and a short writing sample to Nawaid.Ladak@mail.house.gov. Please no phone calls or walk-ins.
Congressman Robert Aderholt (AL-4) seeks full-time or part-time unpaid interns for his Washington D.C. office for the spring semester. Intern duties will include, but are not limited to, answering the phone, providing constituent Capitol tours,
MEM-042-15
 MEM-039-15
Page 6 of 12

 MEM-036-15
assisting with the mail program, attending various briefings and hearings, and data entry. Qualified candidates will possess a strong sense of timeliness, excellent written and verbal communications skills, a positive attitude, and a solid work ethic. Ideal candidates will also have Alabama or Southern ties.
Those interested should email their resumes with the subject line “Internship Applicant” to Chris Lawson at chris.lawson@mail.house.gov.
New Jersey Democratic Congressman Frank Pallone (NJ-06) seeks full time and part time unpaid interns for his personal office during the spring 2015 semester. We are seeking personable, hardworking and motivated individuals with excellent oral and written communication skills.
Job duties will include, but are not limited to: answering phones, assisting staffers with general administrative duties, attending briefings, drafting letters to constituents, and conducting congressional research. New Jersey ties are strongly preferred, but not necessary. A good sense of humor is a plus.
Please email a resume, cover letter, and references to thomas.egan@mail.house.gov, please include your dates and times of availability. We have immediate vacancies to be filled.
The Committee on Education and the Workforce, Democratic Staff is currently seeking a press intern who would be able to start immediately. Applicants can be undergraduate or graduate and be willing to commit through mid-May. Interns perform a variety of tasks that support the staff in our legislative and media work. Media tasks may include helping organize and staff Committee press conferences, events and calls, updating and maintaining social media accounts, press list and contact management, drafting of talking points and press releases and assisting with the production of daily news clips relating to Committee issues. Press interns also perform administrative duties related to running the front office. Interested applicants should email their cover letter and resume to jobs_ewdems@mail.house.gov. Please include two short, relevant writing samples in your application materials. Please visit our website at http://democrats.edworkforce.house.gov/about/internships for more information.
The Office of Congressman John Ratcliffe (TX-04) is currently seeking interns for the Washington, D.C. office for the Spring 2015 semester. Intern responsibilities include but are not limited to, assisting staff with general office duties, attending hearings/briefings for staff members, answering phones, sorting through mail, drafting response letters, and giving tours of the U.S. Capitol. Candidates should be highly motivated and have good communication skills. This position is unpaid, but does offer a great educational experience for anyone with aspirations of working on the Hill. Having Texas ties is a plus. All interested applicants should send a cover letter and resume to Robert.peters@mail.house.gov.
 MEM-032-15
  MEM-031-15
 Page 7 of 12

MEM-029-15
Arizona Democrat seeks full-time hard working intern for immediate hire. Responsibilities include, but aren’t limited to, answering phone calls, assisting with the mail program, providing constituent tours, attending briefings, or providing research for the legislative staff. Qualified candidates will have exceptional writing skills, strong communication skills, ability to work in a fast paced working environment, and have an interest in learning more about the legislative process.
Send a resume and a cover letter to azdcinternships@gmail.com. Individuals with Arizona ties, women, and minorities are strongly encouraged to apply.
The Republican Office of the Committee on Science, Space, and Technology seeks energetic and self-motivated undergraduate or graduate level students, as well as recent graduates, with an interest in government and public policy for Summer 2015 internship. Working closely with Committee staff, interns will have the opportunity to gain first-hand knowledge of the inner-workings of a congressional committee and learn about the day-to-day administrative operations of the House of Representatives. Interns are responsible for assisting Committee staff with official proceedings (hearings/markups), oversight, research, assisting with phone inquiries and providing support to all Committee staff. Background in science a plus. To apply, please send resume and cover letter to ashley.smith@mail.house.gov.
Michigan Office seeks intern who will report to the Intern Coordinator and Chief of Staff.
CORE RESPONSIBILITIES:
• to assist in performing research, processing the mail, data entry, reception duties and other office errands.
QUALIFICA TIONS:
• good oral and written communication skills;
• ability to work cooperatively and courteously with others; • flexible schedule – Wednesday work day required;
• able to work at least 12 hours a week;
• ability to maintain calm in a high stress environment;
• preference for students from Michigan
• good organizational skills; and
• responsible, dependable and willing to learn.
DUTIES:
• performs research (CRS, the Library of Congress, MIN, or other available resources);
• sorts and distributes mail;
• attends committee meetings, intern conferences, and seminars;
 MEM-028-15
 MEM-027-15
Page 8 of 12

 MEM-024-15
• performs data entry, which involves logging in letters and constituent requests, including names and addresses of constituents;
• answers the telephones;
• checks faxes;
• notes constituent opinions, including their full names, addresses, and all relevant information;
• greets visitors and signs for deliveries; and performs other duties as assigned.
SEND ALL RESUMES AND ONE WRITING SAMPLE TO:
CapitolHill14@gmail.com
Spring Internship. The office of Representative Stephen Fincher (TN-08) is looking for motivated interns for the 2015 Spring semesters in the Washington, D.C. office. Intern responsibilities include assisting the staff with general office duties, attending briefings and hearings, answering phones, sorting mail, giving Capitol tours, and performing various other tasks based on ability and interests. Applicants must possess strong communication skills, have a positive attitude and be well-organized. Internship may be full-time or part-time to fit applicant's schedule. Interested candidates should send a cover letter and résumé to TN08.Intern@mail.house.gov.Tennessee ties preferred, but not required.
The Republican office of the Committee on House Administration seeks energetic and self-motivated individuals with an interest in government and public policy, to apply for its full-time Spring 2015 internship program. Working closely with Committee staff, interns will have the opportunity to gain first-hand knowledge of the inner-workings of a congressional committee and learn about the day-to-day administrative operations of the House of Representatives. Interns are responsible for assisting Committee staff with official proceedings (hearings/markups), oversight, research, assisting with phone inquiries, and providing support to all Committee staff. This is a paid internship. To apply, please send a cover letter and one page resume to CHARep.Intern@mail.house.gov.
The office of Congressman Alex X. Mooney (WV-2) is seeking full-time, paid and/or unpaid interns for Spring 2015 with immediate availability. Ideal candidates should be strong conservatives with excellent verbal and written communication skills. West Virginia ties are preferred, but not required. Responsibilities include answering phones and greeting visitors, sorting and inputting mail into IQ, facilitating Capitol tours, attending meetings/hearings, and assisting staff. Interested candidates should email their resume to Sean McMahon at sean.mcmahon@mail.house.gov with the subject line “Internship Application”.
Democratic Member of the House seeks unpaid intern in Washington, DC. Interested applicants submit a resume to Bklynny09@gmail.com.
Core Responsibilities:
 MEM-021-15
 MEM-019-15
MEM-016-15
   Page 9 of 12

  MEM-015-15
 To assist in performing research, processing the mail, data entry, reception duties and other office errands, and
 To draft floor statements, speeches and memorandums on legislative issues.
Qualifications:
 Must be a current student – with student identification
 Good oral and written communication skills;
 Ability to work cooperatively and courteously with others;
 Good organizational skills; and
 Responsible, dependable and willing to learn.
 Flexible schedule – a minimum of 12 hours of work per week,
Wednesday work day required.
Duties:
 Performs research (CRS, the Library of Congress, MIN, or other available
resources);
 Sorts and distributes mail;
 Attends committee meetings, intern conferences, and seminars;
 Performs data entry, which involves logging in letters and constituent
requests, including names and addresses of constituents;
 Answers the telephones;
 Notes constituent opinions, including their full names, addresses, and all
relevant information;
 Greets visitors and signs for deliveries; and
 Performs other duties as assigned by the Intern Supervisor.
Democratic Member of the House seeks unpaid intern in Washington, DC, starting in January. Responsibilities include assisting with social media campaigns and strategies, writing press releases, talking points and memos, conducting research and assisting the Press Staff with the day-to-day operations. Candidate should be energetic, enthusiastic and able to thrive in a fast-paced working environment. Creativity is a must. Previous experience in politics and press are not required but candidates should have a general understanding of the governmental process, knowledge of North Carolina, and interest in communications. If interested, please send a cover letter and resume via email to: NCCongressionalJobs@gmail.com (subject line should read: Social Media Intern). Absolutely no phone calls, e-mails or walk-ins, please. Minorities and women encouraged to apply, North Carolina ties preferred but not required.
The Office of Representative Sam Farr (CA-20) is looking for a full-time press intern to start immediately. Intern will be responsible for accumulating daily press clips, monitoring local news outlets, drafting social media statements and press releases and generally assisting the Communications Director. Intern will also be asked to assist staff with phones, mail, research, mail correspondence, and
 MEM-013-15
Page 10 of 12

 MEM-012-15
MEM-011-15
constituent tours. CA ties a plus. Sense of humor mandatory! Students welcome to apply. Please send resumes and a brief writing sample to Morgan.Keese@mail.house.gov
The office of Representative Marcia L. Fudge is looking for a motivated unpaid intern in the Washington, D.C. office. Intern responsibilities include assisting the staff with general office duties, attending briefings and hearings, answering phones, sorting mail, giving Capitol tours, and performing various other tasks as assigned. Applicants must possess strong communication skills, have a positive attitude and be well-organized. Interested candidates should send a cover
letter, résumé, and writing sample to District11resumes@mail.house.gov. Ohio ties preferred, but not required.
Chairman Candice S. Miller (R-MI) seeks legislative interns for the Winter/Spring 2015 semester. Interns will work in a fast-paced congressional office, gaining valuable exposure and knowledge of the legislative process and the United States Congress. Intern responsibilities include legislative research and writing, constituent relations, and assisting staff with administrative tasks. Interns will also have the opportunity to conduct historical tours of the Capitol, assist with constituent correspondence, and attend legislative briefings, congressional hearings, receptions, and press events.
Interns must have a good attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Successful interns will be able to find information with little assistance, be able to work both independently as well as part of a team environment, and possess a strong attention to detail. Applicants should have working knowledge of current events and policy topics, as well as a willingness to perform a variety of tasks and administrative functions. Michigan ties are strongly preferred; however, candidates from outside the state will be
considered. Undergraduate students are strongly encouraged to apply. This is an unpaid position but a great opportunity for students seeking academic credit, and the hours are flexible to accommodate the intern’s schedule.
Send a cover letter, resume, and brief writing sample to MI10Intern@gmail.com
Democratic Congressman seeks applicants for full- or part-time unpaid congressional internship for Spring 2015. Duties will include conducting legislative research, drafting memos, assisting with front office duties, and performing basic administrative tasks. Candidates must exhibit strong writing and communication skills. California residents or strong ties to San Diego are preferred. Please send a resume, cover letter and writing sample to ca52internships@gmail.com with “Spring Congressional Internship” in the subject line.
The Office of Representative Kevin Brady (TX-08) is currently seeking paid full- Page 11 of 12
 MEM-008-15
MEM-005-15
 
 MEM-002-15
time interns to start immediately in our Washington, D.C. office. Qualified candidates are well organized, with good oral and written communication skills, and possess a strong interest in learning about the political process and congressional affairs. Duties include but are not limited to, answering phones, compiling briefing binders, batching mail, performing legislative research, and attending briefings. Interns interact heavily with constituents so a positive attitude is a must. Applicants must be detail oriented with a strong work ethic and an eagerness to represent the 8th district of Texas. Previous Hill experience not required. Interested Candidates should send a resume and cover letter to: TX08intern@gmail.com.
Florida Republican seeks an intern for the Spring 2015 semester. Interns will work in a fast-paced Congressional Office, gaining valuable exposure and knowledge of the legislative process and the United States Congress. Intern responsibilities include greeting constituents, handling constituent phone calls, opening and sorting mail, and assisting staff with administrative tasks. Interns will also have the opportunity to conduct legislative research, as well as attend Capitol Hill briefings, congressional hearings and receptions. Our office is looking for an intern with a positive attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Successful interns will be self-starters, take and listen to direction, and be willing to work both independently as well as part of a team environment. Applicants should have a willingness to assist with daily office tasks. Florida ties preferred, but not required. Interns must be able to commit three full days a week (9:00am-6:00pm during Session and 9:00am- 5:00pm during Congressional Recess) at minimum. Students welcome to apply. Those interested please send resume and cover letter to FL26Internships@gmail.com.
 Page 12 of 12
