 ________________________________________________________________________
House Vacancy Announcement and Placement Service (HVAPS)
B-235 Longworth House Office Building Washington, D.C. 20515 202-226-5836
Vacancy Bulletins are available for pick-up in
in the CAO Human Resources Office - Ford HOB 102
To Subscribe or Unsubscribe to the Vacancy Listserv visit:
http://www.house.gov/content/jobs/
Job Line: 202-226-4504 _____________________________________________________________________________
INTERNSHIP VACANCY LISTING
Week of November 4, 2019
 MEM-579-19
The Office of Congressman Donald Norcross (NJ-01) seeks paid Press and
   Legislative interns for Spring 2020.
Press responsibilities will include updating press lists, drafting social media posts for the Member’s official social media pages (including Facebook, Twitter and Instagram), designing graphics and editing short video clips as needed. Ideal applicants will have experience with iMovie, Adobe Photoshop and social media. Legislative responsibilities include researching legislation for the legislative staff, attending hearings and briefings and drafting constituent letters on the Member’s behalf. All interns are expected to work collaboratively with the staff to answer phones, greet constituents and guide tours of the U.S. Capitol Building.
The Office of Congressman Norcross is an equal opportunity employer. We do not discriminate based on race, ethnicity, gender, sexual orientation, religion, national origin, age or socio-economic status. All are welcome and encouraged to apply. New Jersey ties are a plus but not required.
Applicants should send a resume, cover letter (including weekly availability and start date) and two references to Elizabeth.leer@mail.house.gov with the subject line “Last Name – Spring Intern – Legislative *or* Press” (please indicate).
 Page 1 of 33

    DC office who will be responsible for answering phones, running errands, researching legislation, answering constituent letters, and taking detailed briefing notes for staff.
The ideal candidate will have a demonstrated interest in learning about the legislative process, be highly articulate, as well as possessing strong organizational skills.
Start dates and weekly hours are negotiable for this paid internship, Florida ties are a plus. Please email resume and cover letter to Alex.Murglin@mail.house.gov.
About Congressman Steube: Congressman Greg Steube represents Florida’s 17th District in Congress. From 2010-2018, Steube used his background in the military, agriculture, and law, to advance conservative values as a member of the Florida House of Representatives (2010-2016) and Florida Senate (2016-2018). In Congress, Steube continues to champion these issues while serving on the House Judiciary, Oversight and Reform, and Veterans’ Affairs committees.
  MEM-578-19
The office of Congressman Greg Steube (FL-17) is seeking spring interns for his
MEM-577-19
The Office of Congresswoman Susan Wild (PA-07) is seeking a full or part-time press intern to assist a fast-paced press team in Washington D.C. Intern duties include drafting press releases and advisories, drafting digital content, sorting press clips, and assisting the press team with a variety of projects as needed.
The ideal candidate possesses strong writing skills and is passionate about public service. Adobe Premiere, Photoshop, and Illustrator skills a plus. Preference will be given to candidates who have completed their first year of college, who have Pennsylvania ties, and who are majoring in Communications, Journalism, Public Relations, English, Government or other related fields. At the top of your cover letter, please indicate that you are specifically interested in the press internship. Please be advised that though this is a press-focused internship, regular intern duties will also be assigned.
TO APPLY, please e-mail a resume and cover letter including desired start date and availability to wildinterns@gmail.com.
  MEM-576-19 The Office of Congresswoman Susan Wild (PA-07) has Spring 2020 openings for full and part-time congressional interns for her Washington, D.C. office.
Candidates should be motivated, flexible, and detail-oriented individuals with availability beginning immediately, and a preference will be given for those who can stay at least three months. Pennsylvania ties are a plus but are not required.
 Page 2 of 33

Intern responsibilities include answering constituent phone calls, leading tours of the Capitol, sorting mail and faxes, and assisting experienced staff with projects in diverse issue areas.
Candidates should be outgoing and possess strong oral and written communication skills, an ability to multitask in a fast-paced environment, and a good sense of humor. Candidates with Pennsylvania ties are strongly encouraged to apply.
TO APPLY, please e-mail a resume and cover letter including desired start date and availability to wildinterns@gmail.com.
  MEM-575-19
The House Foreign Affairs Committee Majority Staff is currently looking for a full-time intern to start immediately through the Spring 2020 semester.
Interns will be responsible for providing staff members with policy and administrative support. Duties may include answering phones, compiling press clips, attending staff briefings, performing legislative and policy research, drafting memoranda and other written materials, and a variety of other tasks.
Candidates should be team-oriented, resourceful, upbeat people who have skills beyond research and require little supervision. This internship is open to undergraduates (rising seniors and above), recent graduates, and Master’s and law students. Minorities, women, and LGBTQ persons are strongly encouraged to apply. Please note that this internship is unpaid.
If you would like to be considered for an internship please submit a one-page resume and cover letter in PDF format to hcfa.democrat@mail.house.gov and include “HFAC Internship Application” in the subject line of the email.
  MEM-574-19
Congressman Dan Newhouse (WA-04) is seeking paid interns for Spring 2019 in Washington, D.C. Interns will assist the legislative and administrative staff with various duties. Some duties include: attending briefings, answering phones, conducting Capitol tours, drafting constituent correspondence letters, and performing legislative research and analysis.
We’re looking for responsible individuals that are dependable, organized, and willing to learn. Internships are open to undergraduate students and college graduates. Washington state ties are encouraged but not required. To apply, please email a cover letter and resume to: Johnny.Alavez@mail.house.gov
CORE RESPONSIBILITIES:
•to assist in performing research, processing the mail, data entry, reception duties and other office errands.
QUALIFICATIONS:
•good oral and written communication skills;
•ability to work cooperatively and courteously with others;
  Page 3 of 33

•good organizational skills; and
•responsible, dependable and willing to learn.
DUTIES:
•performs research
•sorts and distributes mail;
•attends committee meetings, intern conferences, and seminars;
•performs data entry, which involves logging in letters and constituent requests, including names and addresses of constituents;
•answers the telephones;
•notes constituent opinions, including their full names, addresses, and all relevant information;
•greets visitors and signs for deliveries; and
•performs other duties as assigned by the Intern Supervisor
 MEM-573-19
The Office of Congressman Eric Swalwell is seeking an energetic press intern to join a fast-paced press shop for the spring semester. Opportunities will include compiling daily press clips, transcribing media hits, writing talking points and assisting communications staff with the creation of additional materials as needed.
The ideal candidate is a voracious consumer of news, detail-oriented and a self- starter who is familiar with graphic and/or video design. Applicants must have strong writing skills and be willing to work in high-stress situations. No calls or drop-ins please. California ties are a plus.
Applicants should send a resume, brief cover letter and one writing sample to Natalie.edelstein@mail.house.gov. Graphic design or video work is not required but recommended.
Please include: Press Intern Spring 2020, Last Name in the subject line.
  MEM-572-19
The Office of Congressman Daniel Lipinski (IL-03) is currently seeking interns for the spring semester in the Washington D.C. office. Prospective interns should have a love for politics and the legislative process, a desire to learn, and a willingness to work hard in this fast-paced office.
Day to day intern responsibilities include: drafting constituent correspondence, leading tours of the U.S. Capitol, working with legislative staff on policy issue research, attending briefings and hearings, and answering phones. Interns will work closely with legislative staff and will be given all the tools necessary to learn to become a congressional staffer by the end of the internship.
Applications can be submitted via email to IL03StaffAssistant@mail.house.gov. Applications are due by 5:00pm, Friday, November 8th. A complete application should include a cover letter, resume and one short writing sample of 2-3 pages.
  Page 4 of 33

Please be sure the application includes your name, contact information, university, year of graduation, dates you are available, and your intended work schedule (full time or part time). Third District of Illinois ties are preferred.
Please no drop ins.
 MEM-571-19
The Washington, D.C. office of Congressman Sean Casten (IL-06) is seeking candidates for a paid internship for Spring 2020 Interns will observe the inner workings of a Congressional office while gaining firsthand knowledge of the legislative process. DC responsibilities include leading Capitol tours, answering phones, assisting staff with legislative projects, attending briefings and hearings, and working on special projects.
Qualifications: Interns must have a pleasant attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Successful interns will be able to find information with little assistance, be able to work both independently and as part of a team and have strong attention to detail.
Interested applicants should visit the Congressman’s website https://casten.house.gov/services/internships/ or email Casten.Internship@mail.house.gov with “Internship Application” in the subject line. Please fill out the provided applications and attach a resume and cover letter. If you believe you are eligible for financial assistance, please also explain in 2-3 paragraphs why you believe you should receive assistance.
Applications will be accepted on a rolling basis. No drop ins, please. This office is an equal opportunity employer; we do not discriminate on the basis of race, color, religion, sex, national origin, age, disability, gender identity or expression, or sexual orientation. Full and part-time candidate with Illinois ties are preferred. Do not hesitate to contact the office if you have any questions regarding our internship program, 202-225-4561.
   MEM-570-19
The office of Congressman John Sarbanes (D-Md.) seeks highly motivated, personable and professional legislative interns to begin January 2020. Tasks include answering phones, handling incoming and outgoing mail, addressing constituent concerns, attending briefings and supporting legislative staff as needed.
Preferred candidates are current students or recent graduates with strong writing skills and close attention to detail. Successful candidates would spend 25-40 hours per week interning in the DC office. Maryland ties a plus.
To apply, please send a cover letter, a resume, list of references and availability to employment@mail.house.gov. If you have further questions, please call the Intern Coordinator at (202) 225-4016.
  Page 5 of 33

MEM-569-19 We are currently looking for fall and spring interns in Congressman Steven Palazzo’s office in Washington, D.C. Please email your resume, and cover letter to Bailey.senyitko@mail.house.gov.
Please complete the application
here https://palazzo.house.gov/uploadedfiles/intern_application_dc_office_.pdf
       motivated legislative intern to assist a fast-paced legislative team in the Spring 2020 semester.
Primary responsibilities will include: answering phones, running errands, researching legislation for the Member and legislative staff, attending hearings and briefings and answering constituent letters on various policy issues. As a result, interns learn about the legislative process and the many other functions of a congressional office. Candidates should have strong written and verbal communication skills, high attention to detail, and the ability to work under tight deadlines. This position would begin in January 2020.
Previous internship experience and Illinois ties are a plus. Please apply on https://schneider.house.gov/services/internships.
 MEM-565-19
The Office of Congressman Brad Schneider (IL-10) seeks a creative and highly
   motivated press intern to assist a fast-paced communications team in the Spring 2020 semester.
Primary responsibilities will include: compiling press clippings, creating and updating press lists, drafting social media content, and other writing projects. Candidates should have strong written and verbal communication skills, high attention to detail, and the ability to work under tight deadlines.
Previous internship experience and Illinois ties are a plus. This position would begin in January 2020. Please apply on https://schneider.house.gov/services/internships.
  MEM-564-19
The Office of Congressman Brad Schneider (IL-10) seeks a creative and highly
MEM-563-19
The Democratic office of the Committee on House Administration seeks self- motivated undergraduate or graduate level students, as well as recent graduates, with an interest in government and public policy to apply for its Fall 2019 internship. Working closely with Committee staff, interns will have the opportunity to gain first-hand knowledge of the inner-workings of a congressional committee and learn about the day-to-day administrative operations of the House of Representatives.
Interns are responsible for assisting Committee staff with official proceedings (hearings/markups), elections oversight, member services, and other projects, as well as providing general front office support.
 Page 6 of 33

 The Committee is committed to, and benefits from, a diverse staff, and qualified candidates of all backgrounds are encouraged to apply.
Interested applicants should send a cover letter, resume, and available hours to intern.CHADEM@mail.house.gov with the subject headline, “CHA Dem Internship.”
 MEM-562-19
The Washington, D.C. office of Congressman Mike Johnson (LA-04) is seeking candidates for full-time and part-time internships for the remainder of 2019 with the potential to extend into Spring 2020 with certain positions being paid.
Interns will have the opportunity to observe the inner-workings of a Congressional office while acquiring specific knowledge about the legislative process.
Responsibilities include leading Capitol tours, assisting staff with legislative projects, attending briefings and hearings, answering phones, and working on special projects. Louisiana ties are preferred but are not required.
Please apply online at https://mikejohnson.house.gov/services/internships.
  MEM-561-19
“The office of Congressman Paul Mitchell (MI-10) is currently looking to hire full time, paid interns in our Washington, DC Office for the Spring 2020 semester. The internship runs from January to May but start/end dates are flexible. Michigan ties are a plus but not required!
Responsibilities Include:
•Answering phones
•Sorting and distributing mail
•Giving Capitol tours
•Researching legislation for the Member and legislative staff •Attending hearings and briefings
•Other projects as assigned
Qualified applicants should possess strong oral and written communication skills, an ability to multitask, and a desire to learn about the legislative process and other functions of a congressional office.
To apply, please email a PDF Resume and Cover Letter to Faith.Mabry@mail.house.gov with the subject line “Spring 2020 Internship Application”. Please include dates available in your cover letter.”
  MEM-560-19 Congressman Paul Cook (CA-08) is seeking a highly motivated intern to join his Washington, DC office from November through January for a 3 month internship. Candidates should be motivated, professional, quick learners, and phenomenal team players. Strong oral and written communication skills and close attention to detail are important.
 Page 7 of 33

 Duties include assisting staff with legislative, administrative, and press related projects, writing memos and talking points, attending hearings and meetings, answering constituent phone calls, leading tours of the US Capitol, assisting with scheduling, and sorting and distributing mail. Full-time candidates with California ties and previous internship/work experience are preferred. This is a paid internship.
Please e-mail a resume, cover letter and dates of availability to
joe.tavares@mail.house.gov
 MEM-559-19 U.S. Rep. Lloyd Doggett (D-Texas) seeks interns for his Washington office the spring. Spanish skills and Texas connections a plus. Send resume, brief writing sample, and three references to DoggettJobs@mail.house.gov. Use the subject line: Spring Internship Application. No drop-ins please.
     a fall semester, financial services intern to assist the Senior Advisor covering the financial services portfolio. The person in this role will work on substantive financial services issues ranging from banking, housing, capital markets, fintech, insurance, monetary policy, etc.
This will not be a typical internship answering phones or giving tours. You will be attending hearings, monitoring legislation, assisting with industry and constituent correspondence, auditing briefings, etc. You will gain an in-depth understanding of working on the Hill and within the Committee. You should leave this internship with a better understanding of both the financial services industry as well as current policy that is impacting our the industry.
Specific responsibilities include, but are not limited to:
• Attend Committee hearings and briefings.
• Conduct legislative and policy research.
• Track and monitor legislation.
• Formulate hearing questions from witness testimony.
• Assist with preparation of hearing, markup, and Floor briefing books.
• Observe House proceedings.
• Acquire an understanding of Committee mechanics.
• Prepare memoranda on meetings, hearings, and briefings attended or
researched.
• Collect signatures from Member offices for letters, dissenting views, etc.
• Attend Congressional Research Training seminars. •
Ideal candidates must be hard working, have an interest in financial services, and
 a willingness to learn. Candidates do not have to have a background in financial
 services in order to be considered.
 MEM-558-19
A senior member serving on the House Financial Services Committee is seeking
Page 8 of 33

Please contact Ashley.gunn@mail.house.gov if interested.
  MEM-557-19
A senior-ranking Republican member on the Committee of Ways & Means is seeking candidates for full-time or part-time internships starting in December. Interns will observe the inner workings of a Congressional office while gaining firsthand knowledge of the legislative process.
D.C. responsibilities include leading Capitol tours, answering phones, assisting staff with legislative projects, attending briefings and hearings. Florida ties are strongly preferred.
Please send your resume and cover letter to housegopinternshipfl@outlook.com. No phone calls or drop-ins will be considered.
   MEM-556-19
Congressman John Ratcliffe – Spring Internship (Jan-May)
Congressman John Ratcliffe’s office is seeking intelligent and hardworking individuals for their spring internship program. Responsibilities would include giving Capitol tours, greeting visitors, answering the phone, sorting and logging constituent mail, and assisting in various administrative tasks.
Texas ties are preferred but not required. Interested candidates should email their resume to paige.boogaard@mail.house.gov.
  MEM-554-19
Southern Republican seeks motivated, detail-oriented, and energetic individuals for spring internships in Washington, DC.
Description: Southern Republican seeks motivated, detail-oriented, and energetic individuals for paid internships in Washington, DC. Qualified Applicants should have strong interpersonal skills, the ability to manage multiple tasks, possess strong writing skills, and demonstrate a solid work ethic.
Duties include: answering phones, leading tours of the Capitol, researching legislation for the Member and legislative staff, attending hearings and briefings and answering constituent letters on various issues before the House.
To apply, please send a resume, and cover letter with the phrase “Spring 2019 Internship Application” in the subject line to LA05.Intern@mail.house.gov. Please indicate expected start and end dates as well as hours available to work in your cover letter.
  MEM-553-19 JOB TITLE: Spring 2020 Intern
SUMMARY:
Interns are responsible for providing Senior and Professional Staff with policy
 Page 9 of 33

and administrative support. The individual is required to demonstrate exceptional research and organizational skills.
ESSENTIAL JOB FUNCTIONS:
• Performs legislative and policy research.
• Assists with the coordination and production of hearings and bill markups
 by: o
o
o
Researching background on witnesses and hearing topics. Finalizing documents for Members and Committee Staff. Delivering said documents to Members of the Committee.
• Oversees physical and digital Correspondence to and from the Committee.
• Conducts clerical work for the Office Manager and staff by:
o Answering Phones
o General office tidiness and maintenance
• Represents the Committee on Homeland Security during legislative and
policy negotiations, discussions and other activities.
•
QUALIFICATIONS:
Must be at least a Sophomore in college. Law school students and recent graduates are highly recommended to apply as well. Coursework and experience in Political Science, Government Affairs, Homeland Security Issues or a related field is preferred. Strong organizational skills; excellent oral and written communication skills; the ability to perform under pressure and tight deadlines. Must be familiar with Microsoft Office.
Applicants should send a resume, cover letter, and a short (1-2 page) writing sample to Amanda.Mims@mail.house.gov.
    internships for Spring 2020 in his Washington, D.C. office.
Responsibilities will include drafting memos and constituent letters, answering phones, assisting legislative staff with research, managing the front office, leading Capitol tours, greeting constituents, among other tasks.
Pennsylvania ties are preferred but not required. Interested candidates should send a cover letter and resume to PA09Jobs@mail.house.gov. Please no drop-ins or phone calls.
 MEM-552-19
Congressman Dan Meuser (PA-09) seeks applicants for part-time and full-time
MEM-551-19
The Office of Rep. Paul Tonko (NY-20) is seeking legislative interns for the Spring Semester. Qualified candidates have academic or professional experience in American politics, can work on extremely short deadlines, and excel at most or all of the following: writing, editing, and event support.
Intern duties will include assisting with administrative and legislative tasks, answering phones, processing mail, providing Capitol tours, and attending
 Page 10 of 33

briefings. Preference will be given to residents of the 20th district and Upstate New Yorkers. Interested applicants should email a cover letter, resume, 1-3 page writing sample, and dates of availability to katie.greenberg@mail.house.gov with “Spring Internship” in the subject field.
  MEM-550-19
The Office of Rep. Paul Tonko (NY-20) is seeking press intern to assist with fast-paced communications operation for Spring 2020. Qualified candidates have academic or professional experience in American politics, can work on extremely short deadlines, and excel at most or all of the following: writing, editing, event support, social media (esp. Facebook, Twitter, Instagram) and photography.
Intern duties may include:
Daily press clips
Answering phones
Drafting documents for distribution to media Messaging & interview prep documents Social media content development
Event photography ...and more!
Preference will be given to residents of the 20th district and Upstate New Yorkers. Interested applicants should email a cover letter, resume, 1-3 page writing sample and dates of availability to katie.greenberg@mail.house.gov with “Press Internship” in the subject field.
  MEM-549-19
The Office of Congresswoman Sylvia R. Garcia (TX-29) seeks a motivated, detail-oriented, and energetic individual for a legislative internship position this fall in Washington, DC. This internship will be an invaluable opportunity to gain hands-on office experience while learning about the legislative process.
Qualified applicants have strong writing and communication skills, the ability to manage multiple tasks, a strong sense of professionalism and demonstrate a solid work ethic. English and Spanish bilingual candidates with Texas ties are strongly encouraged to apply.
Responsibilities include but are not limited to: Drafting constituent correspondence on a variety of issues, leading Capitol tours, assisting legislative staff with research, answering and screening telephone calls, managing the front office, participating in hearing preparation, tracking media coverage, and other duties as necessary.
The position is available beginning in January 2020. To apply, send a resume and cover letter to ellie.valega@mail.house.gov with the subject “Spring Internship Application”. In your cover letter please indicate expected start and end dates, hours available to work, and if course credit is available for this internship.
  Page 11 of 33

This office is an equal opportunity employer: Women and minorities are strongly encouraged to apply. This office does not discriminate on the basis of race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity and expression, national origin, disability military status, age, marital status, or parental status.
 MEM-548-19
The Office of Congresswoman Sylvia R. Garcia (TX-29) seeks a press intern for the DC office for Spring 2020. Qualified applicants have very strong writing and communication skills, experience with video editing and content creation, a strong sense of professionalism and demonstrate a solid work ethic. Spanish speaking candidates with Texas ties are strongly encouraged to apply.
Responsibilities include but are not limited to: working closely with staff to draft social media content on a variety of issues and social media platforms, tracking media coverage, executing daily press clips, and editing the weekly video shoot.
The position is available beginning in January 2020. To apply, send a resume and cover letter to ellie.valega@mail.house.gov with the subject “Spring Press Internship Application”. In your cover letter please indicate expected start and end dates, hours available to work, and if course credit is available for this internship.
This office is an equal opportunity employer: Women and minorities are strongly encouraged to apply. This office does not discriminate on the basis of race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity and expression, national origin, disability military status, age, marital status, or parental status.
  MEM-547-19
Congressman Conor Lamb (PA-17) has Spring 2020 openings for full and part- time congressional interns for his Washington, D.C. office. Candidates should be motivated, flexible, and detail-oriented individuals with availability beginning in January, and a preference for those who can stay at least three months. Pennsylvania ties are a plus but are not required.
Intern responsibilities include answering constituent phone calls, leading tours of the Capitol, sorting mail and faxes, and assisting experienced staff with projects in diverse issue areas. Candidates should be outgoing and possess strong oral and written communication skills, an ability to multitask in a fast-paced environment, and a good sense of humor. Candidates with Pennsylvania ties are strongly encouraged to apply.
Please e-mail a resume and cover letter including desired start date and weekly availability to lamb.tours@mail.house.gov
   MEM-546-19 The Office of Congressman Jared Huffman (D-CA) seeks a Communications/Digital Fellow. Qualified candidates will have strong writing, editing, and social media skills, as well as basic familiarity with graphic
 Page 12 of 33

design/video editing software. One to two years of experience in a press or digital media role (including internships) preferred. California ties are a plus!
This position requires the ability to thrive under pressure, multi-task, and
work in a team environment. Candidates must have strong written and verbal communication skills, with the desire to come up with creative communications ideas and the ability to work under tight deadlines. The fellow will work closely with the Communications Director and the legislative staff of Congressman Huffman.
Responsibilities include:
●Drafting social posts
●Maintaining/updating website
●Designing graphics + editing photos/videos
●Assisting with drafting speeches, press releases, op-eds, advisories, and other written materials
●Creating and maintaining media lists
Interested applicants should email a resume, two writing samples, and two digital samples to huffmanpressfellow@gmail.com with the subject line “Last Name - Press Fellow.” This is a full time position and offers a monthly stipend
     full-time interns for the fall 2019 semester (October – December) with the possibility of extension through the spring 2020 semester. Interns will be responsible for providing staff members with policy and administrative support. Duties may include answering phones, compiling press clips, attending staff briefings, performing legislative and policy research, and other tasks.
This internship is open to undergraduates (juniors and above) and recent graduates. The office is an equal opportunity employer and minorities, women, and LGBTQ persons are encouraged to apply. Please note that this internship is unpaid.
If you would like to be considered, please submit a one-page resume and cover letter to housesmallbusinessinternshipr@gmail.com and include “Fall 2019 Internship Application” in the subject line of the email.
 MEM-545-19
The House Small Business Committee Minority Staff is currently looking for
MEM-544-19
The Office of Congressman Tom Malinowski (NJ-07) is currently seeking qualified candidates for their Spring 2020 internship program in the Washington D.C. office. This internship runs from January to May. Ideal candidates will be professional, motivated, dependable, a team player, and be able to show strong written and verbal communication skills.
Responsibilities include, but are not limited to, answering phones, assist with writing constituent correspondence, Capitol tours, attending Congressional
 Page 13 of 33

hearings and briefings, assisting legislative staff and producing press clips. Interns will work closely with legislative staff on interested issue areas and assist with the Congressman’s committee work.
Applicants must be able to commit to a full-time schedule (35-40 hours per week) and must be enrolled in a college or graduate program to be eligible for the position. Applicants with New Jersey ties, previous internship/ work experience, and receiving educational credit are strongly preferred. Start date is in early January.
Please e-mail a resume, cover letter, and writing sample (1 page only) in a single PDF document to nj07.interns@mail.house.gov with “(Last name) - Paid Spring Internship.”
No calls or drop ins. Deadline to submit applications is Nov. 5th.
     qualified candidates for an unpaid internship for Spring 2020 in the Washington D.C. office. This internship runs from January to May but considers the availability of the applicant. Ideal candidates will be professional, motivated, a team player, and be able to show strong written and verbal communication skills.
Responsibilities include, but are not limited to, answering phones, assist with writing constituent correspondence, Capitol tours, attending Congressional hearings and briefings, assisting legislative staff and producing press clips. Interns will work closely with legislative staff on interested issue areas and assist with the Congressman’s committee work.
Applicants should be able to commit to a part-time schedule (15-25 hours per week). Applicants with New Jersey ties and have previous internship/ work experience are a plus, but not required.
Interested applicants should e-mail a cover letter (1 page only), resume, writing sample and available dates in a single PDF document to nj07.interns@mail.house.gov with “(Last name) - Unpaid Spring Internship” in the subject line.
No calls or drop ins. Deadline to submit applications is Nov. 5th.
 MEM-543-19
The Office of Congressman Tom Malinowski (NJ-07) is currently seeking
MEM-542-19
The Office of Congressman Matt Cartwright (PA-08) is seeking candidates for a part-time or full-time paid internship able to start immediately in our Washington, D.C. office. Responsibilities will include drafting memos and constituent letters, assisting legislative staff with research, answering phones, managing the front office, giving Capitol tours, greeting constituents, and other tasks as assigned.
 Page 14 of 33

Send resume and cover letter only to Alexander.Heldring@mail.house.gov with “Fall Intern Application” in the subject line. Pennsylvania ties are strongly preferred. The office is an equal opportunity employer and encourages women, minorities, and LGBTQ candidates to apply.
  MEM-540-19
The Office of Congressman Harley Rouda (CA-48) is seeking a paid Press/Digital Intern in his DC office.
Qualified candidates will have strong writing, editing, and social media skills, as well as basic familiarity with graphic design/video editing software. California ties are a plus!
This position requires the ability to thrive under pressure, multi-task, and work in a team environment.
Responsibilities include:
•Drafting social posts
•Compiling daily press clips
•Assisting with speechwriting •Maintaining/updating website
•Designing graphics + editing photos/videos
Interested applicants should email a cover letter, resume, short writing sample/portfolio to ca48resumes@gmail.com with "Press/Digital Intern" in the subject line.
  MEM-538-19
Democratic Congressman seeks applicants for full or part-time congressional internship for Spring. Duties will include conducting legislative research, drafting memos, assisting with front office duties, and performing basic administrative tasks. Candidates must exhibit strong writing and communication skills.
California residents or strong ties to San Diego are preferred. Candidates should be prepared to work a minimum of 10 hours per week. Please send a resume, cover letter, writing sample (1-2 pages), and availability (start and end dates as well as days per week) to CA52Internship@mail.house.gov with “Last Name, First Name, CA52 Internship” in the subject line.
     temporary paid position in his Washington, D.C. office. The intern will assist with the greater communications operation, but will focus on digital media content creation.
Intern responsibilities include but are not limited to social media content generation, website maintenance, analytics, photography, videography, media monitoring and staffing the member. Candidates will have a keen eye for design,
MEM-537-19
Congressman Andy Levin (D-MI) is seeking a Digital Media Intern for a
Page 15 of 33

a desire to grow and learn in the political communications space, knowledge of graphic design and video editing, a positive attitude and a sense of humor. Candidates of all backgrounds are encouraged to apply.
To apply, please send a resume, cover letter, a writing sample, graphic design sample and a link to a video using the subject line “Digital Media Intern” to MI09.Resumes@gmail.com
  MEM-536-19
The House Foreign Affairs Committee Majority Staff is currently looking for a full-time legal intern for the Spring 2020 semester.
In addition to providing administrative and operations support to the committee as needed, the legal intern will work closely with the Counsels team with research projects, drafting legislation, providing support for full committee markups and hearings, and attending meetings and briefings. Candidates should be current law students and require little supervision. Minorities, women, and LGBTQ persons are strongly encouraged to apply.
If you would like to be considered for an internship please submit a one-page resume and cover letter in PDF format to hcfa.democrat@mail.house.gov and include “Spring 2020 Legal Internship Application” in the subject line of the email.
  MEM-535-19
The Office of Congresswoman Katherine M. Clark [MA-05] is currently seeking full-time & part-time paid interns for Spring 2020 in her Washington, D.C. office. Qualified applicants should have strong oral & written communication skills, the ability to manage multiple tasks, the willingness to work in a fast-paced environment, and be comfortable assisting constituents. A sound knowledge of Microsoft Office, a solid work ethic as well as a basic understanding of the political process in Congress is expected.
Responsibilities include but are not limited to: answering and screening phone calls, leading capitol tours, working with staff to research legislative issues and process information, attending congressional briefings, assisting with administrative tasks, drafting constituent correspondence on a variety of issues, assisting the communications team with various tasks, and other projects as they arise.
Full-time and part-time positions are available beginning in January 2020. To apply, please send a resume, cover letter, and a brief writing sample to RepClarkInternships@mail.house.gov. Please indicate availability and expected start date.
     join his Washington, DC office in early to mid-November. Candidates should be
MEM-534-19
Congressman John Garamendi (CA-03) is seeking a highly motivated intern to
Page 16 of 33

professional, quick learners, and phenomenal team players. Strong oral and written communication skills and close attention to detail are imperative.
Duties include assisting staff with legislative, administrative, and press related projects, writing memos and talking points, attending hearings and meetings, answering constituent phone calls, leading tours of the US Capitol, assisting with scheduling, sorting and distributing mail, and managing tour and flag requests.
Full-time candidates with California ties and previous internship/work experience are preferred. This is an paid internship. Please e-mail a resume, cover letter and dates of availability to Garamendi.Internships@mail.house.gov.
  MEM-530-19
Marisol del Carmen Rodriguez was a faithful and tireless advocate of civic engagement. Marisol herself was afforded a public service internship that led to a lifelong commitment to the ideals of enriching and empowering all people in her community. Through this fellowship, Marisol will continue her legacy of service, education and a selfless dedication to the betterment of her community.
The Marisol del Carmen Rodriguez Congressional Fellowship is a fully funded fellowship program in Congresswoman Sylvia R. Garcia’s Washington, DC office. It is a competitive program awarded to outstanding students with a demonstrated interest in public service or public policy and strong ties to the 29th Congressional District of Texas.
The fellow will gain hands-on office experience while learning about the legislative process. They will work closely with staff conducting research, drafting letters, and preparing for hearings. Other responsibilities will include leading Capitol tours, answering and screening telephone calls, managing the front office, tracking media coverage, and other duties as necessary.
Qualified applicants have strong writing and communication skills, the ability to manage multiple tasks, a strong sense of professionalism and demonstrate a solid work ethic. English and Spanish bilingual candidates are strongly encouraged to apply.
The position is available beginning in January 2020. To apply, send a resume and cover letter to ellie.valega@mail.house.gov with the subject “Marisol Rodriguez Congressional Fellowship”. In your cover letter please indicate expected start and end dates, hours available to work, and if course credit is available for this internship.
This office is an equal opportunity employer: Women and minorities are strongly encouraged to apply. This office does not discriminate on the basis of race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity and expression, national origin, disability military status, age, marital status, or parental status.
  Page 17 of 33

MEM-529-19
“The Republican Office of the Committee on Science, Space, and Technology seeks energetic and self-motivated undergraduate or graduate-level students, as well as recent graduates, with an interest in government and public policy for a Spring 2020 internship. Working closely with Committee staff, interns will have the opportunity to gain first-hand knowledge of the inner-workings of a congressional committee and learn about the day-to-day administrative operations of the House of Representatives.
Interns are responsible for assisting Committee staff with official proceedings (hearings/markups), oversight, research, assisting with phone inquiries and providing support to all Committee staff. Background in science is a plus. To apply, please send your resume and cover letter to house.science.committee@mail.house.gov.”
  MEM-528-19
Southern Democratic Member of Congress seeks both full-time and part-time interns for their Spring 2020 paid internship in the Washington, D.C. office. Responsibilities include answering phones, researching legislation for the Member and legislative staff, attending hearings and briefings, running errands, drafting constituent correspondence, and other tasks as assigned.
Applicants should have excellent written and verbal communication skills, and work well under pressure in a fast-paced environment. No drop-ins or phone calls.
Please email nchousejobs@gmail.com with the subject line “Spring 2020 - Internship Application” and attach a resume, writing sample, and include information regarding your full-time or part-time availability.
The office is an equal opportunity employer, and diverse candidates are encouraged to apply.
     2020 interns for our Washington, D.C. office. Responsibilities will include drafting memos and constituent letters, assisting legislative staff with research, answering phones, managing the front office, giving Capitol tours, greeting constituents, and other tasks as assigned.
Preferred candidates are current college students or recent graduates who work well under deadlines, pay close attention to detail, have a strong work ethic, have excellent customer service skills, and work well on a team. Nevada ties are strongly preferred, but not required. Women, LGBTQ+, and minority candidates are encouraged to apply. All applicants will be considered without regard to race, color, national origin, religion, sex, gender identity, disability, or age.
Interested candidates should send a resume and cover letter to NV03Resumes@gmail.com with “Spring Intern” in the subject line by COB
 MEM-527-19
The Office of Congresswoman Susie Lee is seeking full-time, unpaid Spring
Page 18 of 33

Friday, November 15, 2019. Please indicate expected start and end dates in your cover letter. No phone calls or walk-ins please.
 MEM-526-19
The Office of Congressman Anthony Brindisi (NY-22) is seeking candidates for a full-time paid internship for the Spring 2020 Semester in our Washington, D.C. office.
Responsibilities include but are not limited to answering phones, conducting legislative research and analysis, attending briefings/hearings, leading Capitol tours, and managing the front office.
New York ties are preferred but not required. To apply, please send a resume, cover letter, and a writing sample to Kevin.Porter@mail.house.gov with the subject line “Spring Internship Application”.
  MEM-525-19
Congressman Alcee L. Hastings (FL-20) is seeking enthusiastic and highly motivated applicants for a full or part-time unpaid internship starting January 2020.
Candidates should possess a strong interest in the legislative process. Strong oral and written skills and close attention to details are imperative. Interns are considered an integral part of the team and will have the opportunity to gain experience working on Capitol Hill and learn firsthand about the workings of a Congressional office.
Responsibilities will include conducting legislative research, drafting memos and responses to letters from constituents, assisting constituents and visitors to the office, and attending briefings and hearings. Congressman Hastings supports students requesting credit for their internship through their school or university.
Please e-mail a resume, cover letter, writing sample and dates of availability to internship.alhastings@mail.house.gov with “Internship" in the subject line. No phone calls or walk-ins will be accepted.
     for internships in the Congressman’s D.C. office for the spring of 2020. Duties include drafting constituent correspondence, greeting constituents and answering phones, performing legislative research, leading tours of the Capitol, attending policy briefings and meetings, and conducting research and additional tasks to assist the Congressman’s staff.
We’re looking for college students or recent graduates who are motivated, detail- orientated, and ready to work in a fast-paced setting. A positive attitude and an interest in politics are a must. District 8 or Indiana ties are preferred but not required. To apply for the position, please follow the directions outlined on the
MEM-524-19
The office of Congressman Larry Bucshon (IN-08) is currently seeking applicants
Page 19 of 33

Congressman’s website here: https://bucshon.house.gov/constituent- services/internships.htm
     MEM-523-19
The Washington D.C. office of Congressman Ken Buck (CO-04) is currently accepting internship applications for the Spring of 2020. Typical duties will include answering phones, leading Capitol tours, researching legislation for the Member and legislative staff, attending hearings and briefings, and answering constituent letters on a variety of issues. The ideal candidate for this paid internship will be team-oriented and have strong written and verbal communication skills.
Students and recent graduates interested in learning more about our country’s legislative process are encouraged to apply. The Congressman sits on both the Judiciary Committee and the Foreign Affairs Committee, making this an ideal opportunity for those interested in law and/or foreign policy. Colorado ties are preferred but not required.
All interested applicants should e-mail their resume and a brief writing sample to Zach Mendelovici at Zach.Mendelovici@mail.house.gov with the subject line “Spring 2020 Internship.”
  MEM-522-19
The Majority Staff of the Select Committee on the Climate Crisis seeks full or part-time Legal Interns for an early to mid-January start date, running through April 2020. Responsibilities may include conducting legislative research, producing legal analyses on proposed climate and environmental policies, attending briefings and hearings for staff, and other tasks as assigned or needed.
The ideal candidate will be detail-oriented, self-motivated, reliable, and have excellent writing and communications skills. An interest in environmental law is strongly desired; this internship is geared towards those in 2L or 3L programs in Washington, DC.
Please send a resume and cover letter to SCCCDjobs@mail.house.gov with “Winter/Spring Legal Intern” in the subject line by November 15, 2019. Please include your approximate dates of availability in the message, and how many days per week you would be available. The office is an equal opportunity employer, and diverse candidates are encouraged to apply. No calls or drop-ins please.
  MEM-521-19
The Majority Staff of the Select Committee on the Climate Crisis seeks full or part-time Interns for an early to mid-January start date, running through April 2020. Responsibilities may include conducting administrative tasks for the committee, attending briefings and hearings for staff, conducting research projects, preparing and assembling materials for Committee hearings and events, and other tasks as assigned or needed.
 Page 20 of 33

The ideal candidate will be detail-oriented, self-motivated, reliable, and have excellent writing and communications skills. An interest in environmental, climate change, or science policy is strongly desired and preferred.
Please send a resume and cover letter to SCCCDjobs@mail.house.gov with “Winter/Spring Intern” in the subject line by November 15, 2019. Please include your approximate dates of availability in the message, and how many days per week you would be available.
The office is an equal opportunity employer, and diverse candidates are encouraged to apply. No calls or drop-ins please.
  MEM-520-19
The Office of Congressman Doug Collins (GA-09) is looking for candidates for an internship in his Washington, D.C. office. We are looking for highly qualified candidates that are motivated, detail-oriented, personable, and have a passion for public service. The ideal candidates will have excellent research and writing abilities, be able to multi-task and interact well with constituents visiting the office and on the phone.
Interns will have the opportunity to experience working on Capitol Hill, learn about the legislative process, and attend briefings of interest. Responsibilities include answering the phone, researching and preparing policy memos, giving tours of the Capitol, assisting with constituent correspondence, supporting the communications staff among many other projects.
Qualifications:
•Current student or recent graduate interested in politics and gaining legislative experience
•Exhibits passion for politics, government, and/or any related policy areas
• Excellent verbal and written communication and interpersonal skills
•Ability to multitask independently, learn quickly, and demonstrate sound judgment
•Exhibits great attention to detail, punctuality, respect, and initiative
•Ability to work and contribute in a highly collaborative, team environment Benefits:
•Working closely with the representative and Chief of Staff
•Observation of internal campaign operations and preparation for campaign and political jobs
•Opportunity to bolster organizational and communication skills
•Attend special events, political meetings, and congressional hearings
•Meals and snacks will regularly be provided at events and activities
Interested candidates should email a resume and cover letter to Raymond Sweney, at raymond.sweney@mail.house.gov
  Page 21 of 33

MEM-518-19
The Office of Congressman Mark Pocan (D-WI) is seeking full and part-time Interns for the Washington, D.C. office starting at the end of December or early January. Interns in our office perform legislative and administrative work while gaining valuable career and educational experience. Specific duties include drafting constituent correspondence, attending policy briefings and committee hearings, performing legislative research, producing daily press clips, and supporting staff members on various projects of interest.
Qualified candidates are organized and detail-oriented, responsible, willing to learn, able to work cooperatively, possess strong oral and written communication skills, and are committed to public service. Wisconsin ties and sense of humor are a plus! Candidates of all backgrounds are encouraged to apply.
To apply, please submit a form on our website at:
https://pocan.house.gov/services/internships/congressional-internship-application
or send a resume, cover letter, and a brief writing sample to Sydney.Scott@mail.house.gov with “Winter 2020 Pocan Internship” in the subject line.
For further information regarding the internship program, please see the internship page on our website at: https://pocan.house.gov/services/internships/. We also highly encourage every applicant to apply to our scholarship program after submitting an application. The application can be found here: https://pocan.house.gov/scholarship-program.
     MEM-517-19
“San Antonio-native and fighting Texas Aggie, Congressman Will Hurd serves as the United States Representative for one of the largest non-state districts in the nation. Texas-23 stretches from San Antonio to El Paso and encompasses 820 miles of border. Prior to Congress, Hurd served for nearly a decade as an undercover CIA officer and helped start a cybersecurity company. The third-term Congressman is known for his bipartisan work on national security, border security, and cybersecurity.
An internship in the Washington, DC office encompasses a variety of tasks and assignments such as answering phones, greeting visitors, giving Capitol tours, writing letters, and assisting with media clips. In addition, interns may be assigned to work with the legislative team and outreach staff to assist with legislation, special projects, writing, and/or research.
The ideal intern should be responsible, focused, enthusiastic, able to work cooperatively with Congressional staff, and possess excellent oral and written communications skills. Schedule is flexible and stipends may be available. Texas ties preferred. Spanish speaking skills preferred, but not required.
 Page 22 of 33

To apply for an internship, please email your resume and a brief cover letter to Reilly.Knecht@mail.house.gov with “2019 Spring Internship” in the subject line. In your email, please specify your dates of availability. “
      internship program. Applicants should be dependable, team-oriented, and have a strong desire to work for the residents of Connecticut’s 4th District. This position is an exciting opportunity to gain first-hand knowledge of how the legislative process works. Congressional interns are expected to draft constituent correspondence, attend briefings and Congressional hearings, prepare memoranda and daily press clips, and lead Congressional tours.
Please apply by submitting your application materials through the internship page on himes.house.gov. Please be sure to put Fall 2019 in the subject line when applying. A need-based stipend may be available, and the schedule is flexible.
 MEM-515-19
Congressman Jim Himes (CT-04) has an immediate opening for our Fall 2019
   Washington, D.C. office. Responsibilities will include answering phones, managing the front office, giving Capitol tours, greeting constituents, assisting legislative staff with research, and other tasks as assigned.
Preferred candidates are current college students or recent graduates who work well under deadlines, pay close attention to detail, have a strong work ethic, have excellent customer service skills, and work well on a team. Nevada ties are preferred, but not required. Women, LGBTQ+, and minority candidates are encouraged to apply. All applicants will be considered without regard to race, color, national origin, religion, sex, gender identity, disability, or age.
Interested candidates should send a resume and cover letter to NV03Resumes@gmail.com with “Fall Intern” in the subject line. No phone calls or walk-ins please.
 MEM-510-19
The Office of Congresswoman Susie Lee is seeking Fall 2019 interns for our
MEM-509-19
The Republican Staff of the Committee on Oversight and Reform, the chief investigative body of the House of Representatives, is seeking full- and part-time interns for the remainder of the fall semester. Interns will have the opportunity to work with the administrative, policy, and press teams, conducting research, assisting during hearings and markups, and helping with other administrative tasks as necessary.
This position is available immediately and would go through December, with the potential for extending into the spring semester. Specific dates for this internship will be determined on a case-by-case basis, and preference will be afforded to those who are available at least 15 hours a week.
Applicants must be strong writers, organized, and detail-oriented, as they will balance multiple, often disparate, projects corresponding with the broad
 Page 23 of 33

jurisdiction of the Committee. The strongest candidates will also exhibit discretion in working on confidential matters and be enthusiastic and knowledgeable about the Committee’s work. Previous experience on Capitol Hill is desired, but not required. The position is unpaid, but we are happy to work with an applicant so they can receive class credit.
Interested individuals should submit a cover letter and resume to oversight.committee@mail.house.gov. Please place "INTERN" in the subject line. Applications will be reviewed on a rolling basis.
  MEM-508-19
The Republican Staff of the Committee on Oversight and Reform, the chief investigative body of the House of Representatives, is seeking full- and part-time law clerks for the remainder of the fall semester. Law Clerks will have the opportunity to work with the oversight and policy teams, conducting researching, reviewing documents, and preparing for hearings and markups. Law clerks will balance multiple, often disparate, projects corresponding with the broad jurisdiction of the Committee.
This position is available immediately and would go through December, with the potential for extending into the spring semester. Specific dates for this internship will be determined on a case-by-case basis, and preference will be afforded to those who are available at least 15 hours a week.
Applicants must be current law school students or recent graduates of law school who are organized and detail-oriented. Strong writing and blue booking skills are also necessary. The strongest candidates will also exhibit discretion in working on confidential matters and be enthusiastic and knowledgeable about the Committee’s work. This position is unpaid, but we are happy to work with an applicant so they can receive class credit.
Interested individuals should submit a cover letter and resume to oversight.committee@mail.house.gov. Please place "LAW CLERK" in the subject line. Applications will be reviewed on a rolling basis.
     part-time legislative and press interns for spring 2020. Responsibilities include but are not limited to conducting legislative research, answering phones, attending briefings and hearings for staff, compiling press clips, drafting content, and other tasks depending on the needs of the Committee and the intern’s interests.
Qualified candidates will have strong oral and written communications skills as well as a desire to help veterans and learn about the House and legislative process.
MEM-507-19
The Democratic Staff of the House Committee on Veterans’ Affairs seeks full or
Page 24 of 33

Apply by submitting an application at https://veterans.house.gov/contact/internship and sending a resume and cover letter to veterans.internships@mail.house.gov. Applications are considered on a rolling basis. Student veterans preferred, but not required.
This internship is unpaid, students receiving outside funding or school sponsorship are preferred.
   MEM-505-19
The Office of Congressman Greg Murphy (NC-03) is currently seeking paid interns with our DC office for the Spring 2020 session. The internship would begin in January and last until early May. Our specific dates are tentative on the release of the official House schedule.
This is a great opportunity to gain hands-on experience and knowledge over the day-to-day happenings within Congress. The internship is an ideal fit for any student that is interested in politics, law or government – however, any interested student is encouraged to apply! Interns will assist the legislative staff by conducting policy research, answering phones, leading tours, and helping with administrative tasks.
Qualified candidates should:
• Be a current undergraduate or graduate student, or have recently graduated
• Demonstrate an interest in politics, policy and/or public service
• Have strong communications and writing skills.
• Be hard-working, dependable, detail-oriented and professional.
The deadline to apply for the Spring Session is Friday, November 15th. Interested candidates should address their application materials to Collin Sabine at Interns.NC03@gmail.com. Applications should include a cover letter, resume, and what the individual’s internship schedule may look like.
  MEM-504-19
The Office of Congressman Denny Heck (D-WA) is seeking applicants for paid full-time or part-time Fall 2019 internships in Washington, D.C. Responsibilities include answering phone calls, greeting visitors, leading tours of the Capitol, drafting letters to constituents, attending briefings and hearings, and helping conduct research for various projects.
Ideal candidates will have a meticulous attention to detail, strong writing skills, an ability to work in a fast-paced environment, and an enthusiasm for the political process and congressional operations. Pacific Northwest ties preferred but not required.
Interested applicants should send a resume, cover letter, and two references to noelle.gasper@mail.house.gov with “Fall 2019 Internship” in the subject line.
    Page 25 of 33

MEM-503-19
Congressman Charlie Crist (FL-13) is seeking Full time or Part Time interns for Spring 2020 in Washington, D.C. Interns will assist the legislative and administrative staff, attending briefings, answering phones, coordinating and conducting tours, drafting constituent correspondence letters, performing legislative research and analysis, and various other tasks. District and Florida ties are encouraged but not required. No phone calls or drop ins, please.
To apply, email a single PDF including your resume, 1-2 page writing sample, and cover letter listing your availability to FL13.Internships@mail.house.gov.
  MEM-502-19
The Office of Rep. Ro Khanna (D-CA) seeks Press/Legislative interns for the upcoming winter/spring 2020 term.
Press responsibilities will include building press lists, drafting social media posts for the Member’s official social media pages (including Facebook, Twitter, and Instagram), designing graphics, and creating short video clips as needed. The intern will be an integral part of the communications team, generating engaging content for the Member and supplying creative ideas throughout the week. Ideal applicants will have a background in iMovie, the Adobe creative suite, and TweetDeck.
Legislative responsibilities include researching legislation for both the Member and legislative staff, attending hearings and briefings, and drafting constituent letters on the Member’s behalf.
This is a unique opportunity to gain both legislative and communications experience in a fast-paced and high-volume congressional office.
All interns are paid $15.00 per hour for a maximum of 30 hours a week, and are expected to work collaboratively with the staff to answer phones, greet constituents, and guide tours of the U.S. Capitol Building. The Office of Rep. Ro Khanna is an equal opportunity employer. We do not discriminate based on race, ethnicity, gender, sexual orientation, religion, national origin, age, or socio- economic status. All are welcome and encouraged to apply.
Applicants should send a resume, a short writing sample (no more than 2-pages), sample tweets on a current event, a sample graphic (optional) and availability to julia.albertson@mail.house.gov.
  MEM-501-19
Congressman Dwight Evans (PA-03) is seeking highly motivated interns for the Winter/Spring of 2020. Strong communication skills required. Must be dependable and a team player.
Duties include answering constituent phone calls and inquiries, attending congressional briefings and hearings, conducting research for legislative staff, compiling press clips for the communications team, and leading Capitol tours.
 Page 26 of 33

Interns will gain valuable professional experience and inside knowledge of the legislative process on Capitol Hill.
Minorities, women, and LGBTQ persons are encouraged to apply. Philadelphia or Pennsylvania ties preferred but not required. Qualified candidates should send a resume and cover letter to Matthew.Holcombe@mail.house.gov with the subject line “Spring 2020 Internship.”
  MEM-500-19
The Office of Congresswoman Gwen Moore (WI-04) is seeking a press intern to assist with a fast-paced communications operation for Spring 2020 (starting at the beginning of January 2020). This is a paid position. Qualified candidates will have strong writing, editing, event planning, social media, graphic design, and photography skills, and be able to work on tight deadlines. Selected candidates will also be expected to perform standard administrative duties.
Intern responsibilities include:
* Social media content development * Event photography
* Compiling press clips
* Clipping videos
* Creating graphics
* Drafting press releases
* Answering phones
Interested applicants should email a cover letter, resume, short writing sample, and dates of availability to GwenMoorePress.Moore@mail.house.gov with “Spring 2020 Press Internship” in the subject line. We also recommend, but do not require, applicants submit 1-3 sample graphics.
  MEM-499-19
The office of Congresswoman Rosa L. DeLauro is accepting applications for the Spring 2020 internship program in the Washington, DC office. Applicants should have an ability to work in a fast-paced environment, possess excellent writing skills, and an enthusiastic attitude.
Intern responsibilities include supporting legislative and press staff, attending hearings and briefings, answering constituent phone calls, leading US Capitol tours, organizing constituent mail, greeting office visitors, and various ad hoc projects. For application information, please visit https://delauro.house.gov/services/internships. Please email your completed application to Harper.White@mail.house.gov
Applicants and employees shall not be discriminated against with respect to compensation, terms, conditions, or privileges of employment, because of such person’s race, color, religion, sex, age, national origin, service in the military, disability or sexual orientation.
   Page 27 of 33

MEM-497-19
Congressman Bill Johnson’s office (OH-06) is currently seeking internship applicants in the D.C. office for Spring of 2020. Qualified applicants should possess strong communication skills, be interested in learning about the legislative process, and have a willingness to work in our fast-paced office.
Responsibilities would include answering phones, leading tours of the Capitol, attending policy briefings and meetings, and conducting research and additional tasks to assist the Congressman’s staff. Ohio ties are preferred but not required.
Interested applicants should send resume, cover letter and availability to intern.OH06@gmail.com.
  MEM-496-19
“A Midwest Republican House Member is seeking paid interns for the Fall 2019/Spring 2020 session in his Capitol Hill office. The Spring session dates are January 13th-May 15th, but more flexibility can be offered. The internship schedule is also flexible to accommodate classes. Interns will have the opportunity to attend committee hearings and briefings for staff members, assist in the constituent correspondence process, as well as assist with other constituent services.
Responsibilities include: taking phone calls, processing constituent mail, and performing other general office duties. Ideal applicants should be interested in the legislative process, enthusiastic, reliable, and hard-working. Full or part time internships with flexible schedules are available. Ties to the Midwest are preferred but not required.
Interested candidates should e-mail their resume and cover letter to Dylan.Jones@mail.house.gov. Please specify what your internship schedule may look like, including preferred start/end dates.”
  MEM-494-19
Congressman Jodey Arrington (TX-19) is seeking highly motivated interns to join his Washington D.C. team in January for a 4-5 month paid internship. Candidates should be motivated, professional, quick learners, and phenomenal team players. Strong oral and written communication skills and close attention to detail are important.
Duties include assisting staff with legislative, administrative, and press related projects, writing memos and talking points, attending hearings and meetings, answering constituent phone calls, leading tours of the US Capitol, and sorting and distributing mail.
Full-time candidates with Texas ties and previous internship/work experience are preferred. Please e-mail a resume, cover letter and dates of availability to marisa.burleson@mail.house.gov
  MEM-493-19 Republican Florida Office Searching for Paid Spring Interns.
 Page 28 of 33

Florida ties preferred but not required. Full and Part Time Internships available.
TITLE: Intern
REPORTS TO: Intern Coordinator/Supervisor
CORE RESPONSIBILITIES:
•to assist in performing research, processing the mail, data entry, reception duties and other office errands.
QUALIFICATIONS:
•good oral and written communication skills;
•ability to work cooperatively and courteously with others; •good organizational skills; and
•responsible, dependable and willing to learn.
DUTIES:
•performs research (CRS, the Library of Congress, MIN, or other available resources);
•sorts and distributes mail;
•attends committee meetings, intern conferences, and seminars;
•performs data entry, which involves logging in letters and constituent requests, including names and addresses of constituents;
•answers the telephones;
•notes constituent opinions, including their full names, addresses, and all relevant information;
•greets visitors and signs for deliveries; and
performs other duties as assigned by the Intern Supervisor
Please submit applications to Carl.Schuler@mail.house.gov please include a resume and writing sample.
  MEM-492-19
The Democratic Staff of the Committee on Science, Space and Technology seeks full-time, paid interns for the Spring semester. Interns are asked to work with staff to help prepare for committee hearings and markups and will work on substantive research and oversight projects in addition to press matters. Furthermore, interns will be critical to the daily operation of the office including tasks such as answering phones, greeting visitors, and filing official documents.
Interested applicants should visit the Committee’s website at https://science.house.gov/contact/internships. Please fill out the provided application and attach a resume. No calls or drop-ins please.
  MEM-491-19 The Office of Congresswoman Gwen Moore (WI-04) is seeking a highly motivated full-time intern for Spring 2020 (starting at the beginning of January 2020). This is a paid internship. Qualified candidates will be dependable team players, capable of excelling in a fast-paced office, and will possess strong writing, editing, verbal communication, and organizational skills. Experience
 Page 29 of 33

with research is a plus since there are opportunities to work with the legislative staff on relevant issues.
This position’s responsibilities include serving as a primary contact with constituents, greeting visitors, providing Capitol Tours, and assisting with projects assigned from other staff members. These projects often include assisting with data entry or drafting correspondence.
Interns will have the ability to attend Capitol Hill briefings, hearings, and other informative events that are available. Interns will also have the opportunity to gain professional and educational experience while learning more about Congress and the legislative process. Wisconsin ties are a plus.
Interested applicants should email a cover letter, resume, short writing sample, and dates of availability to maryah.thompson@mail.house.gov with “Spring 2020 Internship” in the subject line.
  MEM-490-19
Congressman Jason Smith (MO-08) is currently seeking full or part-time interns to work in his Washington, DC office for the Spring 2020 term from January to May.
Primary intern responsibilities include answering phones, interacting with residents of the district in person or over the phone, sorting mail, leading Capitol building tours, reviewing legislative correspondence, and assisting staff with administrative and research tasks. Interns will also have opportunities to conduct legislative research and attend staff briefings, Congressional hearings, and press events.
The ideal candidate has a positive attitude, disciplined work ethic, strong attention to detail, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Ties to Missouri are preferred but not required. Please note state ties in your cover letter or email.
Those interested should send a resume and cover letter to Zach.Wong@mail.house.gov with “Spring Internship” in the subject line. Applications are reviewed on a rolling basis until all spots are filled. Internship time frame and hours are flexible and can be adjusted to accommodate class/work schedules.
  MEM-489-19 The office of Congressman Ralph Norman (SC-05) is currently seeking applications for the current fall and winter semester at our Washington, D.C. office. Interns' responsibilities will vary.
Applicants must be motivated, professional, dependable and hold strong written and verbal communication skills.
 Page 30 of 33

 Responsibilities include, but are not limited to, answering phones, corresponding with constituents, leading U.S. Capitol tours, attending Congressional hearings, assisting the legislative staff, and participating in a legislative project. Successful candidates will be mature, personable, detail-oriented, and self-starters.
The hours may be flexible to accommodate students' course schedules, but generally run 8:30 a.m. to 5:30 p.m. when Congress is in session, and 9:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m. when not in session. Internships are available for 6 weeks, 8 weeks, and semester length.
To apply, please send a resume, cover letter, and available start date to Kimberly Hammond at Kimberly.hammond@mail.house.gov
 MEM-488-19
The Committee on Education and Labor, Majority is currently seeking undergraduate and graduate interns and fellows for spring of 2020. Specifically we are seeking general undergraduate interns, graduate and legal interns and fellows for the labor policy team, graduate and legal interns and fellows for the health policy team and graduate and legal interns and fellows for the oversight team. Interns perform a variety of tasks that support the staff in our legislative and media work.
Legislative tasks may include, but are not limited to: legislative research and fact checking; technical writing including legislation, memos, and speeches; assisting staff in hearing and markup preparation and execution; and attending other hearings, markups, briefings and meetings for the purpose of informing staff and Members as they work to craft legislation and policy proposals. Media tasks may include helping to organize and staff Committee press conferences and assisting with the production of daily news clips.
Applicants who are applying for graduate internships or fellowships should be able to demonstrate academic or professional exposure to the subject matter of the team to which they are applying. Fellows must be participating in an established fellowship program. Applicants should be able to start in January and commit through April/May.
Interested applicants should email their cover letter, resume and internship applicant information form to E&L_Interns&Fellows@mail.house.gov and indicate, in the subject line of the email, to which position they are applying.
Please also include ‘Spring 2020’ in the subject line. If you are applying for a graduate internship or fellowship, please include two short, relevant writing samples in your application materials. Please visit our website at https://edlabor.house.gov/about/internships for more information. Applicants should aim to submit their materials by November 1, 2019.
  Page 31 of 33

MEM-485-19
The Committee on Education and Labor is a legislative office within the U.S. House of Representatives. The Committee has jurisdiction over a broad array of child welfare, education and labor policy areas, including early childhood education, K-12 education, higher education, employer/employee relations, worker safety, and employer provided health care. Representative Robert C. “Bobby” Scott (D-VA) serves as Chairman.
 MEM-486-19
The Office of Congresswoman Brenda L. Lawrence (MI-14) seeks motivated,
   detail-oriented, and energetic professionals for internships in Washington, DC. Qualified applicants should have strong interpersonal skills, the ability to manage multiple tasks, possess strong writing skills, and demonstrate a solid work ethic.
Responsibilities include but are not limited to:
Answering and screening telephone calls, managing the front office, greeting constituents and visitors, leading Capitol tours, assisting legislative staff with research, attending congressional briefings, participating in hearing preparation, drafting constituent correspondence on a variety of issues, assisting the Communications Director with drafting talking points, creating graphics for social media, tracking media coverage, and other duties as necessary.
Full-time and part-time internship positions are available beginning in January 2020.
To apply, please send a resume, cover letter, and brief writing sample to Ryan.Casman@mail.house.gov with the phrase “Internship Application” in the subject line. Please indicate expected start and end dates as well as hours available to work in your cover letter.
 Congresswoman Lauren Underwood (IL-14) is delighted to announce spring
   internship opportunities in her Washington, DC and West Chicago, IL offices. Internships are designed to offer students and recent graduates direct participation in public service through supporting our offices' constituent engagement and services, administrative responsibilities, and research.
Interns' responsibilities will vary. They will be asked to answer phones, assist with correspondence, coordinate and conduct tours, research legislation, assist with constituent casework, and attend hearings and briefings on various issues. Qualified candidates must be friendly, organized, flexible, and possess the ability to multitask in a fast-paced environment.
Spring internships are available from January through mid-May, with start and end dates tailored to accommodate an academic calendar year. Internship hours run from 9:00 a.m. to 6:00 p.m. on weekdays. Please note that interns are expected to work a minimum of 20 hours per week. A limited number of paid positions are available for internship applicants who are not sponsored by outside organizations.
Page 32 of 33

 MEM-446-19
MEM-416-19
The deadline to apply, for the spring semester is October 31, 2019. Preference will be given to applicants with ties to the Illinois 14th.
To learn more and apply, please click here. (https://underwood.house.gov/services/internships/internship-form)
For questions about internships please call our office (202) 225-2976.
 The Office of the Representative Linda Sánchez is currently accepting
   applications for a full-time Spring internship. Ideal candidates will possess excellent communication skills, a strong attention to detail, the ability to work in a fast-paced environment, and a good sense of humor.
Primary responsibilities will include processing mail, greeting visitors, answering phones, leading Capitol tours, attending briefings, drafting memos and constituent correspondence, and assisting staff with various administrative tasks. Southern California ties are preferred, but not required.
Interested applicants should send a resume, cover letter, a one-page writing sample, and dates of availability in a single PDF to DCInternship.CA38@mail.house.gov with “CA-38 Spring Internship” in the subject line. The application deadline is Friday, November 8th.
 The Democratic Staff on the House Education and Labor Committee seeks a
   health care intern/fellow. This position will work on the health team. Candidates should have familiarity with health policy, including the Affordable Care Act. Knowledge of other statutes and policies within the Committee’s jurisdiction and how they impact health and human services policy is preferred. Prior Hill experience or policy experience is also preferred.
Tasks will include supporting the development of legislation regarding health policy, conducting issue and legislative research, and preparing written materials and legislative analyses. Applicants should be available to start in September 2019 and commit through December 2019.
To apply, applicants must submit the internship applicant information form (https://edlabor.house.gov/about/internships/form), a resume and a short writing sample. The office is an equal opportunity employer and encourages candidates of diverse backgrounds to apply.
Please email resume and writing sample to E&L_Interns&Fellows@mail.house.gov with "Health Policy Intern/Fellow" in the subject line.
      Page 33 of 33
