 ________________________________________________________________________
House Vacancy Announcement and Placement Service (HVAPS)
B-235 Longworth House Office Building Washington, D.C. 20515 202-226-5836
Vacancy Bulletins are available for pick-up in
Longworth HOB - B-227 (CAO First Call Customer Service Center) or in the CAO Human Resources Office - Ford HOB 102
To Subscribe or Unsubscribe to the Vacancy Listserv visit:
http://www.house.gov/content/jobs/
Job Line: 202-226-4504 _____________________________________________________________________________
 MEM-338-14
INTERNSHIP VACANCY LISTING
Week of October 20, 2014
The Office of Representative Kevin Brady (TX-08) is currently seeking a paid full-time intern (part-time also possible- but may not be paid) for our Washington, D.C. office. Qualified candidates are well organized, with good oral and written communication skills, and possess a strong interest in learning about the political process and congressional affairs. Duties include but are not limited to, answering phones, compiling briefing binders, batching mail, performing legislative research, and attending briefings. Interns interact heavily with constituents so a positive attitude is a must. Applicants must be detail oriented with a strong work ethic and an eagerness to represent the 8th district of Texas. Previous Hill experience not required. Interested Candidates should send a resume and cover letter to: TX08intern@gmail.com.
Congressman Blaine Luetkemeyer (MO-3) is currently seeking interns in his Washington, D.C. office for Spring 2015 (January-May). Interns perform a variety of responsibilities, including answering phones, receiving guests, and providing tours of the Capitol Building. They will
 MEM-337-14
Page 1 of 11

 MEM-336-14
also research legislation for the legislative staff, attend hearings and briefings, and answer constituent letters on various issues before the House. Interns should possess strong research, writing, analytical, and interpersonal skills. Moreover, candidates should express an interest in politics and conservative values. All internships are unpaid. However, if your college or university offers credit hours we are happy to complete any necessary evaluations. Interested candidates should contact Claire Trokey and email their resume and cover letter to: claire.trokey@mail.house.gov.
The Democratic office of the Committee on House Administration seeks energetic and self-motivated undergraduate or graduate level students as well as recent graduates with an interest in government and public policy to apply for its Fall 2014 internship. Working closely with Committee staff, interns will have the opportunity to gain first- hand knowledge of the inner-workings of a congressional committee and learn about the day-to-day administrative operations of the House of Representatives. Interns are responsible for assisting Committee staff with official proceedings (hearings/markups), elections oversight, member services, and other projects as well as providing general front office support. Please note that this is not a paid internship. Interested applicants should send a cover letter, resume, and available hours to CHADem.Intern@mail.house.gov with the subject headline, “CHA Dem Internship.”
Moderate Democratic Congressman seeks applicants for full or part- time unpaid congressional internship for Fall 2014. Duties will include conducting legislative research, drafting memos, assisting with front office duties, and performing basic administrative tasks. Candidates must exhibit strong writing and communication skills. San Diego residents or strong ties to California are preferred. Please send a resume, cover letter and writing sample to CA52.internships@gmail.com with “Fall Congressional Internship” in the subject line.
Conservative Fall & Spring Internship. The office of Representative Stephen Fincher (TN-08) is looking for motivated interns for the 2014 Fall and 2015 Spring semesters in the Washington, D.C. office. Intern responsibilities include assisting the staff with general office duties, attending briefings and hearings, answering phones, sorting mail, giving Capitol tours, and performing various other tasks based on ability and interests. Applicants must possess strong communication skills, have a positive attitude and be well-organized. Internship may be full-time or part-time to fit applicant's schedule. Interested candidates should send a cover letter and résumé to TN08.Intern@mail.house.gov. Tennessee ties preferred, but not required.
 MEM-335-14
 MEM-334-14
 Page 2 of 11

MEM-333-14
Congressman John Garamendi (CA-03) is seeking a highly motivated intern to join his Washington, DC office from November through February. Candidates should be collegial, professional, quick learners, and phenomenal team players. Strong oral and written communication skills and close attention to detail are imperative. Duties include assisting staff with legislative, administrative, and press related projects, writing memos and talking points, attending hearings and meetings, answering constituent phone calls, leading tours of the US Capitol, assisting with scheduling, sorting and distributing mail, and managing tour and flag requests. Full-time candidates with California ties and previous internship/work experience are strongly encouraged to apply. This is an unpaid internship. Please e-mail a resume, cover letter and dates of availability to Garamendi.Internships@mail.house.gov.
The DC office of Congressman Derek Kilmer, hailing from Washington’s 6th district, is looking for personable, diligent full-time or part-time interns to start for the late fall session (beginning in late October, flexible end-date). This is an opportunity to learn about the inner-workings of a congressional office on the Hill in a fast-paced work environment. The internship allows access to briefings and interesting events related to a wide range of important issues. Responsibilities include assisting with constituent correspondence, producing daily press clips, and leading tours of the Capitol. This is a unique opportunity and prime for students or recent grads who are interested in learning about the legislative process or may eventually want to work for the federal government.
To apply, please send a resume, contact information for two references, and a cover letter outlining your interest in the position to nwcongressionalinternship@gmail.com and expect a response within a week. Those with Washington state ties strongly encouraged to apply. We look forward to hearing from you!
The office of Congressman Mike Rogers (MI-08) is seeking qualified candidates to intern for his Washington, DC office starting immediately (October thru November). Duties include but are not limited to: legislative research, answering phones, opening and sorting mail, leading tours of the Capitol building, attending committee hearings and assisting the rest of the staff with day-to-day responsibilities. This internship is a unique opportunity for individuals to gain first-hand experience of the legislative process while working in a dynamic office environment. The position is unpaid and is subject to flexible scheduling. Michigan ties are a plus but are not required. Resumes should be submitted to kyle.bevers@mail.house.gov
 MEM-330-14
 MEM-329-14
 Page 3 of 11

MEM-328-14
MEM-327-14
A Conservative Republican from Florida is currently seeking un-paid interns for this Washington, D.C. office. Responsibilities will include, but not limited to, handling constituent phone calls, composing correspondence, conducting capitol tours, and attending congressional hearings and briefings. Candidates should be professional, organized, and eager to learn. Florida ties are preferred, but all applicants are encouraged to apply. Please email your cover letter, resume, and availability to FL11internship@gmail.com
House Democratic congressional office seeks part-time and full-time interns for the fall 2014 semester. Ideal candidates will be good writers with strong interpersonal skills and an interest in policy issues of all kinds. Florida ties preferred but not required. This office strives to provide students with exposure to substantive duties like drafting legislative correspondence and covering hearings and briefings for staff, as well as administrative tasks like answering phones and sorting mail. Applications must be submitted to internshipsincongress@outlook.com. A cover letter, which will be used as a writing sample, should be included in the body of your email with a resume separately attached.
The Republican office of the Committee on House Administration seeks energetic and self-motivated individuals with an interest in government and public policy, to apply for its full-time Fall 2014 internship program. Working closely with Committee staff, interns will have the opportunity to gain first-hand knowledge of the inner- workings of a congressional committee and learn about the day-to-day administrative operations of the House of Representatives. Interns are responsible for assisting Committee staff with official proceedings (hearings/markups), oversight, research, assisting with phone inquiries, and providing support to all Committee staff. This is a paid internship. To apply, please send a cover letter and one page resume to CHARep.Intern@mail.house.gov.
Congressman Emanuel Cleaver, II (MO-05) seeks a responsible, focused, self-motivated, enthusiastic, and organized Intern. Positions are available to start immediately. Although internships are unpaid positions, interns are treated as full participants in the Congressional office. Duties will include, but are not limited to: answering phones, processing mail, researching issues, drafting correspondence, attending hearings and briefings, and maintaining a professional atmosphere. Strong writing and effective communication skills, as well as the ability to multi-task, are necessary. Current students are especially encouraged to apply. If you are interested, e-mail a cover letter, resume, and short writing sample to Parker Low at Parker.Low@mail.house.gov.
  MEM-326-14
 MEM-324-14
 Page 4 of 11

MEM-323-14
Republican Congressman seeking paid interns to start immediately. Main responsibilities include answering phones, processing mail, guiding Capitol tours, and assisting the legislative staff by drafting constituent correspondence letters and researching legislative issues. There will be opportunities to attend meetings and hearings as needed, as well as receptions and seminars that interest you. Qualified candidates must be highly motivated self-starters who are detail oriented and have excellent organization and communication skills. This is a paid internship starting immediately with flexible starting and ending dates. California ties are a plus, but not required. Please send inquiries with resume and cover letter attached to cagopintern@gmail.com.
Congressman Benishek from Michigan’s First District seeks unpaid interns to fill positions for January through May 2015. Main responsibilities include answering phones, processing mail, drafting constituent correspondence letters, researching legislative issues, and attending meetings/hearings as needed. There will also be opportunities to attend receptions and seminars of interest. Candidates should be self- motivated, enthusiastic, flexible, and computer-literate (with a good understanding of MS Office). This is a great opportunity for college students seeking academic credit. Michigan ties are preferred. Please e- mail your cover letter, resume, and references to Samuel Grossman at samuel.grossman@mail.house.gov.
The office of Congressman Keith Ellison seeks unpaid interns to fill positions for August through December 2014. Main responsibilities include answering phones, processing mail, drafting constituent correspondence letters, researching legislative issues, and attending meetings/hearings as needed. There will also be opportunities to attend receptions and seminars of interest. Candidates should be self- motivated, enthusiastic, flexible, and computer-literate (with a good understanding of MS Office). This is a great opportunity for college students seeking academic credit. Minnesota ties strongly preferred. If interested, please send resume, cover letter, and two writing samples to zach.freed@mail.house.gov
U.S. Congressman Marc Veasey’s (D-TX) Washington, D.C. press office seeks self-motivated, detail-oriented and highly energetic press intern for fall semester 2014. This is a perfect opportunity for talented students who want to get involved in the communications arena, political arena or both!
Duties include assisting with daily news clips, writing and research, issue tracking, drafting media releases and other communications materials, maintaining press contact lists, special event support,
 MEM-322-14
 MEM-317-14
 MEM-316-14
Page 5 of 11

 MEM-315-14
creating social media content, assisting with digital communications and social networking operations, press events and website content management.
Proficiency in Microsoft Office as well as familiarity with digital and social media preferred. A background in journalism or communications and special skills such as photography, video editing and graphic design a plus, but not required. Undergraduate and graduate students, as well as recent graduates, are encouraged to apply.
Applicants should email a cover letter, resume, two references and a short writing sample to: Jessica.Coscia@mail.house.gov
Paid Fall Internship: The Washington, D.C. office of a California Republican is currently seeking paid interns. Main responsibilities include answering phones, processing mail, guiding Capitol tours, and assisting the legislative staff by drafting constituent correspondence letters and researching legislative issues. There will also be opportunities to attend meetings, briefings, and hearings as needed. Qualified candidates must be highly motivated self-starters who are detail oriented and have excellent organizational and communication skills. This is a paid fall internship starting immediately. California ties are preferred, but not required. Please send inquiries with resume, cover letter, and two one-page writing samples attached to ca.intern2013@gmail.com
Florida Democrat seeks interns for Washington, D.C. office available to start immediately. Candidates should be proactive, and possess superior written and oral communication skills.
This internship will provide exposure to all areas of a legislative
office. Interns will be responsible for assisting the team with phones, mail, tours, flag-requests, and related front office duties. Additional tasks, including drafting constituent correspondence, conducting legislative research, and attending hearings may be assigned as needed. This is a great opportunity for individuals who are interested in learning about the inner-workings of Capitol Hill and the legislative process in a busy office.
To apply, please send an e-mail to DCInternship.Grayson@mail.house.gov with your cover letter, résumé, and two writing samples (not to exceed one page each) attached as PDFs.
A Senior Democratic Maryland Congressman is seeking highly motivated candidates to join his Washington D.C. on Tuesdays,
 MEM-314-14
 MEM-312-14
Page 6 of 11

 MEM-311-14
Wednesdays, and Thursdays through December for an unpaid internship. Candidates should be organized, professional, quick learners, team players and approach new challenges with a positive attitude. To apply for this position, please send an email to Brett.Cozzolino@mail.house.gov with a resume, cover letter, and a short writing sample.
REPORTS TO: Intern Coordinator/Supervisor
CORE RESPONSIBILITIES:
 to assist in performing research, processing the mail, data entry,
reception duties and other office errands.
DUTIES:
 Performs research (CRS, the Library of Congress);
 Sorts and distributes mail;
 Performs data entry, which involves logging in letters and
constituent requests, including names and addresses of
constituents;
 Answers the telephones;
 Notes constituent opinions, including their full names,
addresses, and all relevant information;
 Greets visitors and signs for deliveries; and
 Performs other duties as assigned by the Intern Supervisor.
Ohio Republican seeks full time hard working interns for Fall 2014. Responsibilities include, but aren’t limited to, answering phone calls, assisting with the mail program, providing constituent tours, attending various briefings, providing research for the legislative staff. Qualified candidates will have exceptional writing skills, strong communication skills, ability to work in a fast paced working environment, and have an interest in learning more about the legislative process.
Send a resume and a cover letter to Stephen.Hostelley@mail.house.gov. Ohio candidates are preferred.
Congressman Brad Schneider (IL-10) is currently seeking an unpaid intern to start work in September in his Washington, D.C. office. Interns perform a variety of front office responsibilities, including answering phones, receiving guests, and providing tours of the Capitol Building. They will also research legislation for the Member and legislative staff, attend hearings and briefings, write memos, and answer constituent letters on various issues before the House. Interns should possess strong research, writing, analytical, and interpersonal skills. Interested candidates should email their resume and cover letter to internshipsIL10@gmail.com.
 MEM-310-14
 Page 7 of 11

MEM-309-14
House Judiciary Committee press office seeks self-motivated, detail- oriented and highly energetic part-time press intern for fall 2014. Duties include compiling daily news clips, issue tracking and research, drafting media releases and other communications materials, maintaining press contact lists, special event support, and conceptualizing social media content. A background in journalism or communications and special skills such as photography, video editing and graphic design a plus, but not required. Undergraduate and graduate students, as well as recent graduates, are encouraged to apply. Michigan ties are a plus. Start and end dates are flexible. This internship is unpaid, but the office will accommodate applicants seeking to earn academic credit. Please submit a one page resume, a short writing sample, and a cover letter that includes date and hours of availability to HouseJudiciaryDems@gmail.com.
The office of Congressman Jim Himes (D-CT-4) is currently seeking full and part time unpaid interns for the fall 2014 semester to work in the Congressman’s Washington, DC office. Responsibilities include, but are not limited to, sorting income constituent correspondence, drafting reply letters on behalf of the Congressman, and giving tours of the U.S. Capitol to constituents.
Successful applicants are strong communicators – i.e., are good writers and speakers – are able to work cooperatively with others, are organized, have a positive attitude and a sense of humor, and are reliable. Applicants should also have working knowledge and curiosity of current events and policy topics, as well as a willingness to perform a variety of tasks and administrative functions. This is an excellent opportunity to learn more about the legislative process and better understand the inner workings of a Congressional office.
Connecticut ties are preferred, but all applicants are encouraged to apply. For any questions or to apply, please contact our internship coordinator at himes.internship@mail.house.gov. All applications should consist of one cover letter, resume, and a brief (1-3 page) writing sample. No phone calls or drop-ins, please.
Illinois Representative John Shimkus is currently accepting applications for Fall semester internship positions in his Washington D.C. office. This unpaid internship is available on either a full-time or part-time basis. Qualified candidates will be highly organized, prompt, responsible, and ready to work in a fast paced environment. Strong oral and communication skills are a must. Daily responsibilities will include, but are not limited to, assisting staff, answering phones, organizing mail, giving tours of the Capitol Building, and attending hearings and briefings for legislative staff. Interns will gain valuable
  MEM-307-14
 MEM-306-14
Page 8 of 11

 MEM-305-14
Capitol Hill experience and further their understanding of the legislative process. Illinois ties are preferred but not necessary. All interested applicants should e-mail their resume and cover letter to midwestinternship@gmail.com
The Office of Congressman McClintock (CA-04) is seeking immediate fall interns for his Washington, D.C. office. Applicants should possess conservative values, as well as strong written and verbal communication skills. Interns will gain first-hand experience in the operation and management of a Congressional office. Internship duties include attending Congressional hearings, leading U.S. Capitol tours, answering phones, managing constituent mail database, drafting constituent correspondence, and assisting legislative staff with research.
Those with ties to California are encouraged to apply. Interested applicants should send their resume, availability, and a brief cover letter summarizing their interest in working for Congressman McClintock to Rachel.Long@mail.house.gov. Please use “2014 Fall Internship” in the subject line. No phone calls, drop-ins, or faxes please.
The office of Congressman Ron Barber of Arizona seeks qualified interns for our fall internship program. Interns can expect to gain exposure to the day-to-day activities of Congress while playing an active role in the daily work of a Congressional office. Congressman Barber’s district deals extensively with border and immigration issues, alternative energy, scientific research, and national security. Interns can expect experience dealing with a wide variety of issues of critical importance to the nation.
Our internship program places interns in roles with significant responsibility, so we seek only those looking to gain meaningful experience. Responsibilities include assisting with constituent communications, leading Capitol tours, general administrative duties and assisting with special projects. Prospective applicants should be personable, self-starters, quick-learning and eager to take an active role in the workings of a Congressional office.
Internships are unpaid, but arrangements can be made with your school for academic credit. Both part-time and full-time internships are available, but preference will be given to those who can dedicate at least 25 hours per week.
Interested applicants should send a cover letter and resume to az.house.internship@gmail.com. Individuals with Arizona ties are strongly encouraged to apply. No calls please.
 MEM-304-14
 Page 9 of 11

MEM-303-14
Fall Press Intern - NY Democrat is seeking press and social media interns for the Fall of 2014 in his Washington, D.C.
office. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to, compiling press clips, monitoring daily news, drafting talking points and press releases, managing social media outlets and working closely with senior staff. The ideal candidate will possess meticulous editing skills, expertise in new social media platforms, an ability to work in a fast- paced environment, professionalism and a good sense of humor. Please note that the internship is unpaid and housing is not provided, but students can qualify for academic credit depending on the requirements of the college or university. Interested applicants should e-mail a cover letter, resume, short writing sample (in the form of a speech or press release), and dates of availability with "Press Intern Fall 2014" in the subject line to NY.PressIntern@mail.house.gov. Equal opportunity employer. No phone calls or drop-ins please.
A Democratic California Congressman is seeking highly motivated interns to join his Washington, DC office for a part or full time unpaid internship for the autumn term (September-December). Candidates should be organized, professional, quick learners, and team players. Strong oral and written communication skills and close attention to detail are important. Main responsibilities include but are not limited to assisting staff with legislative, administrative, and press related projects, writing memos and talking points, attending hearings and meetings, answering constituent phone calls, leading tours of the US Capitol, assisting with scheduling, sorting and distributing mail, and managing tour and flag requests. Candidates with California ties and previous internship/work experience are strongly encouraged to apply. Please e-mail a resume and cover letter to Intern.Resume@mail.house.gov.
Fall Intern – The Office of Congressman David Price (NC-04) is seeking qualified candidates to intern in our Washington, D.C. office for the fall semester (September through the end of November.) This unpaid internship will provide valuable hands-on experience in a Congressional office and a greater understanding of the legislative process. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to: attending Congressional briefings, conducting research for staffers, responding to constituent inquiries, operating the phones, sorting the mail, and giving tours of the Capitol.
The internship program is open to college undergraduates, regardless of major, who are attending a DC-area college or who are participating in a semester program in Washington sponsored by a college or university. NC ties are required. Please fill out the application and follow the submitting instructions at
 MEM-271-14
 MEM-259-14
Page 10 of 11

http://price.house.gov/internships/.
 Page 11 of 11
