 ________________________________________________________________________
House Vacancy Announcement and Placement Service (HVAPS)
B-235 Longworth House Office Building Washington, D.C. 20515 202-226-5836
Vacancy Bulletins are available for pick-up in
Longworth HOB - B-227 (CAO First Call Customer Service Center) or in the CAO Human Resources Office - Ford HOB 102
To Subscribe or Unsubscribe to the Vacancy Listserv visit:
http://www.house.gov/content/jobs/
Job Line: 202-226-4504 _____________________________________________________________________________
 MEM-294-14
INTERNSHIP VACANCY LISTING
Week of August 18, 2014
Nevada Congressman Steven Horsford is seeking current college students or recent college graduates wishing to gain Capitol Hill experience for a full-time or part-time semester internship to begin in August and/or September 2014.
We are seeking motivated, organized, and reliable individuals to assist the legislative and administrative staff with day-to-day duties. Such duties include assisting the legislative and communications staff, attending briefings and hearings, answering phones, drafting constituent correspondence letters, doing legislative research and various other tasks. The internship is unpaid, though interns will gain valuable Hill and office experience and will have access to many unique Hill opportunities. Nevada and District 4 ties are preferred, but not necessary.
Please send a resume and cover letter
to NV04Internships@mail.house.gov. Your application should include your anticipated start date and availability. Please no drop bys
 Page 1 of 17

MEM-293-14
or phone calls.
Internships are currently available in Congresswoman Zoe Lofgren’s (CA-19) Washington, D.C. office for the 2014 Fall Semester. Congresswoman Lofgren represents California’s 19th Congressional District, which lies in the heart of California’s “Silicon Valley”.
Interns have the chance to experience the fast-paced atmosphere of a busy Congressional office and gain invaluable work experience. This is an excellent opportunity for those interested in the legislative process. Interns’ responsibilities will vary—in addition to answering phones and running errands around the Capitol, interns will have the opportunity to attend hearings and briefings, research legislation for legislative staff, and answer constituent letters on various issues before the House.
Qualified applicants must possess excellent writing and analytical skills, a demonstrated work ethic, and ability to function in a fast-paced environment. A successful candidate will be motivated, able to multitask, and have the ability to work well under pressure. Full-time and part-time internship positions are available beginning September 3, 2014. Part-time interns must work at least three full days a week. Internships are unpaid. California-19 and/or California ties are preferred but not required. Interested applicants should apply through http://lofgren.house.gov/. Please cite Brad Traverse as source of this lead.
Congressman Dan Kildee’s Washington, D.C. office is always seeking motivated and hard-working college students for fall internships. Although internships are unpaid, students will gain valuable work experience in a fast-paced congressional office.
QUALIFICATIONS: Applicants must be highly motivated, have excellent oral and written communications skills, responsible, dependable, and eager to learn.
JOB DESCRIPTION: Interns are expected to carry out any task assigned to them. Tasks include and are not limited to the following: Researching legislative issues, preparing constituent correspondence, data entry, and helping maintain the efficient day-to-day operations of an active Congressional office.
If interested, please send a resume and letters of recommendation to Ghada Alkiek at ghada.alkiek@mail.house.gov
For more information on Congressman Dan Kildee and Michigan’s 5th Congressional District, please visit our website at www.dankildee.house.gov
 MEM-292-14
  Page 2 of 17

MEM-291-14
New York Congressman Jerrold Nadler (D-NY) is seeking unpaid Interns for the fall semester, preferably to begin in late August and finish in December. Interns will:
 Assist with office administrative tasks including, sorting incoming mail, greeting visitors, and answering the telephone.
 Assist in the preparation of constituent responses, bills, and amendments.
 Perform legislative research.
 Respond to requests from constituents.
 Attend briefings, hearings, and special events where they may
have the opportunity to meet with Members of Congress,
leaders of industry, and the press.
 Gain valuable Hill experience and learn about the federal
legislative process.
Currently, Congressman Jerrold Nadler represents New York's 10th Congressional District, which includes the residents of most of the Upper West Side, Lower Manhattan and sections of
Brooklyn. Congressman Nadler serves on the Judiciary Committee and on the Transportation and Infrastructure Committee, where he is the highest ranking member from New York. He is the Ranking member of The Subcommittee on Courts, Intellectual Property, and the Internet.
Applicant Instructions:
Please e-mail or fax a resume, brief cover letter, and 1-2 page writing sample to:
Email: Gabriella.Libby@mail.house.gov Fax: 202-225-6923.
Congressional Black Caucus Internship- Fall 2014 - The Congressional Black Caucus is accepting applications for internship positions available for fall 2014. This unpaid internship will provide valuable hands on experience in developing and executing initiatives for a Congressional Caucus and will provide an understanding the Caucus’s role in the legislative process. This is an excellent opportunity for college students and recent graduates seeking Capitol Hill experience. All majors are encouraged to apply. Interested applicants should e-mail a resume, cover letter, and writing sample to Charlyn.Stanberry@mail.house.gov with “Fall 2014 Internship” in the subject. Please also include dates of availability.
Fall Legal Fellow - Energetic NY Freshman Democrat is seeking a highly motivated Legislative Fellow to assist with a number of issues, including criminal justice, intellectual property, and financial services. Responsibilities include analyzing policy issues, drafting memos, researching policy positions, and assisting extremely active
 MEM-290-14
 MEM-289-14
Page 3 of 17

 MEM-288-14
legislative staff as needed. The ideal candidate should possess strong communication skills, attention to detail, and the ability to operate in a fast-paced environment. Candidates with New York ties and previous internship/work experience are strongly encouraged to apply. This fellowship is unpaid but is eligible for school credit where
applicable. Please e-mail a resume, cover letter, and a writing sample to NY.ResumeInbox@mail.house.gov with “Legal Fellowship” in the subject line. Equal opportunity employer. No calls or walk-ins please.
The office of Congresswoman Diana DeGette (CO-01) is seeking applications for internships during the Fall. As a fast-paced office for an active member of the Democratic leadership, we expect a lot from our interns and pride ourselves on an excellent internship program. Duties include, but are not limited to, answering phones, sorting mail, attending briefings, drafting constituent correspondence, and providing assistance to the legislative staff. Applicants must have excellent writing and communications skills. Interested applicants should email a cover letter, resume, and brief writing sample (2-3 pages) to tom.gibson@mail.house.gov with the subject line “Intern Application.”
The Washington, DC office of Congressman Peter DeFazio (OR-04) seeks highly motivated interns, full time or part time, for Fall 2014. Successful candidates will demonstrate that they are organized, detail- oriented, and professional. Strong written and oral communication skills are essential.
Intern responsibilities will include but are not limited to assisting staff with legislative, administrative, constituent relations, and press activities. Interns will: answer phones; sort, distribute, and respond to constituent mail; lead tours of the US Capitol building; attend hearings and briefings; and assist with legislative research.
Please send a resume, cover letter, and brief writing sample to matt.leasure@mail.house.gov. Candidates with Oregon ties are strongly encouraged to apply. No phone calls or drop-ins, please.
 MEM-287-14
  The office of Congresswoman Suzan DelBene seeks full and part-time
 interns for her Washington, D.C. office. Interns will work in a fast- paced congressional office, gaining valuable experience and knowledge of the United States Congress. Intern responsibilities include greeting constituents and handling constituent phone calls, assisting staff with administrative tasks, conducting research, and assisting with constituent correspondence. Washington, D.C. interns will have the opportunity to lead tours of the U.S. Capitol as well as attend hearings and briefings for the legislative staff. The ideal candidates will possess exceptional
MEM-284-14
Page 4 of 17

 written and oral communication skills, a high degree of professionalism, as well as a strong interest in public service. Washington state ties are a plus, but are not required. Interested applicants should email a current resume and cover letter to Internship.DelBene@mail.house.gov.
 MEM-283-14
Congressman John Lewis, Representative for the 5th District of Georgia, seeks fall interns for his Washington, D.C., office. Interns will work in a fast-paced setting and gain valuable experience and knowledge of the United States Congress. Responsibilities include greeting constituents and visitors, handling phone calls, supporting staff with administrative tasks, conducting legislative research, aiding communications staff, and assisting with special projects and assignments. Preference will be given to those with Georgia connections and those available full-time.
If you would like to receive more information or apply to our internship program, please complete the application at http://johnlewis.house.gov/. For immediate consideration, please send the application, resume, and writing sample to William.Feeney@mail.house.gov.
Congressman Tim Walz (D-MN) seeks interns for the Fall 2014 semester. Applicants should be highly-motivated, well-organized, and eager to assist with legislative and administrative needs of the staff. Such duties include but are not limited to attending briefings, answering the phones, drafting and responding to constituent letters, assisting in research, giving tours of the capitol, and various other administrative tasks. Applicants should possess an interest in the legislative process, as well as strong written and verbal communications skills. Minnesota ties a plus. Veterans and active military encourage to apply. Applications accepted for both full-time and part-time positions (min. 16 hours per week). This is an unpaid position. To be considered, please send a resume and cover letter by August 22nd to denise.fleming@mail.house.gov with “Fall Internship” in the subject line.
The office of Congressman Keith Ellison seeks unpaid interns to fill positions for August through December 2014.Main responsibilities include answering phones, processing mail, drafting constituent correspondence letters, researching legislative issues, and attending meetings/hearings as needed. There will also be opportunities to attend receptions and seminars of interest. Candidates should be self- motivated, enthusiastic, flexible, and computer-literate (with a good understanding of MS Office). This is a great opportunity for college students seeking academic credit. Minnesota ties strongly preferred. If
  MEM-282-14
 MEM-279-14
Page 5 of 17

 MEM-278-14
interested, please send resume, cover letter, and two writing samples to
zach.freed@mail.house.gov
Congresswoman Terri Sewell (D-AL) is now accepting applications for highly motivated interns to join her Washington, DC for a full time, unpaid internship in the Fall of 2014. Interns will work in a fast-paced Congressional office, gaining valuable experience and knowledge of the United States Congress. Candidates should be proactive, professional, dependable, and have an interest in the legislative process. Excellent oral and written communication skills, the ability to multi- task, and attention to detail are critical for this position. Internships are open to all majors and designed for undergraduate students and recent graduates with an interest in public service. Applicants must have a 3.0 GPA or higher, be enrolled in or have graduated from college, and be 18 years of age or older. Starting and ending dates are flexible, depending on academic calendar, with a preferred start date of September 2nd. Main responsibilities include, but are not limited to, assisting Congressional Staff, preforming research, answering telephones, processing mail, data entry, and general office
duties. Interns will also have the opportunity to attend special events, such as committee meetings and seminars. Candidates with Alabama ties are strongly encouraged to apply. Please e-mail a resume, cover letter, a short writing sample, and a transcript (unofficial is okay) to sewell.interns@mail.house.gov by August 20th, 2014. No calls or walk-ins please.
The office of Congresswoman Susan Davis (CA-53) is accepting applications for interns in Washington, DC on a full or part-time basis for the fall semester. Qualified candidates must be highly motivated, well-organized, detail-oriented, and possess excellent communication skills. The ability to work in teams and use good judgment is critical. Duties will include helping staff with correspondence and research, greeting guests, answering phones, scheduling tours and assisting with other front-office duties. Applicants with an interest in Education Policy are encouraged to apply. Proficiency in Microsoft Office is required. All interested applicants should send a cover letter, resume, and writing sample to CA53DCInternApp@mail.house.gov.
Long-serving, southern Republican is seeking fall interns. Duties include, but are not limited to: staffing front office and greeting visitors, answering phones, coordinating and executing flag and tour requests, assisting with mail processing, and helping with other projects as needed. Strong organizational skills and a positive, team-oriented attitude are required. Interested candidates should send resume and cover letter to congressionalofficejobs@gmail.com
 MEM-277-14
 MEM-276-14
 Page 6 of 17

MEM-275-14
The Office of Congresswoman Jackie Speier (CA-14) is seeking interns fall semester for the DC office. Qualified candidates will be able to multi-task and thrive in a fast-paced work environment, while providing high-quality “customer service” to our constituents. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to, handling constituent correspondence, answering phones, booking and leading constituent tours, attending hearings and briefings, and assisting legislative staff where needed. Students and recent graduates with ties to California’s 14th district are strongly preferred; general California ties are a must. Interested candidates should send their resume, cover letter, and two writing samples to speier.internships@mail.house.gov no later than August 15. Interns will begin August 25 or September 2 depending on their availability, and end in mid-December. Qualified candidates will be contacted for interview. No phone calls, please.
The Washington, D.C. office of Congressman Tim Bishop is currently seeking interns available to begin August and September 2014. Interns should be comfortable answering office phones, greeting office visitors, giving tours of the U.S. Capitol, assisting the legislative staff with research, sorting mail, taking notes at hearings and briefings, and assisting with general office work. Strong writing and interpersonal skills are necessary. Applicants should be hard working, intelligent, and enthusiastic with an interest in politics, history and government. Long Island or New York ties are a plus, but not required. Those interested should send a resume to ny01.internapplications@gmail.com. Qualified applicants will be sent an application packet. College students and recent graduates encouraged to apply. Please note this is an unpaid position. The office of Congressman Tim Bishop is happy to work with colleges and universities for credit.
A Democratic California Congressman is seeking highly motivated interns to join his Washington, DC office for a part or full time unpaid internship for the autumn term (September-December). Candidates should be organized, professional, quick learners, and team players. Strong oral and written communication skills and close attention to detail are important. Main responsibilities include but are not limited to assisting staff with legislative, administrative, and press related projects, writing memos and talking points, attending hearings and meetings, answering constituent phone calls, leading tours of the US Capitol, assisting with scheduling, sorting and distributing mail, and managing tour and flag requests. Candidates with California ties and previous internship/work experience are strongly encouraged to apply. Please e-mail a resume and cover letter to Intern.Resume@mail.house.gov.
The Washington, DC office of Rep. Mark Sanford (SC-01) seeks Page 7 of 17
 MEM-274-14
 MEM-271-14
 MEM-270-14

 MEM-269-14
applicants for unpaid fulltime internships for the fall semester to begin immediately. Applicants should be able to competently handle telephone calls, be well-organized, have an eye for detail, possess strong writing skills, be generally knowledgeable of legislative and related issues, and be able to complete tasks as directed. Main duties include answering telephones, logging constituent calls, giving tours of the Capitol to visitors, opening and sorting mail, and assisting with other administrative tasks. Interns will have many opportunities to take on additional responsibilities within the office, at the discretion of staff. Anyone interested should send a resume to Martha@mail.house.gov.
Congresswoman Chellie Pingree (ME-01) is currently seeking full- or part-time interns for the 2014 fall semester in her Washington, DC office. Interns will assist in the day-to-day operations of a DC Congressional office by supporting members of staff with constituent communication, legislative research, and administrative activities. They will also serve as a tour coordinator and occasionally act as a guide of the United States Capitol to Maine constituents visiting Washington.
Qualified candidates will possess an interest in the legislative process, excellent writing and communication skills, strong attention to detail, and a willingness to learn and take on new tasks. The internship is unpaid, though interns will be an essential component to the effectiveness of the office and will be considered an integral member of the team. Maine ties are preferred, but not necessary.
Please send a resume, cover letter, and brief writing sample to evan.johnston@mail.house.gov with the subject line Fall Internship. Applications will be considered on a rolling basis. Please no drop bys or phone calls.
Congressman Steve Israel (D-NY) is seeking unpaid interns for his Washington, DC office for the fall term (August/September - December, full or part time). Intern duties include answering the phone, writing letters, attending legislative briefings, and assisting staff members with special projects. Attention to detail and strong writing and grammar skills are required. Candidates from the 3rd Congressional District of New York are especially encouraged to apply, although all applications will be considered equally regardless of state or district ties. Prospective candidates should apply online and submit a resume and cover letter to repisraelinterns@gmail.com. No phone calls or drop ins, please.
Congressman Alcee L. Hastings (D-FL) is seeking highly-motivated, self-starting, and detail-orientated individuals for his Fall 2014 internship program to begin as early as August 18th. Opportunities include answering phones, processing mail, drafting constituent
 MEM-268-14
 MEM-267-14
Page 8 of 17

 MEM-266-14
correspondence letters, researching legislative issues, attending Congressional hearings/briefings/seminars, and assisting in administrative operations. The internship is unpaid. Work may qualify for academic credit, depending on the requisites of the college or university.
Please e-mail your cover letter, resume, and a short writing sample to Christian Sy at Christian.Sy@mail.house.gov.
The Washington, D.C. office of Congresswoman Louise M. Slaughter (NY-25) is seeking a full-time press intern to work with Congresswoman Slaughter’s communications team. This position is more advanced than a standard Congressional internship, requiring strong writing skills while being an avid consumer of political media.
The press intern will work directly with the Press Secretary and Digital Director to carry out responsibilities including - but not limited to - helping create digital content, developing press lists, collecting and distributing press clips, drafting press releases, and contacting reporters. Special skills such as photography or video editing a plus. Standard schedule begins with aggregating news clips at 8:00 am and ends at 4:00 pm.
While the position is unpaid, the office will work with universities and academic programs to accommodate applicants wishing to earn academic credit. First-hand experience in the congressional office will provide a unique opportunity into the functions of a fast-paced press operation for a senior Democratic member office. It will also offer a unique insight into legislative and parliamentary procedure, as Congresswoman Slaughter is Senior Democrat on the Committee on Rules. The Rules Committee determines the parameters of debate for all major legislation before it can be considered on the House Floor, including which amendments can be offered.
Applicants should e-mail a cover letter, resume, and a one-to-three page writing sample, and if applicable, a portfolio sample to Jack Spasiano at NY25.InternApplications@mail.house.gov Please do not hesitate to contact Jack at 202-225-3615 with any questions.
Senior Democratic Congressman Brad Sherman (CA-30) seeks highly motivated, full and part-time interns for Fall 2014. Interns are responsible for both administrative and legislative duties. Legislative support includes preparing materials for hearings, attending hearings and briefings, reaching out to agencies and congressional offices, and researching legislation for the Member and Legislative
Staff. Administrative tasks include answering phones, greeting visitors, leading tours and sorting mail.
 MEM-265-14
Page 9 of 17

 MEM-264-14
Candidates should be professional, possess strong oral and written communication skills, have the ability to multitask, and have a good sense of humor. Ties to California’s 30th Congressional District are a plus but not required. Interested applicants should e-mail a cover letter and resume to luke.stone@mail.house.gov with “CA-30 Internship” as the subject. Please do not hesitate to contact Luke with any questions by sending him an email or calling (202) 225-5911.
Congressman Vern Buchanan (R-FL-16) has full-time and part-time, unpaid internships available for the fall session (August-December) in his Washington, DC office. Qualified candidates should possess excellent organizational and communication skills, should have a positive attitude, and a strong work ethic. Although internships are unpaid, our office is happy to fill out any necessary forms for students to receive credit at their respective college or university.
All interested individuals should submit a cover letter and resume to jillian.gates@mail.house.gov with “2014 Fall Internship” in the subject line.
The Office of Congresswoman Ann McLane Kuster (NH-02) is seeking qualified candidates to intern full time and part time in our Washington, D.C. office starting in August/September 2014. Candidates with ties to the Northeast—especially New Hampshire—are especially encouraged to apply.
Interns will assist the staff with a variety of tasks, including office administration, legislative research, constituent correspondence, and other duties as assigned.
Administration will include daily tasks such as welcoming guests, being aware of the Congresswoman’s and staff schedules, answering phones, constituent tours, mail administration, and other duties. Legislative research and constituent correspondence will include being aware of current and pending legislation, researching legislation for constituent correspondence, attending briefings, and other duties.
Candidates should have excellent writing and communication skills, strong organizational abilities, a good work ethic, an ability to work independently, and a drive to take initiative.
If candidates have any questions or wish to apply, please send a cover letter, resume, writing sample, and references to the ATT of Scott Elias at NH02.Internship@mail.house.gov or call 202-225-5206. Please include “Your Last Name-Internship App” in the subject line and include your availability in your cover letter and/or email.
 MEM-263-14
 Page 10 of 17

MEM-262-14
Congressman Brad Schneider (IL-10) is currently seeking an unpaid intern to start work in August or September in his Washington, D.C. office. Interns perform a variety of front office responsibilities, including answering phones, receiving guests, and providing tours of the Capitol Building. They will also research legislation for the Member and legislative staff, attend hearings and briefings, write memos, and answer constituent letters on various issues before the House. Interns should possess strong research, writing, analytical, and interpersonal skills. Interested candidates should email their resume and cover letter to internshipsIL10@gmail.com.
The Washington, DC office of Congresswoman Louise Slaughter (D- NY) is offering internship opportunities for students and recent graduates starting immediately. First-hand experience in Congresswoman Slaughter’s office will provide interns with an unparalleled knowledge and understanding of the development of public policy and government affairs. Intern responsibilities include drafting letters to constituents, attending committee hearings, writing summary briefs, researching various issues for the legislative staff and assisting with additional office duties.
Interns will receive unique insight into the legislative process and parliamentary procedure as a result of her position as the Ranking Member of the House Rules Committee. The Rules Committee determines the parameters of debate for all major pieces of legislation before it can be considered on the House Floor, including which amendments can be offered.
The internship provides different opportunities with staff to discuss their experiences on the Hill and future employment strategies.
Applicants should e-mail a cover letter, resume, and a one to three page writing sample to Jack Spasiano at NY25.InternApplications@mail.house.gov. Please do not hesitate to contact Jack at (202) 225-3615 with any questions.
The Office of Representative Kevin Brady (TX-08) is currently seeking full-time fall interns for our Washington, D.C. office. Qualified candidates are well organized, with good oral and written communication skills, and possess a strong interest in learning about the political process and congressional affairs. Duties include but are not limited to, answering phones, compiling briefing binders, batching mail, performing legislative research, and attending briefings. Interns interact heavily with constituents so a positive attitude is a must. Applicants must be detail oriented with a strong work ethic and an eagerness to represent the 8th district of Texas. Previous Hill
 MEM-261-14
 MEM-260-14
Page 11 of 17

 MEM-259-14
experience not required. Though start date is flexible, a mid-August start date is ideal. Interested Candidates should send a resume and cover letter to: TX08intern@gmail.com
Fall Intern – The Office of Congressman David Price (NC-04) is seeking qualified candidates to intern in our Washington, D.C. office for the fall semester (September through the end of November.) This unpaid internship will provide valuable hands-on experience in a Congressional office and a greater understanding of the legislative process. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to: attending Congressional briefings, conducting research for staffers, responding to constituent inquiries, operating the phones, sorting the mail, and giving tours of the Capitol.
The internship program is open to college undergraduates, regardless of major, who are attending a DC-area college or who are participating in a semester program in Washington sponsored by a college or university. NC ties are required. Please fill out the application by September 1st and follow the submitting instructions at http://price.house.gov/internships/.
Congresswoman Candice S. Miller (R-MI) seeks legislative interns for the Fall 2014 (September-December) semester. Interns will work in a fast-paced congressional office, gaining valuable exposure and knowledge of the legislative process and the United States Congress. Intern responsibilities include greeting constituents, managing constituent phone calls, and assisting staff with administrative tasks. Interns will also have the opportunity to conduct legislative research, assist with constituent correspondence, and attend legislative briefings, congressional hearings, receptions, and press events.
Interns must have a good attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Successful interns will be able to find information with little assistance, be able to work both independently as well as part of a team environment, and possess a strong attention to detail. Applicants should have working knowledge of current events and policy topics, as well as a willingness to perform a variety of tasks and administrative functions. Michigan ties are strongly preferred; however, candidates from outside the state will be considered. Undergraduate students are strongly encouraged to
apply. This is an unpaid position, but a great opportunity for students seeking academic credit. To apply, please send cover letter, resume and writing sample to MI10Internship@gmail.com .
The Office of Congressman Robert A. Brady (PA-01) seeks interns for fall 2014 (Sept-Dec). Internship responsibilities will include: assisting
 MEM-258-14
 MEM-257-14
Page 12 of 17

 MEM-256-14
with research, processing mail, data entry, reception duties, office errands, and other duties as assigned by Intern Supervisor. Ideal candidate will have strong social skills, good oral and written communication abilities, a willingness to learn, basic knowledge of the political process, and a firm opinion on the best cheesesteak in Philadelphia. Pennsylvania ties preferred. Please send a resume, cover letter, and writing sample to Liz Leibowitz at liz.leibowitz@mail.house.gov. Please no phone calls or drop-ins.
The Office of Congresswoman Elizabeth H. Esty is seeking qualified candidates to intern in our Washington, D.C office. Start date: Immediately through November with flexibility
Interns will assist the staff with a variety of tasks, including office administration, legislative research, constituent correspondence, and other duties as assigned.
Administration will include daily tasks such as welcoming guests, being aware of the Congressman’s and staff’s schedules, answering phones, constituent tours, mail administration, and other duties.
Legislative research and constituent correspondence will include being aware of current and pending legislation, researching legislation for constituent correspondence, attending briefings, and other duties.
Candidates should have excellent writing and communication skills, strong organizational abilities, a good work ethic, an ability to work independently.
Connecticut ties preferred but not required.
Hours will be Monday-Friday 9:00am-6:00pm
If candidates have any questions or wish to apply, please send resume, cover letter, and writing sample to Nakia.Mulley@mail.house.gov
Congresswoman Jaime Herrera Beutler’s office is currently accepting applications for internships in the Washington D.C. and the Vancouver offices. This is a great opportunity for college students, recent graduates, military veterans and others who are interested in an insider’s view of the legislative process and the daily operations of a congressional office.
Typical intern responsibilities in the D.C. office include: leading tours Page 13 of 17
   MEM-255-14

   MEM-254-14
of the U.S. Capitol, fielding calls from constituents, administrative tasks, attending congressional hearings and briefings, and assisting staff in a variety of projects including research, writing and editing.
Intern tasks in the Vancouver office include: fielding calls from constituents, administrative tasks, assisting staff in a variety of projects and events, sorting and delivering mail, and entering data.
All candidates should possess great oral and written communication skills, be highly motivated, demonstrate knowledge of computer applications, maintain a positive attitude and show initiative.
Applicants must be able to make a commitment of at least 10 weeks. Those with Washington state or Pacific Northwest ties are preferred, but all may apply. Internships are unpaid; however, if academic credit can be awarded through your school, the office will be happy to assist in that process.
To apply, please submit the following materials to
Breanna.Deutsch@mail.house.gov:
Do not hesitate to contact the office if you have any questions regarding our internship program.
Nevada Congressman Steven Horsford (NV-04) is currently seeking an intern for the Fall of 2014. Applicants must be at least a high school junior/senior, college student, or recent college graduate wishing to gain legislative experience for a full-time or part-time semester internship to begin in August and/or September 2014. We are seeking motivated, organized, and reliable individuals to assist the district office staff with day-to-day duties. Such duties include assisting the staffers and communications staff, attending congressional outreach events, answering phones, working with the constituents of NV-04, doing legislative research and various other tasks.
The internship is unpaid, and will take place in the Congressman’s District office in Nevada. Interns will gain valuable congressional and office experience and will have access to many unique opportunities. Nevada and District 4 ties are preferred, but not necessary. Please send a resume and cover letter to NV04Internships@gmail.com. Include your anticipated start and end dates and have “DO Internship” as the subject of your email. Please no drop bys, phone calls, or emailing staff members.
Progressive Maryland Democrat seeks qualified interns to join her Page 14 of 17
 MEM-252-14

 MEM-251-14
District office for unpaid Constituent Services and Outreach internships during the Fall 2014 term.
Constituent Service Internship - Constituent Service Interns will work in the District office to assist Constituent Service Representatives. Responsibilities include assisting with constituent files, gathering information from federal agencies, and answering constituent calls. S/he will monitor congressional inquiries through online databases.
Outreach Internship - The Outreach Intern will work in the District office supporting the team with a variety of outreach projects and activities, including event planning, and advocacy communications. The Outreach Intern also conducts project research using the web and traditional sources such as booth set up at events. S/he helps develop several databases and lists of state, local/civic, and federal organizations and government agencies. S/he must monitor local and national media through print, online/blog and television news media. The Outreach Intern also responds to outreach-related initiatives and assists with general outreach efforts.
Ideal candidates for both positions will be detailed oriented, well organized, and able to conduct research. Interns should also possess strong written and verbal communication skills in a professional setting. Undergraduates and recent graduates of any major with ties to Maryland are strongly encouraged to apply. Please email a resume, cover letter stating your availability, and a brief and relevant writing sample (maximum one page) by August 15th to internship.md04@mail.house.gov.
Progressive Maryland Democrat seeks qualified interns to join her Washington, D.C. office for an unpaid legislative internship during the Fall 2014 term. Applicants should have a familiarity with the legislative process and have a desire to learn while being a part of a hardworking team. Ideal candidates will possess strong writing and verbal communication skills, a demonstrated interest in legislative issues, the ability to multi-task and conduct research, and an enthusiastic attitude. Interns will have the opportunity to assist staff with legislative and scheduling projects, attend briefings and hearings, draft memos, sort and distribute mail, and give Capitol tours. Candidates with Maryland ties are strongly encouraged to apply. Please email a resume, cover letter stating your availability, and a brief and relevant writing sample (maximum one page) by August 15th to internship.md04@mail.house.gov.
The office of Congressman Jon Runyan (NJ-03) seeks full-time unpaid interns for the Washington D.C. office for fall 2014. The office would
 MEM-250-14
Page 15 of 17

 MEM-249-14
prefer applicants to have an availability from mid-August through December. Intern responsibilities include answering phones, interacting with constituents, running errands, and administering tours of the Capitol. NJ ties are preferred, but not required, and candidates should lean towards having conservative views. Please email a resume, cover letter, and writing sample to NJ03Internships@gmail.com.
The office of Congressman Keith Ellison seeks unpaid interns to fill positions for August through December 2014.Main responsibilities include answering phones, processing mail, drafting constituent correspondence letters, researching legislative issues, and attending meetings/hearings as needed. There will also be opportunities to attend receptions and seminars of interest. Candidates should be self- motivated, enthusiastic, flexible, and computer-literate (with a good understanding of MS Office). This is a great opportunity for college students seeking academic credit. Minnesota ties strongly preferred. If interested, please send resume, cover letter, and two writing samples to zach.freed@mail.house.gov
Congressman John D. Dingell (D-MI) is seeking full-time Congressional Interns for his Washington, DC office during the fall 2014. This internship position will provide individuals the opportunity to work in a fast-paced Congressional office while receiving hands-on political experience. Duties include answering phones, leading U.S. Capitol tours and assisting staff members with research and special projects. There will also be frequent opportunities to attend legislative hearings of personal interest. The ideal candidate will be motivated, detail orientated and possess strong communication and writing
skills. This is a great opportunity for recent graduates seeking Hill experience. Michigan ties are preferred. Interested applicants should submit a resume and cover letter to kevin.rambosk@mail.house.gov
Legislative Intern- The Office of Congressman Hakeem Jeffries is seeking a highly motivated intern to join his Washington, DC office for a part time unpaid internship this fall. Candidates should possess a professional and courteous demeanor, interest in the legislative process, excellent communication skills, the ability to multi-task, attention to detail, and a sense of humor. Main responsibilities include, but are not limited to, attending Congressional briefings, responding to constituent correspondence, assisting with flag requests, and general office
duties. Candidates with New York ties and previous internship/work experience are strongly encouraged to apply. Please e-mail a resume, cover letter, and a short writing sample to NY.ResumeInbox@mail.house.gov. Equal opportunity employer. No calls or walk-ins please.
 MEM-248-14
 MEM-247-14
 Page 16 of 17

MEM-246-14
MEM-223-14
The Office of Rep. Scott Rigell (VA-02) is seeking politically Conservative unpaid fall interns in their Washington, DC office to begin mid-August or early September. The Office seeks an outgoing, enthusiastic person with at least 3 days/week availability who would like experience working in a Congressional Office. Virginia ties are a plus. Interested persons should submit brief Cover Letter and Resume to VA02internships@gmail.com.
Congressman Jerry McNerney (CA-09) is currently accepting applications for Fall semester internship positions in his Washington D.C. office. This unpaid internship will provide valuable hands-on experience in a Congressional office and a greater understanding of the legislative process. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to, attending Congressional briefings, giving tours of the Capitol, conducting research, responding to constituent inquiries, and processing tour and flag requests. Qualified applicants should possess a professional and courteous demeanor, excellent communication skills, the ability to multi-task, fastidious attention to detail, and interest in the legislative and governmental process.
This is an excellent opportunity for college students and recent graduates seeking Capitol Hill experience. All majors are encouraged to apply. Ties to California’s Ninth Congressional District are preferred, but not required. Interested applicants should email a resume and cover letter to nick.sullivan@mail.house.gov with “CA-09 Internship” in the subject line. Include dates of availability.
  Page 17 of 17
