 ________________________________________________________________________
House Vacancy Announcement and Placement Service (HVAPS)
B-235 Longworth House Office Building Washington, D.C. 20515 202-226-5836
Vacancy Bulletins are available for pick-up in
Longworth HOB - B-227 (CAO First Call Customer Service Center) or in the CAO Human Resources Office - Ford HOB 102
To Subscribe or Unsubscribe to the Vacancy Listserv visit:
http://www.house.gov/content/jobs/
Job Line: 202-226-4504 _____________________________________________________________________________
 MEM-326-14
INTERNSHIP VACANCY LISTING
Week of September 15, 2014
The Republican office of the Committee on House Administration seeks energetic and self-motivated individuals with an interest in government and public policy, to apply for its full-time Fall 2014 internship program. Working closely with Committee staff, interns will have the opportunity to gain first-hand knowledge of the inner- workings of a congressional committee and learn about the day-to-day administrative operations of the House of Representatives. Interns are responsible for assisting Committee staff with official proceedings (hearings/markups), oversight, research, assisting with phone inquiries, and providing support to all Committee staff. This is a paid internship. To apply, please send a cover letter and one page resume to CHARep.Intern@mail.house.gov.
Congressman Emanuel Cleaver, II (MO-05) seeks a responsible, focused, self-motivated, enthusiastic, and organized Intern. Positions are available to start immediately. Although internships are unpaid positions, interns are treated as full participants in the Congressional office. Duties will include, but are not limited to: answering phones,
 MEM-324-14
Page 1 of 13

 MEM-323-14
processing mail, researching issues, drafting correspondence, attending hearings and briefings, and maintaining a professional atmosphere. Strong writing and effective communication skills, as well as the ability to multi-task, are necessary. Current students are especially encouraged to apply. If you are interested, e-mail a cover letter, resume, and short writing sample to Parker Low at Parker.Low@mail.house.gov.
Republican Congressman seeking paid interns to start immediately. Main responsibilities include answering phones, processing mail, guiding Capitol tours, and assisting the legislative staff by drafting constituent correspondence letters and researching legislative issues. There will be opportunities to attend meetings and hearings as needed, as well as receptions and seminars that interest you. Qualified candidates must be highly motivated self-starters who are detail oriented and have excellent organization and communication skills. This is a paid internship starting immediately with flexible starting and ending dates. California ties are a plus, but not required. Please send inquiries with resume and cover letter attached to cagopintern@gmail.com.
Congressman Benishek from Michigan’s First District seeks unpaid interns to fill positions for January through May 2015. Main responsibilities include answering phones, processing mail, drafting constituent correspondence letters, researching legislative issues, and attending meetings/hearings as needed. There will also be opportunities to attend receptions and seminars of interest. Candidates should be self- motivated, enthusiastic, flexible, and computer-literate (with a good understanding of MS Office). This is a great opportunity for college students seeking academic credit. Michigan ties are preferred. Please e- mail your cover letter, resume, and references to Samuel Grossman at samuel.grossman@mail.house.gov.
The office of Congressman Keith Ellison seeks unpaid interns to fill positions for August through December 2014. Main responsibilities include answering phones, processing mail, drafting constituent correspondence letters, researching legislative issues, and attending meetings/hearings as needed. There will also be opportunities to attend receptions and seminars of interest. Candidates should be self- motivated, enthusiastic, flexible, and computer-literate (with a good understanding of MS Office). This is a great opportunity for college students seeking academic credit. Minnesota ties strongly preferred. If interested, please send resume, cover letter, and two writing samples to zach.freed@mail.house.gov
U.S. Congressman Marc Veasey’s (D-TX) Washington, D.C. press office seeks self-motivated, detail-oriented and highly energetic press
 MEM-322-14
 MEM-317-14
 MEM-316-14
Page 2 of 13

 MEM-315-14
intern for fall semester 2014. This is a perfect opportunity for talented students who want to get involved in the communications arena, political arena or both!
Duties include assisting with daily news clips, writing and research, issue tracking, drafting media releases and other communications materials, maintaining press contact lists, special event support, creating social media content, assisting with digital communications and social networking operations, press events and website content management.
Proficiency in Microsoft Office as well as familiarity with digital and social media preferred. A background in journalism or communications and special skills such as photography, video editing and graphic design a plus, but not required. Undergraduate and graduate students, as well as recent graduates, are encouraged to apply.
Applicants should email a cover letter, resume, two references and a short writing sample to: Jessica.Coscia@mail.house.gov
Paid Fall Internship: The Washington, D.C. office of a California Republican is currently seeking paid interns. Main responsibilities include answering phones, processing mail, guiding Capitol tours, and assisting the legislative staff by drafting constituent correspondence letters and researching legislative issues. There will also be opportunities to attend meetings, briefings, and hearings as needed. Qualified candidates must be highly motivated self-starters who are detail oriented and have excellent organizational and communication skills. This is a paid fall internship starting immediately. California ties are preferred, but not required. Please send inquiries with resume, cover letter, and two one-page writing samples attached to ca.intern2013@gmail.com
Florida Democrat seeks interns for Washington, D.C. office available to start immediately. Candidates should be proactive, and possess superior written and oral communication skills.
This internship will provide exposure to all areas of a legislative
office. Interns will be responsible for assisting the team with phones, mail, tours, flag-requests, and related front office duties. Additional tasks, including drafting constituent correspondence, conducting legislative research, and attending hearings may be assigned as needed. This is a great opportunity for individuals who are interested in learning about the inner-workings of Capitol Hill and the legislative process in a busy office.
To apply, please send an e-mail to Page 3 of 13
 MEM-314-14

 MEM-312-14
DCInternship.Grayson@mail.house.gov with your cover letter, résumé, and two writing samples (not to exceed one page each) attached as PDFs.
A Senior Democratic Maryland Congressman is seeking highly motivated candidates to join his Washington D.C. on Tuesdays, Wednesdays, and Thursdays through December for an unpaid internship. Candidates should be organized, professional, quick learners, team players and approach new challenges with a positive attitude. To apply for this position, please send an email to Brett.Cozzolino@mail.house.gov with a resume, cover letter, and a short writing sample.
REPORTS TO: Intern Coordinator/Supervisor
CORE RESPONSIBILITIES:
 to assist in performing research, processing the mail, data entry,
reception duties and other office errands.
DUTIES:
 Performs research (CRS, the Library of Congress);
 Sorts and distributes mail;
 Performs data entry, which involves logging in letters and
constituent requests, including names and addresses of
constituents;
 Answers the telephones;
 Notes constituent opinions, including their full names,
addresses, and all relevant information;
 Greets visitors and signs for deliveries; and
 Performs other duties as assigned by the Intern Supervisor.
Ohio Republican seeks full time hard working interns for Fall 2014. Responsibilities include, but aren’t limited to, answering phone calls, assisting with the mail program, providing constituent tours, attending various briefings, providing research for the legislative staff. Qualified candidates will have exceptional writing skills, strong communication skills, ability to work in a fast paced working environment, and have an interest in learning more about the legislative process.
Send a resume and a cover letter to Stephen.Hostelley@mail.house.gov. Ohio candidates are preferred.
Congressman Brad Schneider (IL-10) is currently seeking an unpaid intern to start work in September in his Washington, D.C. office. Interns perform a variety of front office responsibilities, including answering phones, receiving guests, and providing tours of the Capitol
 MEM-311-14
 MEM-310-14
Page 4 of 13

 MEM-309-14
Building. They will also research legislation for the Member and legislative staff, attend hearings and briefings, write memos, and answer constituent letters on various issues before the House. Interns should possess strong research, writing, analytical, and interpersonal skills. Interested candidates should email their resume and cover letter to internshipsIL10@gmail.com.
House Judiciary Committee press office seeks self-motivated, detail- oriented and highly energetic part-time press intern for fall 2014. Duties include compiling daily news clips, issue tracking and research, drafting media releases and other communications materials, maintaining press contact lists, special event support, and conceptualizing social media content. A background in journalism or communications and special skills such as photography, video editing and graphic design a plus, but not required. Undergraduate and graduate students, as well as recent graduates, are encouraged to apply. Michigan ties are a plus. Start and end dates are flexible. This internship is unpaid, but the office will accommodate applicants seeking to earn academic credit. Please submit a one page resume, a short writing sample, and a cover letter that includes date and hours of availability to HouseJudiciaryDems@gmail.com.
The office of Congressman Jim Himes (D-CT-4) is currently seeking full and part time unpaid interns for the fall 2014 semester to work in the Congressman’s Washington, DC office. Responsibilities include, but are not limited to, sorting income constituent correspondence, drafting reply letters on behalf of the Congressman, and giving tours of the U.S. Capitol to constituents.
Successful applicants are strong communicators – i.e., are good writers and speakers – are able to work cooperatively with others, are organized, have a positive attitude and a sense of humor, and are reliable. Applicants should also have working knowledge and curiosity of current events and policy topics, as well as a willingness to perform a variety of tasks and administrative functions. This is an excellent opportunity to learn more about the legislative process and better understand the inner workings of a Congressional office.
Connecticut ties are preferred, but all applicants are encouraged to apply. For any questions or to apply, please contact our internship coordinator at himes.internship@mail.house.gov. All applications should consist of one cover letter, resume, and a brief (1-3 page) writing sample. No phone calls or drop-ins, please.
Illinois Representative John Shimkus is currently accepting applications for Fall semester internship positions in his Washington D.C. office. This unpaid internship is available on either a full-time or
  MEM-307-14
 MEM-306-14
Page 5 of 13

 MEM-305-14
part-time basis. Qualified candidates will be highly organized, prompt, responsible, and ready to work in a fast paced environment. Strong oral and communication skills are a must. Daily responsibilities will include, but are not limited to, assisting staff, answering phones, organizing mail, giving tours of the Capitol Building, and attending hearings and briefings for legislative staff. Interns will gain valuable Capitol Hill experience and further their understanding of the legislative process. Illinois ties are preferred but not necessary. All interested applicants should e-mail their resume and cover letter to midwestinternship@gmail.com
The Office of Congressman McClintock (CA-04) is seeking immediate fall interns for his Washington, D.C. office. Applicants should possess conservative values, as well as strong written and verbal communication skills. Interns will gain first-hand experience in the operation and management of a Congressional office. Internship duties include attending Congressional hearings, leading U.S. Capitol tours, answering phones, managing constituent mail database, drafting constituent correspondence, and assisting legislative staff with research.
Those with ties to California are encouraged to apply. Interested applicants should send their resume, availability, and a brief cover letter summarizing their interest in working for Congressman McClintock to Rachel.Long@mail.house.gov. Please use “2014 Fall Internship” in the subject line. No phone calls, drop-ins, or faxes please.
The office of Congressman Ron Barber of Arizona seeks qualified interns for our fall internship program. Interns can expect to gain exposure to the day-to-day activities of Congress while playing an active role in the daily work of a Congressional office. Congressman Barber’s district deals extensively with border and immigration issues, alternative energy, scientific research, and national security. Interns can expect experience dealing with a wide variety of issues of critical importance to the nation.
Our internship program places interns in roles with significant responsibility, so we seek only those looking to gain meaningful experience. Responsibilities include assisting with constituent communications, leading Capitol tours, general administrative duties and assisting with special projects. Prospective applicants should be personable, self-starters, quick-learning and eager to take an active role in the workings of a Congressional office.
Internships are unpaid, but arrangements can be made with your school for academic credit. Both part-time and full-time internships are
 MEM-304-14
Page 6 of 13

 MEM-303-14
available, but preference will be given to those who can dedicate at least 25 hours per week.
Interested applicants should send a cover letter and resume to az.house.internship@gmail.com. Individuals with Arizona ties are strongly encouraged to apply. No calls please.
Fall Press Intern - NY Democrat is seeking press and social media interns for the Fall of 2014 in his Washington, D.C.
office. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to, compiling press clips, monitoring daily news, drafting talking points and press releases, managing social media outlets and working closely with senior staff. The ideal candidate will possess meticulous editing skills, expertise in new social media platforms, an ability to work in a fast- paced environment, professionalism and a good sense of humor. Please note that the internship is unpaid and housing is not provided, but students can qualify for academic credit depending on the requirements of the college or university. Interested applicants should e-mail a cover letter, resume, short writing sample (in the form of a speech or press release), and dates of availability with "Press Intern Fall 2014" in the subject line to NY.PressIntern@mail.house.gov. Equal opportunity employer. No phone calls or drop-ins please.
The Office of Congresswoman Eddie Bernice Johnson is seeking full- time and part-time unpaid interns for the Fall 2014 semester in the member’s Washington D.C. office. Responsibilities will include assisting the administrative and legislative staff with writing, legislative research, constituent services, and attending various briefings and hearings. Candidates should be self-motivated, detail oriented and possess strong oral and written communication skills. This is an excellent opportunity to gain experience on Capitol Hill while learning about the legislative process. Texas ties are preferred, but not required. If you are interested in this internship opportunity, please e-mail a cover letter, resume, references and a writing sample to DCintern.tx30@gmail.com. Please no phone calls or walk-ins.
The office of Congressman Albio Sires (NJ-08) seeks motivated, well- organized interns for our Washington, DC office on a full or part-time basis for the fall semester. Excellent writing and communication skills as well as good judgment are essential. Duties will include assisting staff with correspondence and research, attending hearings and briefings, greeting guests, answering phones & other duties as
needed. If you are interested, please fax a cover letter, resume, and writing sample to 202-226-0792.
The House’s most unique and courageous conservative seeks smart, happy interns (of all ages and backgrounds) for the remainder of the
 MEM-302-14
 MEM-301-14
MEM-300-14
Page 7 of 13

 MEM-299-14
year. Alas, we cannot pay you. Schedules and start/end dates are negotiable if you’re worth it. We do not insist on specific, arbitrary submissions: send us whatever personal materials you think will give us reason to hire you, even if that’s just a standard boring resume and canned cover letter. Writing samples are encouraged, but not required, because even a short cover letter belies and betrays a lousy writer. Brevity is the soul of wit.
This Member is not a jerk, and neither loathes nor avoids interns, but loves them, and actually speaks to them. If you are selected for this internship you will have extraordinary access to the Member and to meaningful projects that go well beyond the standard intern grunt work (or your money back).
Personality and ideology are important. Please bring a confident, vigorous intellect and no drama. Ideal candidates will be true patriots who can count up to 17 in trillions, and care more about future generations than they do about sucking up to current leadership. Mushy pleasers/appeasers keep walkin’. HINT: vapid granolas who fear guns, hate babies, are ashamed of America, and think Islamic terrorists and illegal aliens are just misunderstood will not be comfortable here. Reply to: kim.tape@mail.house.gov.
Congresswoman Candice S. Miller (R-MI) seeks legislative interns for the Fall 2014 (September-December) semester. Interns will work in a fast-paced congressional office, gaining valuable exposure and knowledge of the legislative process and the United States Congress. Intern responsibilities include greeting constituents, managing constituent phone calls, and assisting staff with administrative tasks. Interns will also have the opportunity to conduct legislative research, assist with constituent correspondence, and attend legislative briefings, congressional hearings, receptions, and press events.
Interns must have a good attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Successful interns will be able to find information with little assistance, be able to work both independently as well as part of a team environment, and possess a strong attention to detail. Applicants should have working knowledge of current events and policy topics, as well as a willingness to perform a variety of tasks and administrative functions. Michigan ties are strongly preferred; however, candidates from outside the state will be considered. Undergraduate students are strongly encouraged to
apply. To apply, please send cover letter and resume to MI10Intern@gmail.com .
The Office of Congresswoman Eleanor Holmes Norton (D-DC) is Page 8 of 13
 MEM-298-14

 MEM-297-14
seeking a full-time or part-time Press and Social Media intern for the fall of 2014. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to compiling press clips, monitoring daily news, drafting talking points and press releases, updating social media and working closely with the communications director. The ideal candidate will have previous experience in public relations or journalism, possess strong written communications skills, ability to work in a fast-paced environment, and professional manner. Please note that the internship is unpaid and housing is not provided, but student can qualify for
academic credit depending on the requirements of the college or university. Interested applicants should e-mail a cover letter, resume, short writing sample (in the form of a speech or press release) and dates of availability with "Norton Internship" in the subject line to Jason.spear@mail.house.gov. No phone calls or drop-ins please.
The Office of Congresswoman Eleanor Holmes Norton (D-DC) is seeking a full-time or part-time intern for the fall of 2014. This is an opportunity to learn about the inner-workings of a congressional office on the Hill in a fast-paced work environment. The internship allows access to briefings and interesting events related to a wide range of important issues. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to, attending Congressional briefings, giving tours of the Capitol, conducting research, responding to constituent inquiries, and processing tour and flag requests. Qualified applicants should possess a professional and courteous demeanor, excellent communication skills, the ability to multi-task, fastidious attention to detail, and interest in the legislative and governmental process. To apply, please send a resume, contact information for three references, writing sample, and cover letter to Jason.spear@mail.house.gov, with the subject Norton Internship. No phone calls or drop-ins please.
Nevada Congressman Steven Horsford is seeking current college students or recent college graduates wishing to gain Capitol Hill experience for a full-time or part-time semester internship to begin in August and/or September 2014.
We are seeking motivated, organized, and reliable individuals to assist the legislative and administrative staff with day-to-day duties. Such duties include assisting the legislative and communications staff, attending briefings and hearings, answering phones, drafting constituent correspondence letters, doing legislative research and various other tasks. The internship is unpaid, though interns will gain valuable Hill and office experience and will have access to many unique Hill opportunities. Nevada and District 4 ties are preferred, but not necessary.
 MEM-294-14
Page 9 of 13

 MEM-292-14
Please send a resume and cover letter
to NV04Internships@mail.house.gov. Your application should include your anticipated start date and availability. Please no drop bys or phone calls.
Congressman Dan Kildee’s Washington, D.C. office is always seeking motivated and hard-working college students for fall internships. Although internships are unpaid, students will gain valuable work experience in a fast-paced congressional office.
QUALIFICATIONS: Applicants must be highly motivated, have excellent oral and written communications skills, responsible, dependable, and eager to learn.
JOB DESCRIPTION: Interns are expected to carry out any task assigned to them. Tasks include and are not limited to the following: Researching legislative issues, preparing constituent correspondence, data entry, and helping maintain the efficient day-to-day operations of an active Congressional office.
If interested, please send a resume and letters of recommendation to Ghada Alkiek at ghada.alkiek@mail.house.gov
For more information on Congressman Dan Kildee and Michigan’s 5th Congressional District, please visit our website at www.dankildee.house.gov
New York Congressman Jerrold Nadler (D-NY) is seeking unpaid Interns for the fall semester, preferably to begin in late August and finish in December. Interns will:
 Assist with office administrative tasks including, sorting incoming mail, greeting visitors, and answering the telephone.
 Assist in the preparation of constituent responses, bills, and amendments.
 Perform legislative research.
 Respond to requests from constituents.
 Attend briefings, hearings, and special events where they may
have the opportunity to meet with Members of Congress,
leaders of industry, and the press.
 Gain valuable Hill experience and learn about the federal
legislative process.
Currently, Congressman Jerrold Nadler represents New York's 10th Congressional District, which includes the residents of most of the Upper West Side, Lower Manhattan and sections of
  MEM-291-14
Page 10 of 13

 MEM-290-14
Brooklyn. Congressman Nadler serves on the Judiciary Committee and on the Transportation and Infrastructure Committee, where he is the highest ranking member from New York. He is the Ranking member of The Subcommittee on Courts, Intellectual Property, and the Internet.
Applicant Instructions:
Please e-mail or fax a resume, brief cover letter, and 1-2 page writing sample to:
Email: Gabriella.Libby@mail.house.gov Fax: 202-225-6923.
Congressional Black Caucus Internship- Fall 2014 - The Congressional Black Caucus is accepting applications for internship positions available for fall 2014. This unpaid internship will provide valuable hands on experience in developing and executing initiatives for a Congressional Caucus and will provide an understanding the Caucus’s role in the legislative process. This is an excellent opportunity for college students and recent graduates seeking Capitol Hill experience. All majors are encouraged to apply. Interested applicants should e-mail a resume, cover letter, and writing sample to Charlyn.Stanberry@mail.house.gov with “Fall 2014 Internship” in the subject. Please also include dates of availability.
Fall Legal Fellow - Energetic NY Freshman Democrat is seeking a highly motivated Legislative Fellow to assist with a number of issues, including criminal justice, intellectual property, and financial
services. Responsibilities include analyzing policy issues, drafting memos, researching policy positions, and assisting extremely active legislative staff as needed. The ideal candidate should possess strong communication skills, attention to detail, and the ability to operate in a fast-paced environment. Candidates with New York ties and previous internship/work experience are strongly encouraged to apply. This fellowship is unpaid but is eligible for school credit where
applicable. Please e-mail a resume, cover letter, and a writing sample to NY.ResumeInbox@mail.house.gov with “Legal Fellowship” in the subject line. Equal opportunity employer. No calls or walk-ins please.
The office of Congresswoman Diana DeGette (CO-01) is seeking applications for internships during the Fall. As a fast-paced office for an active member of the Democratic leadership, we expect a lot from our interns and pride ourselves on an excellent internship program. Duties include, but are not limited to, answering phones, sorting mail, attending briefings, drafting constituent correspondence, and providing assistance to the legislative staff. Applicants must have excellent writing and communications skills. Interested applicants should email a cover letter, resume, and brief writing sample (2-3
 MEM-289-14
 MEM-288-14
Page 11 of 13

 MEM-287-14
pages) to tom.gibson@mail.house.gov with the subject line “Intern Application.”
The Washington, DC office of Congressman Peter DeFazio (OR-04) seeks highly motivated interns, full time or part time, for Fall 2014. Successful candidates will demonstrate that they are organized, detail- oriented, and professional. Strong written and oral communication skills are essential.
Intern responsibilities will include but are not limited to assisting staff with legislative, administrative, constituent relations, and press activities. Interns will: answer phones; sort, distribute, and respond to constituent mail; lead tours of the US Capitol building; attend hearings and briefings; and assist with legislative research.
Please send a resume, cover letter, and brief writing sample to matt.leasure@mail.house.gov. Candidates with Oregon ties are strongly encouraged to apply. No phone calls or drop-ins, please.
A Democratic California Congressman is seeking highly motivated interns to join his Washington, DC office for a part or full time unpaid internship for the autumn term (September-December). Candidates should be organized, professional, quick learners, and team players. Strong oral and written communication skills and close attention to detail are important. Main responsibilities include but are not limited to assisting staff with legislative, administrative, and press related projects, writing memos and talking points, attending hearings and meetings, answering constituent phone calls, leading tours of the US Capitol, assisting with scheduling, sorting and distributing mail, and managing tour and flag requests. Candidates with California ties and previous internship/work experience are strongly encouraged to apply. Please e-mail a resume and cover letter to Intern.Resume@mail.house.gov.
Fall Intern – The Office of Congressman David Price (NC-04) is seeking qualified candidates to intern in our Washington, D.C. office for the fall semester (September through the end of November.) This unpaid internship will provide valuable hands-on experience in a Congressional office and a greater understanding of the legislative process. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to: attending Congressional briefings, conducting research for staffers, responding to constituent inquiries, operating the phones, sorting the mail, and giving tours of the Capitol.
The internship program is open to college undergraduates, regardless of major, who are attending a DC-area college or who are participating in
 MEM-271-14
 MEM-259-14
Page 12 of 13

 MEM-223-14
a semester program in Washington sponsored by a college or university. NC ties are required. Please fill out the application and follow the submitting instructions at http://price.house.gov/internships/.
Congressman Jerry McNerney (CA-09) is currently accepting applications for Fall semester internship positions in his Washington D.C. office. This unpaid internship will provide valuable hands-on experience in a Congressional office and a greater understanding of the legislative process. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to, attending Congressional briefings, giving tours of the Capitol, conducting research, responding to constituent inquiries, and processing tour and flag requests. Qualified applicants should possess a professional and courteous demeanor, excellent communication skills, the ability to multi-task, fastidious attention to detail, and interest in the legislative and governmental process.
This is an excellent opportunity for college students and recent graduates seeking Capitol Hill experience. All majors are encouraged to apply. Ties to California’s Ninth Congressional District are preferred, but not required. Interested applicants should email a resume and cover letter to nick.sullivan@mail.house.gov with “CA-09 Internship” in the subject line. Include dates of availability.
 Page 13 of 13
