 ________________________________________________________________________
House Vacancy Announcement and Placement Service (HVAPS)
B-235 Longworth House Office Building Washington, D.C. 20515 202-226-5836
Vacancy Bulletins are available for pick-up in
Longworth HOB - B-227 (CAO First Call Customer Service Center) or in the CAO Human Resources Office - Ford HOB 102
To Subscribe or Unsubscribe to the Vacancy Listserv visit:
http://www.house.gov/content/jobs/
Job Line: 202-226-4504 _____________________________________________________________________________
 MEM-307-15
INTERNSHIP VACANCY LISTING
Week of September 28, 2015
The Washington, DC office of Congressman Peter DeFazio (OR-04) seeks highly motivated interns, full time or part time, for Fall 2015. Successful candidates will demonstrate that they are organized, detail-oriented, and professional.
Strong written and oral communication skills are essential.
Intern responsibilities will include but are not limited to assisting staff with legislative, administrative, constituent relations, and press activities. Interns will: answer phones; sort, distribute, and respond to constituent mail; lead tours of the US Capitol building; attend hearings and briefings; and assist with legislative research. Internships are unpaid, but arrangements may be made to earn academic credit.
To apply, please send a resume, cover letter, and brief writing sample to OR04.InternCoordinator@mail.house.gov.
Candidates with Oregon ties are strongly encouraged to apply.
No phone calls or drop-ins, please.
Democratic Congressman Mike Honda is seeking interns for the fall.
 MEM-306-15
Page 1 of 26

 MEM-305-15
Interns will:
- Assist with office administrative tasks including, sorting incoming mail,
greeting visitors, and answering the telephone.
- Assist in the preparation of letters to constituents.
- Perform legislative research.
- Respond to requests from constituents.
- Attend briefings, hearings, and special events.
- Sit in on meetings with stakeholders.
- Gain valuable Hill experience and learn about the legislative process.
Candidates with full-time availability are highly preferred. Additionally, ties to the Bay Area and additional languages are preferred.
Congressman Mike Honda represents California’s 17th Congressional District, which includes much of Silicon Valley. He serves on the prestigious Appropriations Committee’s subcommittees on Commerce, Justice, and Science and on Energy and Water. He is a champion of progressive ideals has a strong focus on education, civil rights, and science and technology policy.
Applicants should email a resume and cover letter to: bayareademocrat@gmail.com.
The Office of Congressman Trent Franks (R-AZ) seeks Fall 2015 interns for his Washington D.C. office. Candidates should be energetic, hard-working, eager to learn, and able to work in a fast-paced environment.
Interns will be responsible for answering phones, speaking with constituents about legislative affairs, scheduling and giving Capitol tours, attending briefings, and supporting the legislative staff. Other responsibilities may include editing or writing briefs, doing research on current legislation, planning events on the Hill, and responding to constituent mail.
Interested candidates should email a current resume to Chelsea.Patterson@mail.house.gov.
Congressman Benishek from Michigan’s First District seeks unpaid interns to fill positions for January through May 2016. Main responsibilities include answering phones, processing mail, drafting constituent correspondence letters, researching legislative issues, and attending meetings/hearings as needed. There will also be opportunities to attend receptions and seminars of interest. Candidates should be self-motivated, enthusiastic, flexible, and computer-literate (with a good understanding of MS Office). This is a great opportunity for college students seeking academic credit. Michigan ties are preferred.
Please e-mail your cover letter, resume, and references to Samuel Grossman at samuel.grossman@mail.house.gov.
 MEM-304-15
 Page 2 of 26

MEM-301-15
Louisiana Republican seeks full and part time intern(s) to start immediately in Washington, DC office. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to, greeting constituents, answering phone calls, opening and sorting mail, scheduling and guiding US Capitol Building tours, and assisting staff with administrative tasks. Interns are also provided the opportunity to conduct legislative research and attend briefings, hearing, and press events.
Ideal candidate will have excellent written and verbal communication skills, strong work ethic, ability to multi-task, and a positive attitude.
Southern ties preferred, but not necessary.
Those interested please send resumes to Ann.Pierce@mail.house.gov with “Intern Application” in the subject line.
The Washington, DC, office of a high profile Member of Congress has unpaid Press internship openings to begin immediately until end of the year.
Press interns are expected to work long hours and commit between 3-5 days per week. Internship duties include, but are not limited to compiling and daily clips, drafting press releases and op-eds, proofreading and editing, maintaining press lists, updating Member's communications calendar, website and social media platforms. Intern may also assist with answering phones, incoming and outgoing mail, addressing constituent concerns, and assisting the Legislative/District office staff. Strong writing skills are needed and familiarity with new media and website development is a plus. Priority will be given to those with journalism or communications education/experience.
The ideal candidate will be creative, motivated, mature, detail-orientated, and possess the ability to multi-task under high pressure. This is a great opportunity for college students and recent graduates. Women and minorities, especially those with Spanish language fluency, are highly encouraged to apply.
To apply for the position, please send your cover letter, resume and writing sample addressed to the Comm. Director at ny13intern@gmail.com with the subject: Press Intern.
Congressman Himes’ Washington D.C. office (CT-04) seeks motivated interns available to start immediately. Potential interns should be able to work independently, have good communication skills, and have an interest in the legislative process. Tasks will include fielding constituent inquiries, drafting memos and letters, attending briefings, leading tours of the capitol and helping with administrative tasks. Interns will also have the opportunity to learn more about and focus on their issues of interest, through letter-writing and briefings.
Interns will work closely with the Staff Assistant, Legislative Correspondent, Legislative Assistants, and Scheduler on day-to day tasks and special projects.
 MEM-291-15
 MEM-290-15
Page 3 of 26

 MEM-289-15
Connecticut ties and full time availability preferred but not required. Interested parties should submit a cover letter, resume, and writing sample to
Kamilah.Tisdale@mail.house.gov.
The office of a New York Congressman seeks an unpaid full-time press intern with exceptional writing and editing skills. Duties will include: authoring interesting and creative content for the website on various topics and other tasks as assigned. The intern must be highly motivated and have excellent writing and communication skills.
All interested and qualified candidates should email a resume and two writing samples. Please submit all inquiries with the subject “Press Internship” to: NY .ResumeInbox@mail.house.gov.
Southern Republican is seeking interns for the Fall 2015 semester to join the Washington, DC office. Ideal candidates will have excellent written and verbal communication skills as this position involves significant constituent interaction. Applicants must be detail oriented, professional, and highly organized. Responsibilities include scheduling and conducting Capitol tours, processing constituent mail, answering phones, conducting general administrative tasks, and supporting policy staff with various projects.
Interested applicants may send a resume and cover letter to eliza.thurston@mail.house.gov.
Congressman Tim Walz (MN-01) is seeking prospective interns available to start immediately. Applicants should be highly-motivated, well-organized and eager to assist with the legislative, communications and administrative needs of the office. Such duties include, but are not limited to, attending briefings, answering phones, drafting constituent response letters, conducting research, giving tours of the Capitol and various other administrative tasks. Applicants should possess an interest in the legislative process, as well as strong written and verbal communications skills. Minnesota ties are a plus, but not required.
Applications accepted for both full and part-time positions (min. 20 hours per week). This is an unpaid position.
To be considered, please send a resume, cover letter and at least three (3) references ASAP to: alyssa.berg@mail.house.gov.
Midwest Republican is currently seeking interns in his Washington, D.C. office for fall 2015 (September-December). Interns perform a variety of responsibilities, including answering phones, receiving guests, and providing tours of the Capitol Building. They will also research legislation for the legislative staff, attend hearings and briefings, and answer constituent letters on
 MEM-288-15
 MEM-287-15
 MEM-286-15
Page 4 of 26

 MEM-283-15
various issues before the House. Interns should possess strong research, writing, analytical, and interpersonal skills. Moreover, candidates should express an interest in politics and conservative values.
All internships are unpaid. However, if your college or university offers credit hours we are happy to complete any necessary evaluations.
Interested candidates should email their resume and cover letter to MOCongressionalInternship@gmail.com.
Congressman John Carney (DE-At-Large) is seeking full-time and part-time unpaid interns starting immediately. Interns will gain exposure to the activities of a Capitol Hill office and develop meaningful relationships with members of the staff. Duties include responding to constituent mail and phone calls, leading U.S. Capitol tours, performing legislative research, compiling press clips, and helping with other office tasks. No minimum time commitment is required, though preference will be given to applicants who can work at least 15 hours a week. The office offers flexibility for those seeking full-time employment who may need to leave the office during the day for interviews or networking activities.
Interested applicants should send a cover letter and resume to carney.scheduling@mail.house.gov.
Intern needed to start immediately. Stipend available. Please indicate any connections to Minnesota in your cover letter's first paragraph.
We are seeking energetic and proficient interns in the Washington, D.C. office of Congresswoman Betty McCollum (MN04). An internship in Congresswoman McCollum’s office will provide valuable experience to students as they prepare for their professional careers. Interns have the opportunity to work with and assist all members of the staff, including legislative, administrative, outreach and press duties. Washington, DC interns will be encouraged to take advantage of the many hearings, workshops and seminars that are held on Capitol Hill.
In addition, we are happy to work with your college or university to arrange for academic credit. Applicants should be highly motivated and enthusiastic, as there are far more applicants than available positions.
Minnesota ties are strongly preferred.
Responsibilities include:
• Supporting administrative staff: answering phones, database entry, and sorting mail.
• Supporting legislative staff: tracking constituent correspondence, drafting letters, and conducting light research.
 MEM-282-15
Page 5 of 26

 MEM-281-15
• Attending briefings and hearings for legislative staff.
• Compiling news clips.
• Promoting constituent outreach efforts by communicating with constituents and constituent groups, attending meetings and events, and drafting correspondence.
Hours:
• Internships are available year‐round.
• They are available on a part‐time or full‐time basis. Minimum 25 hours a week. • Transportation and housing are the responsibility of interns.
Application process:
Applicants should send a cover letter, available hours and a resume.
Those interested in a Washington, DC internship should email scheduler_mn04dc@mail.house.gov.
Please indicate any Minnesota ties in the first paragraph of your cover letter.
Ohio Democrat is seeking interns for the fall 2015 semester. Interns will work in a fast-paced Congressional Office, gaining valuable exposure and knowledge of the legislative process and the United States Congress. Interns will have the opportunity to conduct legislative research, assist with correspondence, as well as attend some Capitol Hill briefings, congressional hearings, and press events. Responsibilities will include handling constituent phone calls, opening and sorting mail, giving Capitol Tours, and assisting staff with administrative tasks. This internship is unpaid.
Qualifications: Interns must have a pleasant attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Successful interns will be able to find information with little assistance, be able to work both independently as well as part of a team, and have strong attention to detail.
9th District Ohio ties a plus!
Please email Courtney.hruska@Mail.house.gov with cover letter and resume. Availability must be in cover letter.
Midwest Democrat is seeking interns for the fall 2015 semester.
Interns will work in a fast-paced Congressional Office, gaining valuable exposure and knowledge of the legislative process and the United States Congress.
Interns will have the opportunity to conduct legislative research, assist with correspondence, as well as attend some Capitol Hill briefings, congressional hearings, and press events. Intern responsibilities will also include greeting constituents, handling constituent phone calls, opening and sorting mail, giving Capitol Tours, and assisting staff with administrative tasks.
This internship is unpaid.
 MEM-280-15
Page 6 of 26

 MEM-279-15
Qualifications:
Interns must have a good attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Successful interns will be able to find information with little assistance, be able to work both independently as well as part of a team, and have strong attention to detail. Applicants should have working knowledge of current events and policy topics, as well as an interest in American Government, fiscal issues, education and reproductive rights.
Wisconsin ties a plus.
Requirements:
Interns must be able to commit to at least two full days per week (9:00 am-6:00 pm).
Please submit resume and 2 one page writing samples to Nairobi.cratic@mail.house.gov by September 18, 2015.
Congressman French Hill (AR-02) has available full-time and part-time, unpaid internships for the 2015 Fall and 2015 Winter semesters in his Washington, D.C. office beginning immediately. Interns will work in a fast-paced Capitol Hill office, gaining valuable exposure and knowledge of the legislative process and the U.S. Congress. Intern responsibilities include greeting constituents, answering constituent phone calls, opening and sorting mail, guiding U.S. Capitol building tours, and assisting staff with administrative tasks. Interns also will have the opportunity to conduct legislative research and assist with correspondence, as well as attend Capitol Hill briefings, congressional hearings, and press events.
Interns will have a positive attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Social media and other communications experience a plus. Successful interns will be self-starters, take and listen to direction, and be able to work both independently and as part of a team. Applicants should have working knowledge of current events and policy topics as well as a willingness to assist with daily office tasks. Arkansas ties strongly preferred.
Those interested please send resume and cover letter to ar02.applications@mail.house.gov.
Congresswoman Mimi Walters (CA-45), a Republican freshman member who holds a GOP leadership positon, seeks part-time interns to start immediately in her DC office. Responsibilities will include but are not limited to administrative duties, legislative research, helping with mail, assisting with tours and other constituent services.
Preference is for an individual who can work part-time from now through December. California ties are preferred, but not necessary.
 MEM-278-15
Page 7 of 26

 MEM-277-15
If interested please send a resume and a brief cover letter to InternshipsCA45@gmail.com with “Internship Application” in the subject line.
Congressman Jim Renacci (R-OH) seeks part time/full time hard working intern for fall 2015. Responsibilities include, but aren’t limited to, answering phone calls, assisting with the mail program, providing constituent tours, attending various briefings, and providing research for the legislative staff.
Qualified candidates will have exceptional writing skills, strong communication skills, ability to work in a fast paced working environment, and have an interest in learning more about the legislative process.
Send a resume and a cover letter to Stephen.Hostelley@mail.house.gov. Ohio candidates are strongly preferred.
  Northeastern House Democrat seeks a full-time intern to start immediately in Washington, D.C. office. Duties will include drafting constituent correspondence, sorting mail, answering telephones, attending legislative briefings, assisting the legislative staff with research, and other tasks as assigned. Ideal candidates will have strong written and verbal communications skills, the ability to multi-task, and a positive attitude.
Please email cover letter, resume, and availability to housedeminterns@gmail.com.
 MEM-275-15
MEM-274-15
The Committee on Education and the Workforce, Democratic Staff is currently seeking undergraduate interns for Fall 2015. Interns perform a variety of tasks that support the staff in our legislative and media work. Legislative tasks may include, but are not limited to, legislative research, assembling information, assisting staff during hearing and markup preparation and execution, and attending hearings, markups, briefings and meetings. Media work may include assisting staff to organize and staff Committee press conferences and assisting with the production of daily news clips relating to Committee’s
issues. Undergraduate Interns are also trained to perform administrative duties, such as answering phones, and sorting and distributing mail.
Applicants should be able to start in September and commit through mid- December.
Interested applicants should email their cover letter and resume to jobs_ewdems@mail.house.gov. Please visit our website at http://democrats.edworkforce.house.gov/about/internships for more information.
The office of Congressman Jeff Fortenberry (NE-01) is seeking full and part-time interns for the fall semester in its DC office. Interns engage in a variety of tasks, and their responsibilities are assigned based on interests, capabilities, and the
  MEM-272-15
Page 8 of 26

 MEM-271-15
needs of the office. Interns will have the opportunity to hone their legislative research and writing skills and interact with senior legislative staff; attend hearings and briefings on Capitol Hill; assist with media/communications tasks and gain proficiency in IQ; and participate in our office’s top priority, constituent outreach, by leading tours, greeting visitors, and answering phones. Exceptional interns in the past have gotten opportunities to write constituent letters and contribute to constituent and staff meetings on and around Capitol Hill.
If you are interested in applying for one of the most robust internship programs on the Hill, please submit a cover letter including the reason you would like an internship in Congressman Fortenberry’s office, your résumé, two writing samples, and references to NE01internships@gmail.com.
The Office of Congressman Paul D. Tonko offers unpaid internship opportunities for students and recent college graduates seeking to gain a better understanding of the legislative process. Interns in our office are offered a comprehensive learning opportunity that goes above and beyond a normal internship on Capitol Hill.
Part of an intern’s responsibilities in our office are fairly typical, including answering phones and helping with our mail program. However, they are also offered the opportunity to research and draft constituent correspondences on a wide variety of issues, provide Capitol tours to constituents, attend briefings both for staffers and for their own learning purposes, and assist with research for legislative staff members.
Every intern plays a critical role in the day-to-day operation of the office, and staff members do everything they can to ensure they receive a beneficial and rewarding experience here in our office.
Ideally looking for an intern who can start immediately or in early September and can intern at least 3 full days a week. Full-time preferred.
If you have any questions regarding our internship program, please do not hesitate to contact James Johnson by email at: james.johnson@mail.house.gov or by phone at (202) 225-5076.
The office of a New York Congressman seeks an unpaid press intern with exceptional writing and editing skills. Duties will include: authoring interesting and creative content for the website on various topics and other tasks as assigned. The intern must be highly motivated and have excellent writing and communication skills. All interested and qualified candidates should email a resume and two writing samples.
Please submit all inquiries with the subject “Press Internship” to: NY .ResumeInbox@mail.house.gov.
 MEM-270-15
 Page 9 of 26

MEM-269-15
Energetic New York Democrat is seeking a highly motivated legislative intern to join his Washington, DC office for a part time unpaid internship this
fall. Candidates should possess a professional and courteous demeanor, interest in the legislative process, excellent communication skills, the ability to multi- task, attention to detail, and a sense of humor.
Main responsibilities include, but are not limited to, attending Congressional briefings and hearings, responding to constituent correspondence, drafting policy memos, and general office duties. Candidates with New York ties and previous internship/work experience are strongly encouraged to apply.
Please e-mail a resume, cover letter, and a short writing sample to NY.ResumeInbox@mail.house.gov. Equal opportunity employer. No calls or walk-ins please.
Arizona Republican is seeking fall semester interns for his Washington D.C. office. Duties of interns include answering telephones, greeting visitors, conducting tours, sorting mail, and assisting staff members with projects as needed. Applicants should be organized, should have strong time management and writing skills, and should be able to complete tasks with minimal supervision. Arizona ties and previous Hill experience a plus but not required.
Please send a cover letter, one-page resume, and a two- to three-page writing sample to GOPinternshipAZ@gmail.com with “Internship Application” in the subject line. No phone calls please.
The office of Congresswoman Jackie Walorski (IN-02) is seeking a full-time communications intern for her Washington D.C. office for Spring of 2016.
Ideal candidate must possess strong writing skills, be detail-oriented and professional. Intern will work directly with the communications director and members of the media.
Responsibilities would include writing releases, monitoring social media and developing media strategies. Position is unpaid and serves to provide professional and educational value to participants.
Office is flexible in allowing interns to attend hearings and briefings as well as work with LA’s on issues of their interest. Potential applicants must be willing to work in a fast-paced environment and be interested in learning more about the legislative process. Candidates with photography and graphic design experience strongly encouraged to apply.
Please send resume and cover letter to internship.in02@gmail.com. No phone calls, please.
 MEM-268-15
 MEM-267-15
 Page 10 of 26

MEM-266-15
The office of Congresswoman Jackie Walorski (IN-02) is seeking full-time interns for her Washington D.C. office for Spring of 2016.
Ideal candidate would be professional, dependable and possess a strong writing skills and work ethic. Responsibilities include phone assistance, constituent correspondence, Capitol tours and other legislative projects. Positions are unpaid and serve to provide professional and educational value to participants.
Office is flexible in allowing interns to attend hearings and briefings as well as work with LA’s on issues of their interest. Candidates must be willing to work in a fast-paced environment and be interested in learning more about the legislative process.
Please send resume and cover letter to internship.in02@gmail.com. No phone calls, please.
The Office of Congresswoman Tulsi Gabbard (HI-02) is seeking a full- or part- time national security intern for Fall 2015. This is an unpaid position in the Congresswoman’s Washington, D.C. office.
Candidates should be well-organized, have good oral and written communication skills, and possess a strong interest in learning about the legislative process, homeland security, defense, and intelligence issues. The intern will assist in the day-to-day operations of a D.C. Congressional office by supporting staff members with constituent communication, and will also assist with legislative research and administrative activities.
National security policy experience and Hawaii ties are appreciated but not required. Interested candidates should send a resume and cover letter detailing availability to Christine.Wagner@mail.house.gov with “Fall 2015 Internship Application” in the email subject line. Applications will be considered on a rolling basis. No calls or walk-ins please.
The district offices of Congressman Rod Blum (R IA-01) are seeking candidates for an unpaid internship to assist with day-to-day operations in Cedar Rapids, Dubuque, or Cedar Falls, Iowa. Responsibilities include administrative office duties, researching legislation, planning and attending district events, recording constituent input, and attending meetings throughout the district.
Part-time or full-time positions are available.
The ideal candidate will be professional, responsible, have strong writing skills, and above all, be dedicated to upholding the principles of the Constitution.
Interested applicants should send their resume and cover letter, including desired office placement, to: Alexah.Rogge@mail.house.gov.
The Office of Congresswoman Ann McLane Kuster (NH-02) is seeking qualified Page 11 of 26
 MEM-260-15
 MEM-259-15
 MEM-258-15

 MEM-257-15
candidates to intern full time and part time in our Washington, D.C. office. Interns will have a chance to experience first-hand the operations of a U.S. Congressional office, learn about the legislative process, and gain Capitol Hill experience.
Responsibilities include administrative tasks such as answering phones, welcoming guests, and leading constituent tours.
In addition, interns will be required to conduct legislative research, draft constituent correspondence and vote recommendations, attend briefings and hearings and other projects as needed.
Candidates should have excellent writing and communication skills, strong organizational abilities, a good work ethic, an ability to work independently, and a drive to take initiative. Candidates with ties to the Northeast—especially New Hampshire—are preferred, but not required.
If candidates have any questions or wish to apply, please send a cover letter, resume, writing sample, and references to NH02.Internship@mail.house.gov. Please include “Last Name, First Name - Internship Application” in the subject line and include your available start and end dates and weekly schedule in the email.
The Office of Congressman Curt Clawson (R-FL) is seeking full-time and part- time interns for the 2015 fall semester (August – December) in its Washington, D.C. location.
The ideal candidate will have excellent research and writing skills, be able to multi-task, and interact well with constituents. Interns will have the opportunity to gain experience working on Capitol Hill, learn about the legislative process, and attend briefings of interest. Responsibilities include answering the phone, guiding tours of the Capitol, assisting with constituent correspondence, and supporting the legislative and communications staff on various projects.
Internships are unpaid, but the office will fill out any necessary forms for students to receive academic credit.
Hours are 8:30 – 5:30 on available days, ideally Monday/Wednesday or Tuesday/Thursday with alternate Fridays.
Please contact Emily.Manning@mail.house.gov with a resume and one-page writing sample to apply.
Senior New Jersey Republican Congressman is seeking interns for his Washington, DC office.
Applications being accepted for Fall semester, and throughout the year. Page 12 of 26
 MEM-256-15

 MEM-252-15
Intern duties will include, but are not limited to: answering constituent letters on various issues, researching legislation for the Member and legislative staff, attending hearings and briefings and answering phones.
Interns will also conduct Capitol tours for visitors.
Interns will learn about the legislative process and the many other functions of a Congressional office.
Candidates must be highly motivated; detail oriented, and possess strong communication and organizational skills, while having a strong work ethic to complete tasks on a deadline.
The internship is unpaid.
Interns can receive college credit based on policy of the educational institution. Flexible work schedules are available, but full days preferred.
Please send resumes and cover letters to Stephen Bradford at NJ05Internship@mail.house.gov.
The Office of Rep. Tom Graves (GA-14) is seeking full and part-time interns for fall 2015 in our Washington, D.C. office. Applicants should possess strong written and verbal communication skills and a strong work ethic.
Intern responsibilities include, but are not limited to, assisting the staff with general office duties, answering phones, responding to constituent mail, researching legislative issues, leading Capitol Hill tours, and attending briefings and hearings.
Interested candidates should send a cover letter and resume to Ryan.Diffley@mail.house.gov, please use the subject “Fall 2015 Intern”.
Congressman Mike Honda represents California’s 17th Congressional District, which includes much of Silicon Valley. He serves on the prestigious Appropriations Committee’s subcommittees on Commerce, Justice, and Science and on Energy and Water. He is a champion of progressive ideals has a strong focus on education, civil rights, and science and technology policy.
Democratic Congressman Mike Honda is seeking interns for the fall. Interns will:
- Assist with office administrative tasks including, sorting incoming mail, greeting visitors, and answering the telephone.
- Assist in the preparation of letters to constituents.
- Perform legislative research.
- Respond to requests from constituents.
- Attend briefings, hearings, and special events.
- Sit in on meetings with stakeholders.
- Gain valuable Hill experience and learn about the legislative process.
 MEM-250-15
Page 13 of 26

 MEM-247-15
Candidates with full-time availability are highly preferred.
Additionally, ties to the Bay Area and additional languages are preferred.
POC for resumes submission: Bayareademocrat@gmail.com.
Congresswoman Diana DeGette (CO-01) seeks undergraduate or graduate students for full-time or part-time unpaid internships in her Washington, DC office. As a fast-paced office for an active member of the Democratic leadership, we expect a lot from our interns and pride ourselves on an excellent internship program. Duties include, but are not limited to, answering phones, sorting mail, attending briefings, drafting constituent correspondence, and providing research assistance to the legislative staff. Qualified candidates will possess excellent writing and communications skills, strong attention to detail, and an interest in the legislative process. Colorado ties preferred but not required.
Interested applicants should send a cover letter, resume, and brief writing sample to CO01.scheduler@mail.house.gov.
West Virginia Republican Congressman is accepting applications for interns for his Washington, D.C. office. Duties will include answering telephones, greeting visitors, conducting tours, processing flag requests and assisting D.C. staff with various projects. Applicants should have excellent organizational skills, time management skills, and writing skills. West Virginia ties are preferred.
Please send a cover letter and resume to WV03Job@gmail.com with “Intern” listed in the subject header. No phone calls or walk-ins please.
Congresswoman Suzan DelBene seeks fall interns for her Washington, D.C. office. Interns will work in a fast-paced and fun congressional office, gaining valuable experience and knowledge of the United States Congress. Intern responsibilities include greeting constituents and handling constituent phone calls, assisting staff with administrative tasks, conducting research, and assisting with constituent correspondence. Additionally, interns will have the opportunity to lead tours of the U.S. Capitol as well as attend hearings and briefings for the legislative staff.
The ideal candidates will possess exceptional written and oral communication skills, a high degree of professionalism, as well as a strong interest in public service. Prospective interns should be able to commit at least 16 hours per week. Washington state ties are a plus, but are not required.
Interested applicants should send a current resume and cover letter to Internship.DelBene@mail.house.gov. No phone calls please.
The Office of Congresswoman Marcia L. Fudge is looking for a motivated unpaid press intern in the Washington, D.C. office. Intern responsibilities include assisting the staff with general office duties, attending briefings and
 MEM-243-15
MEM-242-15
   MEM-241-15
Page 14 of 26

 MEM-240-15
hearings, assisting communications team with research and writing support, compiling news clips, drafting press releases, developing copy for the web, answering phones, sorting mail, and giving Capitol tours.
Applicants must possess strong writing and communication skills, have a positive attitude and be well-organized.
Interested candidates should send a cover letter, resumé, and writing sample to OH11pressjobs@mail.house.gov. Ohio ties preferred, but not required.
The House Committee on Foreign Affairs Subcommittee on Asia and the Pacific seeks interns for the fall and winter 2015 terms.
The subcommittee intern is expected to be motivated and entrepreneurial, have strong written and oral communication skills, be detail-oriented, technically savvy, and perform a variety of tasks. The intern will assist with daily subcommittee operations such as research, database maintenance, fact checking, content editing, and proofreading. The intern will also assist with preparation and execution of subcommittee hearings such as conducting research and analysis, scheduling, and organizing documents for staff and members.
Proactive interns will be able to take advantage of this opportunity by participation in hearings, briefings, and meetings, as well as other opportunities to enhance their knowledge of Asia policy and professional life on Capitol Hill. Interns are expected to demonstrate a high level of professionalism and reliability. All internships are unpaid.
Information about the subcommittee’s membership and recent activities can be found at http://foreignaffairs.house.gov/subcommittees/asia-and-pacific.
Interested candidates should send a resume and a cover letter explaining interest in the subcommittee’s work and qualifications for the position to hfac.asia.internship@gmail.com. Applications will be accepted as late as September 30, but will be considered on a rolling basis.
The Majority Staff of the House Committee on Veterans’ Affairs is seeking a full-time or part-time Communications Intern for the Washington, D.C. office. Responsibilities will include compiling press clips, drafting talking points and press releases, updating the website and working closely with the legislative staff. The ideal candidate will possess strong written communications skills, the ability to work in a fast-paced environment, professionalism and a good sense of humor.
Interested applicants should send your resume, short writing sample and completed application, including essay, found on our website, http://veterans.house.gov/internship-opportunities to Jessica Eggimann at (varinternship@mail.house.gov) with "Press Intern" in the subject line. No phone calls or drop-ins please.
  MEM-239-15
  Page 15 of 26

MEM-238-15
Democratic Congressman seeks applicants for full- or part-time unpaid congressional internship for Fall 2015. Duties will include conducting legislative research, drafting memos, assisting with front office duties, and performing basic administrative tasks. Candidates must exhibit strong writing and communication skills. California residents or strong ties to San Diego are preferred.
Please send a resume, cover letter and writing sample to CA52Internship@mail.house.gov with “Fall Congressional Internship” in the subject line.
Interns based in Washington, D.C. will focus on learning about the legislative process and the federal government by working closely with the legislative, communications and constituent services staff members.
Interested candidates should email their cover letter, resume, a short writing sample and a letter of recommendation to LoebsackInternship@mail.house.gov. Congressman Coffman (R-CO) seeks hard-working, enthusiastic legislative interns for the Fall 2015 semester in his Washington, DC office. Interns are responsible for: giving tours of the U.S. Capitol, answering constituent calls, sorting constituent correspondence, assisting legislative staff with research and writing, processing U.S. flag requests, attending Congressional briefings and hearings, and attending events with the Congressman as necessary.
Applicants should have strong written and oral communication skills, exceptional interpersonal skills, and have demonstrable interest in public policy and government. Attractive applicants will have completed at least 60 credit hours of undergraduate coursework. Those with Colorado ties and professional proficiency in Spanish are encouraged to apply.
Although the internship is unpaid, this is a great way to learn about the legislative process and begin a career on the Hill.
To apply, please send a resume and cover letter to ColoradoRepublican06@gmail.com.
Energetic New York Democrat is seeking a highly motivated legislative intern to join his Washington, DC office for a part time unpaid internship this
Fall. Candidates should possess a professional and courteous demeanor, interest in the legislative process, excellent communication skills, the ability to multi- task, attention to detail, and a sense of humor. Main responsibilities include, but are not limited to, attending Congressional briefings, responding to constituent correspondence, assisting with flag requests, and general office
duties. Candidates with New York ties and previous internship/work experience are strongly encouraged to apply.
Please e-mail a resume, cover letter, and a short writing sample to NY .ResumeInbox@mail.house.gov.
 MEM-236-15
MEM-233-15
  MEM-232-15
 Page 16 of 26

MEM-231-15
Equal opportunity employer. No calls or walk-ins please.
Nevada Republican Congressman is seeking an intern for his Washington, DC office. Applications being accepted for Fall term, and throughout the year. Intern duties will include, but are not limited to answering constituent letters on various issues, researching legislation for the Member and legislative staff, attending hearings and briefings and answering phones. Interns will also learn about the buildings 'on the hill' and conduct tours for visitors.
Interns will learn about the legislative process and the many other functions of a Congressional office. Candidates must be highly motivated; detail oriented, and possess strong communication and organizational skills, while having a strong work ethic to complete tasks on a deadline.
The intern experience can support a college education as well as receive credit through the intern’s college. Flexible work schedules are available and can be discussed. Minimum is 3 full days a week.
Training for all aspects of the intern position will be provided.
Please submit your resume and cover letter to: Deborah.hansen@mail.house.gov.
The Washington, DC office of Congressman Luis V. Gutiérrez is seeking motivated, organized, and reliable individuals to fill internship positions in the fall of 2015. Intern responsibilities include, but are not limited to, answering phones, conducting Capitol Tours, sorting incoming mail, attending briefings, conducting legislative research and performing other administrative tasks.
Successful candidates will possess excellent written and oral communication skills, a strong attentiveness to detail, an ability to work in a fast paced environment, an eagerness to learn about the legislative process, as well as a minimum four day per week availability. Internships are unpaid. Spanish-fluency and Illinois ties are a plus.
Please send a résumé, cover letter, and dates of availability to Julissa.Santoy@mail.house.gov with “Intern” in the subject line.
Congressman Vern Buchanan (R-FL-16) has full-time and part-time, unpaid internships available for the fall session (August - December) in his Washington, DC office. Duties include but are not limited to answering telephones, greeting visitors, conducting tours of the Capitol, researching legislative issues and writing letters. There will also be opportunities to experience Washington DC and attend briefings, classes and hearings.
Qualified candidates should possess excellent organizational and communication skills, should have a positive attitude, and a strong work ethic. Although
 MEM-230-15
 MEM-229-15
Page 17 of 26

 MEM-228-15
internships are unpaid, our office is happy to fill out any necessary forms for students to receive credit at their respective college or university.
All interested individuals should submit a cover letter and resume to jillian.gates@mail.house.gov with “2015 Fall Internship” in the subject line. Include in your cover letter why you would like to intern for Congressman Buchanan’s Washington Office, why you believe you are qualified, and your availability. Potential candidates will be contacted via email.
Democratic Leadership Office seeks highly motivated, part-time or full time interns for Fall 2015. Intern responsibilities include administrative duties and a few legislative duties as necessary. Administrative support includes sorting mail, preparing briefing binders, setting up events, and other special projects as assigned by staff.
The position requires the ability to multitask, strong organizational skills, and a desire to work in a fast-paced environment.
The internship is unpaid, but interns will gain valuable Capitol Hill experience in a Democratic Leadership office.
Please send a resume and cover letter to deminternship@gmail.com. Please no drop bys, phone calls, or emailing staff members.
Congresswoman Chellie Pingree (ME-01) is currently seeking full- or part-time interns for the 2015 fall semester in her Washington, DC office. Interns will assist in the day-to-day operations of a DC Congressional office by supporting members of staff with constituent communication, legislative research, and administrative activities. They will also serve as a tour coordinator and occasionally act as a guide of the United States Capitol to Maine constituents visiting Washington.
Qualified candidates will possess an interest in the legislative process, excellent writing and communication skills, strong attention to detail, and a willingness to learn and take on new tasks.
The internship is unpaid, though interns will be an essential component to the effectiveness of the office and will be considered an integral member of the team. Maine ties are preferred, but not necessary.
Please send a resume, cover letter, and brief writing sample
to evan.johnston@mail.house.gov with the subject line Fall Internship. Applications will be considered on a rolling basis. Please no drop bys or phone calls.
Internships are currently available in Congresswoman Zoe Lofgren’s (CA-19) Washington, D.C. office for the 2015 Fall Semester. Congresswoman Lofgren represents California’s 19th Congressional District, which lies in the heart of
 MEM-226-15
 MEM-225-15
Page 18 of 26

 MEM-224-15
California’s “Silicon Valley”.
Interns have the chance to experience the fast-paced atmosphere of a busy Congressional office and gain invaluable work experience.
This is an excellent opportunity for those interested in the legislative process.
Interns’ responsibilities will vary—in addition to answering phones and running errands around the Capitol, interns will have the opportunity to attend hearings and briefings, research legislation for legislative staff, and answer constituent letters on various issues before the House.
Qualified applicants must possess excellent writing and analytical skills, a demonstrated work ethic, and ability to function in a fast-paced environment. A successful candidate will be motivated, able to multitask, and have the ability to work well under pressure. Full-time internship positions are available beginning August 24, 2015. Internships are unpaid.
California-19 and/or California ties are preferred but not required. Interested applicants should apply through http://lofgren.house.gov.
The Office of Congressman John Ratcliffe (TX-04) is currently seeking interns for the Washington, D.C. office for the Fall 2015 semester. Intern responsibilities include but are not limited to, assisting staff with general office duties, attending hearings/briefings for staff members, answering phones, sorting through mail, drafting response letters, and giving tours of the U.S. Capitol.
Candidates should be highly motivated and have good communication skills.
This position is unpaid, but does offer a great educational experience for anyone with aspirations of working on the Hill. Having Texas ties is a plus.
All interested applicants should send a cover letter and resume to Robert.peters@mail.house.gov.
Moderate Southern Democrat seeks applicants for part-time and full-time unpaid congressional internships in Washington, DC.
Duties will include conducting legislative research, drafting memos and responses to letters from constituents, assisting constituents and visitors to the office, assisting with day-to-day operations at the office, answering phones, leading tours of The US Capitol, running errands and performing basic administrative tasks.
Candidates should possess superior written and verbal communication skills and an interest in learning the intricacies of the legislative process.
Part-time interns will be expected to commit to at least two full day shifts (9:00am to 6:00pm) per week, Monday through Friday.
Ties to Florida are preferred, though not required. Page 19 of 26
 MEM-223-15

 MEM-222-15
Interested parties should submit a resume as well as two professional references to FloridaDemResumeRepository@gmail.com.
Florida Republican seeks an intern for the Fall 2015 semester. Interns will work in a fast-paced Congressional Office, gaining valuable exposure and knowledge of the legislative process and the United States Congress.
Intern responsibilities include greeting constituents, handling constituent phone calls, opening and sorting mail, and assisting staff with administrative tasks. Interns will also have the opportunity to conduct legislative research, as well as attend Capitol Hill briefings, congressional hearings and receptions.
Our office is looking for an intern with a positive attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills.
Successful interns will be self-starters, take and listen to direction, and be willing to work both independently as well as part of a team.
Applicants should have a willingness to assist with daily office tasks.
Florida ties preferred, but not required. Interns must be able to commit three full days a week (9:00am-6:00pm during Session and 9:00am-5:00pm during Congressional Recess) at minimum. Students welcome to apply.
Those interested please send resume and cover letter to
FL26Internships@gmail.com.
The Office of Representative Amash is seeking bright, liberty-minded students to intern this fall. Regular hours for interns are 9 a.m. to 6 p.m. on voting days and 9 a.m. to 5 p.m. on nonvoting days. Our office may accommodate interns who are available only part time.
Successful applicants will have a positive attitude and friendly demeanor, possess excellent written and verbal communication skills, and demonstrate a strong commitment to individual liberty, economic freedom, and the defense of the Constitution.
Responsibilities may include leading U.S. Capitol tours, answering phones, entering data, attending legislative briefings and other meetings, and assisting staff with legislative research and correspondence. Interns will have the opportunity to interact with me on a daily basis and will learn about the legislative process and the many other functions of a congressional office.
To request more information, or to apply for an internship, please contact my office at mi03.internship@mail.house.gov. Required application materials include a résumé, cover letter, and two short writing samples.
Please include "Rep. Amash Internship" in the subject line for all applications. Page 20 of 26
 MEM-220-15
 
MEM-219-15
The Democratic office of the Committee on House Administration seeks energetic and self-motivated undergraduate or graduate level students as well as recent graduates with an interest in government and public policy to apply for its Fall 2015 internship. Working closely with Committee staff, interns will have the opportunity to gain first-hand knowledge of the inner-workings of a congressional committee and learn about the day-to-day administrative operations of the House of Representatives. Interns are responsible for assisting Committee staff with official proceedings (hearings/markups), elections oversight, member services, and other projects as well as providing general front office support. Please note that this is not a paid internship.
Interested applicants should send a cover letter, resume, and available hours to CHADem.Intern@mail.house.gov with the subject headline, “CHA Dem Internship.”
Florida Republican is seeking interns for early September through December 2015. Qualified candidates will be hardworking, motivated self-starters, detail- oriented, and professional with strong communication and writing skills. Daily duties as an intern will include, but are not limited to, providing general constituents services in the form of answering phone calls and sorting mail, leading Capitol tours, conducting research for staff members, drafting constituent correspondence, and attending hearings.
Florida ties are a plus but not a requirement. This internship is unpaid, however, individuals will gain invaluable work experience.
Please send a resume and cover letter to FloridaConservativeRepublican@gmail.com with subject line “Intern” for consideration.
The Washington, DC office of Congresswoman Roybal-Allard is seeking motivated, organized, and reliable individuals to fill internship positions through December 18th.
Intern responsibilities include, but are not limited to, answering phones, conducting Capitol Tours, sorting incoming mail, attending briefings, conducting legislative research and performing other administrative tasks.
Successful candidates will possess excellent written and oral communication skills, a strong attentiveness to detail, an ability to work in a fast-paced environment, an eagerness to learn about the political process and congressional affairs, as well as full-week availability.
Spanish-fluency and California ties are a plus.
Please send a résumé, cover letter, a short writing sample (no longer than one page), and dates of availability to jhostyn.duval@mail.house.gov with “Intern” in the subject line.
 MEM-216-15
 MEM-215-15
 Page 21 of 26

MEM-214-15
The Democratic Staff of the Committee on Science, Space and Technology is seeking interns for the fall starting in September. Interns are asked to work with staff to help prepare for committee hearings and markups. Interns will work on substantive research projects and press matters. Additionally, interns are critical to the daily operation of the office including tasks such as answering phones, greeting visitors, and filing official documents.
Interested applicants should visit the Committee’s website at http://democrats.science.house.gov/contact-us.
Please fill out the application provided and send in a resume and two references.
A Democratic California Congressman is seeking interns to join his Washington, D.C. team for a part- or full-time, unpaid internship starting as soon as possible, for a duration of three months or longer.
Candidates should be self-starters and able to exercise good judgment on a wide range of assignments in a fast-paced and busy office. Very strong writing skills with close attention to detail and a courteous demeanor are essential.
Main responsibilities include: assisting with scheduling, answering phone calls, attending briefings and writing memos, processing mail and leading tours of the U.S. Capitol. A hard-working intern in our office will eventually move on to assisting staff with more complex legislative and press-related projects. Candidates with California ties, especially to the San Fernando Valley, and previous internship/work experience are strongly encouraged to apply.
Please e-mail resume and cover letter in PDF format to Intern.Resume@mail.house.gov.
Congressman Jim Renacci (R-OH) seeks full time hard working intern for fall 2015. Responsibilities include, but aren’t limited to, answering phone calls, assisting with the mail program, providing constituent tours, attending various briefings, and providing research for the legislative staff.
Qualified candidates will have exceptional writing skills, strong communication skills, ability to work in a fast paced working environment, and have an interest in learning more about the legislative process.
Send a resume and a cover letter to Stephen.Hostelley@mail.house.gov. Ohio candidates are strongly preferred.
Congressman Ben Ray Luján (NM-03) is seeking unpaid full-time and part-time interns for his Washington, D.C. office.
Candidates should be motivated, flexible, and detail-oriented individuals with immediate availability, and a preference for those who can stay two-three months.
 MEM-212-15
 MEM-211-15
 MEM-209-15
Page 22 of 26

MEM-208-15
MEM-206-15
The Office of Congressman Robert A. Brady (PA-01) seeks interns for Fall 2015 (September-December). Internship responsibilities will include: assisting with research, processing mail, data entry, reception duties, office errands, and other duties as assigned by the Intern Supervisor. Ideal candidate will have strong oral and written communication abilities, a willingness to learn, basic knowledge of the political process, and a firm opinion on the best cheesesteak in Philadelphia. Pennsylvania ties preferred. Both full and part time will be considered.
Please send a resume, cover letter (including availability), and writing sample to Colleen Carlos at colleen.carlos@mail.house.gov. Please no phone calls or drop- ins.
Florida Democrat seeks a full-time, unpaid press intern for the Washington, D.C. Page 23 of 26
New Mexico ties are a plus, but are not required.
Intern responsibilities include answering constituent phone calls, leading tours of the Capitol, sorting mail and faxes, writing letters, and assisting experienced staff with projects in diverse issue areas. Candidates should be outgoing and possess strong oral and written communication skills, an ability to multitask in a fast- paced environment, and a good sense of humor.
Candidates with New Mexico ties are strongly encouraged to apply. Please e-mail a resume, cover letter, and a 1-2 page writing sample to
michelle.serrato@mail.house.gov.
  Rep. Xavier Becerra is looking for interns for his Leadership
office. Responsibilities include (but are not limited to) transcribing videos, collecting press clips, live-streaming briefings, supporting the Operations team in preparing Caucus events, answering phones, providing constituency outreach support to Democratic Members of Congress and their staff, conducting research, extracting and formatting large quantities of data, writing detailed memos, attending relevant briefings and meetings, and assisting with team projects.
Applicants should be motivated, detail-oriented, possess excellent verbal and written communication skills, and be able to problem solve and multi-task. Experience or interest in social media is a plus. Women and minorities are strongly encouraged to apply.
Applicants must be either college/graduate students receiving academic credit or congressional internship/fellowship program participants.
The intern should be prepared to start working in full-time.
Applications will be reviewed on a rolling basis.
To apply, please send a cover letter and resume to caucusinternresume@mail.house.gov.
  MEM-205-15

 MEM-204-15
office. The ideal candidate will be detail-oriented, motivated, and able to multi- task efficiently. Applicants should possess strong written and oral communication skills. Preference will be given to candidates with Florida ties and those who speak Spanish.
Daily responsibilities may include:
• Updating website content;
• Compiling daily press clips;
• Video filming and editing;
• Conducting research projects;
• Drafting press materials (including e-newsletters, background
information, and press releases);
• Assisting with press events; and
• Transcribing interviews.
This is an excellent opportunity for a candidate to gain substantive press experience with an extremely active Member of Congress.
Please prepare a cover letter addressing prior press experience and interest, a résumé and a one-page writing sample.
Email the .PDF formatted materials to DCInternships.Grayson@mail.house.gov. Please indicate “Press Intern” in the subject line.
Senior Democratic Congressman Brad Sherman (CA-30) seeks highly motivated, full and part-time interns for Fall 2015. Interns are responsible for both administrative and legislative duties. Legislative support includes preparing materials for hearings, attending hearings and briefings, reaching out to agencies and congressional offices, and researching legislation for the Member and Legislative Staff. Administrative tasks include answering phones, greeting visitors, leading tours and sorting mail. Candidates should be professional, possess strong oral and written communication skills, have the ability to multitask, and have a good sense of humor. Ties to California’s 30th Congressional District are a plus but not required.
Interested applicants should e-mail a cover letter and resume to brads.interns@mail.house.gov with “CA-30 Internship” as the subject.
Florida Democrat seeks intern for the Washington, D.C. office for the Fall 2015 semester. Candidates should be motivated, enthusiastic, and possess strong interpersonal skills. The internship will provide exposure to all areas of a legislative office. Interns will be responsible for assisting the team with phones, mail, tours, flag-requests, and related front office duties.
Additional tasks, including drafting constituent correspondence, research projects, and attending hearings may be assigned on a case-by-case basis.
 MEM-202-15
Page 24 of 26

 MEM-201-15
This is a great opportunity for individuals who are interested in learning about the workings of Capitol Hill and the legislative process in a busy office.
Both full and part-time internships are available.
Please email cover letter, résumé and two writing samples to DCInternships.Grayson@mail.house.gov.
Please indicate “FALL 2015 Semester” in the subject line.
California Congressman Jared Huffman is seeking current college students or recent college graduates wishing to gain Capitol Hill experience for a full-time or part-time fall semester internship. We are seeking motivated, organized, and reliable individuals to assist the legislative and administrative staff with day-to- day duties. Such duties include attending briefings and hearings, answering phones, drafting constituent correspondence letters, doing legislative research, and various other tasks. The internship is unpaid, though interns will gain valuable Hill and office experience and will have access to many unique Hill opportunities. California ties are preferred, but not necessary.
Please send a resume and cover letter to DCInternship.Huffman@mail.house.gov. Please no drop bys, phone calls, or emailing staff members.
Congressman Matt Cartwright (D-PA) is seeking unpaid interns for his Washington, DC office for the Fall 2015 term (August/September -
December). Intern duties include answering the phone, writing letters, attending legislative briefings, and assisting staff members with special projects.
Attention to detail and strong writing and grammar skills are required. Candidates with Pennsylvania ties are especially encouraged to apply, although all applications will be considered equally regardless of state or district.
Prospective candidates should apply online and submit a resume and cover letter to http://cartwright.house.gov/services/internships.
No phone calls or drop ins, please.
Colorado Republican is seeking interns for late August through December of 2015. Interns are paid if they do not receive college credit for their internship. Qualified candidates should be detail-oriented, hardworking, and professional with strong communication and writing skills. Intern responsibilities include providing constituent tours, drafting correspondence, attending various briefings, providing research for legislative staff, and assisting the front office staff.
Please send a resume and cover letter to CODCIntern@gmail.com. Conservative Republican seeks highly motivated fall interns for DC office.
Successful candidates will be organized, hard-working, and detail- oriented. Intern will be responsible for assisting staff with legislative and administrative duties such as greeting visitors, drafting constituent
 MEM-200-15
 MEM-198-15
MEM-164-15
 Page 25 of 26

correspondence, answering phones, and leading Capitol tours. Interns will also have opportunities to attend staff briefings and committee hearings to gain firsthand knowledge of the legislative process. The position is unpaid, and the intern is responsible for finding housing in the DC area. Florida ties preferred.
If interested, please send a cover letter, resume, and available dates to fl11internship@gmail.com. No phone calls or walk-ins, please.
 Page 26 of 26
