 ________________________________________________________________________
House Vacancy Announcement and Placement Service (HVAPS)
B-235 Longworth House Office Building Washington, D.C. 20515 202-226-5836
Vacancy Bulletins are available for pick-up in
Longworth HOB - B-227 (CAO First Call Customer Service Center) or in the CAO Human Resources Office - Ford HOB 102
To Subscribe or Unsubscribe to the Vacancy Listserv visit:
http://www.house.gov/content/jobs/
Job Line: 202-226-4504 _____________________________________________________________________________
 MEM-339-15
INTERNSHIP VACANCY LISTING
Week of October 26, 2015
Georgia Congressman David Scott seeks unpaid interns for spring semester. Duties will include the following: attending hearings and briefings, responding to constituent inquiries, researching legislation, conducting U.S. Capitol tours, and basic administrative responsibilities. Qualified candidates must be highly organized, responsible, detail oriented, possess excellent communication and writing skills, and be able to multi-task. Georgia ties and/or an interest in agriculture or financial services are preferred. All interested applicants should send a resume, and cover letter to seema.ibrahim@mail.house.gov with the subject line “Name – Spring Internship Application.”
The Office of Representative Loretta Sanchez (CA-46) is seeking unpaid interns for her Washington, DC office for the 2016 Spring Semester/Winter Quarter. Candidates should have an interest in and knowledge of the legislative process, possess excellent writing and communication skills, and have an understanding of the American political system.
Interns will be responsible for projects such as writing congressional correspondence, fielding constituent phone calls, and other requests. Additional
 MEM-338-15
Page 1 of 19

 MEM-337-15
duties include, but are not limited to, leading Capitol building tours, attending briefings and committee hearings, and conducting research on various legislative issues. Applicants are expected to start in early January.
Individuals with Orange County, California ties are strongly encouraged to apply. Knowledge of the 46th Congressional District is strongly recommended. Applicants should send a cover letter, resume, and 1-2 page writing sample to CA46internships@mail.house.gov. Qualified applicants will be contacted for interviews. No phone calls, please.
Democratic Congressman Pete Aguilar (CA-31) is seeking highly motivated interns to join his Washington D.C. office. Interns will have the chance to experience the fast-paced atmosphere of a congressional office and gain valuable work experience. This is an excellent opportunity for those interested in the legislative process. Intern responsibilities include attending hearings and briefings, assisting with front office duties, answering phones, assisting with tours, researching legislation for staff and drafting constituent correspondence letters on various issues before the House. Qualified applicants must possess excellent written and oral communication skills, professionalism, attention to detail and ability to function in a fast-paced environment.
Full-time 3 month internship positions are available beginning November 16, 2015. CA-31 and/or California ties are preferred but not required. Internships are unpaid, however current students may be eligible for academic credit. To apply, please send your resume by November 9, 2015 to Chelsea.Glynn@mail.house.gov.
The office of a western Republican House member is looking for an experienced unpaid communications intern to assist with day-to-day operations and special projects in the Washington, D.C. office. Candidates should be soon-to-be or recent college graduates with a preferred major in PR, journalism, English, or communications. Interested applicants must be able to commit to at least 30 hours per week. Qualified candidates will have a previous internship in communications, journalism, a political office or on the Hill, excellent writing skills, and a positive attitude and sense of humor. Photoshop experience is a plus. Intern responsibilities will include monitoring news on relevant policy areas and compile media reports, drafting social media posts and graphics on legislation, issue positions, and news items. Interns will also help brainstorm creative ways to concisely convey complex policy initiatives, draft press material, proof and edit documents from Senior Staff, and assist the Communications Director with special projects. Interested candidates should send their resume and two brief writing samples to WesternStateIntern@gmail.com. Writing samples may include: press release, advisory, professional Facebook post & corresponding tweet, school newspaper article, etc.
The office of a western Republican House member is looking for an unpaid Page 2 of 19
 MEM-336-15
 MEM-335-15

 MEM-334-14
intern for Spring 2016. Candidates should be hardworking, detail-oriented, and professional with strong communication and writing skills. Intern responsibilities will include, but are not limited to, providing general constituent services in the form of answering phone calls and sorting mail, leading Capitol tours, conducting research for staff members, drafting constituent correspondence, and attending hearings. Western ties are preferred, but not required. Interested candidates should send their resume, a cover letter, and a brief writing sample to WesternStateIntern@gmail.com.
Internships are currently available in Congresswoman Zoe Lofgren’s (CA-19) Washington, D.C. office. Congresswoman Lofgren represents California’s 19th Congressional District, which lies in the heart of California’s “Silicon Valley”. Interns have the chance to experience the fast-paced atmosphere of a busy congressional office and gain invaluable work experience. This is an excellent opportunity for those interested in the legislative process. Interns’ responsibilities will vary—in addition to answering phones and running errands around the Capitol, interns will have the opportunity to attend hearings and briefings, research legislation for legislative staff, and answer constituent letters on various issues before the House.
Qualified applicants must possess excellent writing and analytical skills, a demonstrated work ethic, and ability to function in a fast-paced environment. A successful candidate will be motivated, able to multitask, and have the ability to work well under pressure. Full-time internship positions are available beginning November 2, 2015. Internships are unpaid.
CA-19 and/or California ties are preferred but not required. Interested applicants should apply through http://lofgren.house.gov.
Senior Republican Congressman is seeking a highly motivated, full-time intern that can start immediately upon acceptance. The individual should be able to multi-task and be prepared to work in a fast-paced office. Some responsibilities include attending briefings, answering phones, guiding tours of the Capitol, assisting with constituent correspondence and mail, and working on various projects for the staff as needed. North Carolina ties are encouraged, but not required. In order to apply, please send capitolhill45@gmail.com a resume and cover letter with “NC Intern Application” in the subject line.
The Office of Congresswoman Debbie Wasserman Schultz (D-FL) has openings for full-time and part-time interns to support our administrative, legislative, and press teams. Responsibilities include: researching legislative issues, attending legislative briefings and hearings, answering phone calls, processing constituent mail, giving Capitol tours, and assisting with special projects.
Applicants should be enthusiastic, reliable, professional, hardworking, and have strong writing and communication skills. South Florida ties are preferred, but not
 MEM-333-15
MEM-332-15
 Page 3 of 19

 MEM-329-15
required. Internships begin in early to mid-January and run through the semester. These positions are unpaid. Interested candidates should submit a resume, cover letter, and one-page writing sample to RepDWSresumes@gmail.com by November 23. Location: Washington, DC.
The Committee on Education and the Workforce, Democratic Staff is currently seeking undergraduate interns for Fall 2015 (available to start immediately) and Spring 2016 (available to start in January). We are also accepting graduate and/or fellowship applications for both labor and education for Spring 2016 (available to start in January).
Interns perform a variety of tasks that support the staff in our legislative and media work. Legislative tasks may include, but are not limited to, legislative research, assembling information, assisting staff during hearing and markup preparation and execution, and attending hearings, markups, briefings and meetings. Media work may include assisting staff to organize and staff Committee press conferences and assisting with the production of daily news clips relating to Committee’s issues. Undergraduate Interns are also trained to perform administrative duties, such as answering phones, and sorting and distributing mail.
Interested applicants should email their cover letter and resume to jobs_ewdems@mail.house.gov. Please visit our website at http://democrats.edworkforce.house.gov/about/internships for more information.
The Office of Congressman Reid Ribble is seeking qualified candidates to intern in our Washington, D.C. office starting in January 2016. We are interested in candidates of all academic disciplines.
Interns will assist the staff with a variety of tasks, including office administration, legislative research, constituent correspondence, and other duties as assigned. Administration will include daily tasks such as welcoming guests, being aware of the Congressman’s and staff’s schedules, answering phones, constituent tours, mail administration, and other duties. Legislative research and constituent correspondence will include being aware of current and pending legislation, researching legislation for constituent correspondence, attending briefings, and other duties.
Candidates should have excellent writing and communication skills, strong organizational abilities, a good work ethic, an ability to work independently, and the drive to take the initiative in a fast-paced environment.
This is an unpaid position. If candidates have any questions or wish to apply, please send a cover letter, resume and writing sample to dominique.yantko@mail.house.gov.
  MEM-328-15
 Page 4 of 19

MEM-327-15
The Washington, DC office of Congressman Luis V. Gutiérrez is seeking motivated, organized, and reliable individuals to fill internship positions in the fall of 2015. Intern responsibilities include, but are not limited to, answering phones, conducting Capitol Tours, sorting incoming mail, attending briefings, conducting legislative research and performing other administrative tasks.
Successful candidates will possess excellent written and oral communication skills, a strong attentiveness to detail, an ability to work in a fast paced environment, an eagerness to learn about the legislative process, as well as a minimum four day per week availability. Internships are unpaid. Spanish-fluency and Illinois ties are a plus.
Please send a résumé, cover letter, and dates of availability to gutierrezopportunities@gmail.com with “Intern” in the subject line.
Democratic Congressman seeks applicants for full- or part-time unpaid congressional internship for Spring 2016. Duties will include conducting legislative research, drafting memos, assisting with front office duties, and performing basic administrative tasks. Candidates must exhibit strong writing and communication skills. California residents or strong ties to San Diego are preferred. Candidates should be prepared to work a minimum of 10 hours per week. Please send a resume, cover letter, writing sample (1-2 pages), and times available (start and end dates as well as days per week) to CA52Internship@mail.house.gov with “LAST NAME, FIRST NAME, CA52 Internship” in the subject line.
The Washington, DC office of Congressman Alcee L. Hastings is seeking motivated, organized and hard-working candidates to intern full time or part time. Intern responsibilities include, but not limited to, answering constituent calls, sorting constituent correspondence, conducting legislative research, writing memoranda, attending briefings and hearings, and conducting U.S. Capitol Tours.
Applicants should have strong written and oral communications skills, exceptional interpersonal skills, an interest in policy and government and the ability to work in a fast pace environment. Internships are unpaid but present an excellent way to learn the legislative process and gain Capitol Hill experience.
Please send a résumé, cover letter, and dates of availability to deborah.posey@mail.house.gov with “Intern” in the subject line.
Congressman John Garamendi (CA-03) is seeking a highly motivated intern to join his Washington, DC office this winter. Candidates should be collegial, professional, quick learners, and phenomenal team players. Strong oral and written communication skills and close attention to detail are imperative. Duties include assisting staff with legislative, administrative, and press related projects, writing memos and talking points, attending hearings and meetings, answering
 MEM-326-15
 MEM-325-15
 MEM-324-15
Page 5 of 19

 MEM-323-15
constituent phone calls, leading tours of the US Capitol, assisting with scheduling, sorting and distributing mail, and managing tour and flag requests.
Interns are considered an integral part of the team and are given the opportunity to learn and grow through working with us both to achieve the goals of the office and to pursue and develop their areas of interest. First-hand experience in Congressman Garamendi’s congressional office provides interns with an unparalleled knowledge and understanding of the development of public policy. Full-time candidates with California ties and previous internship/work experience are strongly encouraged to apply. Please e-mail a resume, cover letter and dates of availability to Garamendi.Internships@mail.house.gov by December 1st.
Congressman Ben Ray Luján (NM-03) is seeking unpaid full-time and part-time interns for his Washington, D.C. office. Candidates should be motivated, flexible, and detail-oriented individuals with immediate availability, and a preference for those who can stay two-three months. New Mexico ties are a plus, but are not required.
Intern responsibilities include answering constituent phone calls, leading tours of the Capitol, sorting mail and faxes, writing letters, and assisting experienced staff with projects in diverse issue areas. Candidates should be outgoing and possess strong oral and written communication skills, an ability to multitask in a fast- paced environment, and a good sense of humor. Candidates with New Mexico ties are strongly encouraged to apply. Please e-mail a resume, cover letter, and a 1-2 page writing sample to michelle.serrato@mail.house.gov.
Congressman Joe Wilson (SC-02) is currently seeking interns for the Washington, D.C. office to start immediately.
Qualified candidates will possess an interest in the legislative process, excellent writing and communication skills, strong attention to detail, and a willingness to learn and take on new tasks.
Intern responsibilities include but are not limited to, assisting staff with general office duties, attending hearings/briefings for staff members, answering phones, sorting through mail, drafting response letters, and giving tours of the U.S. Capitol. Candidates should be highly motivated and have good communication skills. This position is unpaid, but does offer a great educational experience for anyone with aspirations of working on Capitol Hill.
All interested applicants should submit a cover letter and resume to sc02.internship@mail.house.gov.
North Carolina Democrat seeks an unpaid Communications Intern for her Washington, D.C. office. Duties include tracking press clips and traffic on social media networks, updating and maintaining press contact lists, drafting press
 MEM-322-15
 MEM-321-15
Page 6 of 19

 MEM-320-15
releases, and assisting with the office's day-to-day communications operation. Applicants should have a strong interest in political communications, new media, or journalism. North Carolina ties are a plus. Women and minorities are encouraged to apply. Please send your resume and cover letter to nc12internjobs@gmail.com.
California Democratic Congressman Jared Huffman is seeking current college students or recent college graduates wishing to gain Capitol Hill experience for a full-time or part-time internship. We are seeking motivated, organized, and reliable individuals to assist the legislative and administrative staff with day-to- day duties. Such duties include attending briefings and hearings, answering phones, drafting constituent correspondence letters, doing legislative research, and various other tasks.
The internship is unpaid, though interns will gain valuable Hill and office experience as well as have access to many unique Hill opportunities. Congressman Huffman represents California’s 2nd congressional district, which extends along the Pacific coast, from the Golden Gate Bridge to the Oregon border. California ties are preferred, but not necessary. Please send resume and cover letter to DCInternship.Huffman@mail.house.gov.
Nevada Republican seeks a legislative intern for January 2016 and/or Spring 2016. Interns will work in a fast-paced Congressional Office, gaining valuable exposure and knowledge of the legislative process and the United States Congress. Intern responsibilities include greeting constituents, handling constituent phone calls, opening and sorting mail, guiding Capitol building tours, and assisting staff with administrative tasks. Interns will also have the opportunity to conduct legislative research, and assist with correspondence, as well as attend Capitol Hill briefings, congressional hearings, receptions, and press events.
Legislative Internship Qualifications:
Our office is looking for an intern with a positive attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Successful interns will be self- starters, take and listen to direction, and be willing to work both independently as well as part of a team environment. Applicants should have working knowledge of current events and policy topics, as well as a willingness to do assist with daily office tasks. Nevada ties strongly preferred.
Legislative Internship Requirements:
Interns must be able to commit a minimum of three full days a week (9:00am- 6:00pm). Students welcome to apply. Those interested please send cover letter, updated resume, and references to kelsey.wolfgram@mail.house.gov.
Nevada Republican seeks an unpaid communications intern for January 2016 and/or Spring 2016. Interns will work in a fast-paced Congressional office,
 MEM-319-15
 MEM-318-15
Page 7 of 19

 MEM-317-15
gaining valuable exposure and knowledge of the communications process and the United States Congress. Communication intern responsibilities include tracking and reporting on social media and news story comments, drafting social media posts, establishing and managing a twitter account, and reaching out to local/national reporters on social media. Interns will also have the opportunity to attend events and committee meetings to take photos and videos, work with the communications director to put press releases on the website, and assist with writing projects at the discretion of the communications director. Interns will also help facilitate our constituent communications program and guide constituents on tours of the US Capitol building.
Communications Intern Qualifications:
Our office seeks an intern with a positive attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Successful interns will be self- starters, take and listen to direction, and be willing to work both independently and as a member of a team environment. Applicants must have a working knowledge of current events and policy topics as well as a willingness to assist with daily communication tasks. Nevada ties strongly preferred.
Communications Intern Requirements:
Interns must be able to commit a minimum of three full days a week (9:00 am- 6:00 pm) with the option of working full-time, spring semester beginning in January. Students are welcome to apply. If interested, please send a cover letter, updated resume, sample of a social media post for a congressperson, and references to kelsey.wolfgram@mail.house.gov.
Congressman Adam Kinzinger (IL-16) is looking for unpaid interns in his Washington, DC office for the 2015 fall and spring semesters. Interns will observe the inner workings of a Congressional office while gaining firsthand knowledge of the legislative process. Responsibilities include leading Capitol tours, answering phones, greeting constituents, assisting staff with legislative projects, and attending briefings and hearings. Ideal candidates should have a strong work ethic, be energetic and engaging, and possess a positive attitude. Candidates with Illinois ties are encouraged to apply. Please send resume and cover letter (with availability) to internsIL16@gmail.com.
Seeking intern who will report to the Intern Coordinator/Supervisor.
CORE RESPONSIBILITIES:
• to assist in performing clerking duties, processing the mail, data entry, reception duties and other office errands.
DUTIES:
• Sorts and distributes mail;
• Performs data entry, including logging in incoming letters; • Answers the telephones;
 MEM-315-15
Page 8 of 19

 MEM-314-15
• Assists staff with Committee business including: Hearings, Briefings, and Business Meetings;
• Performs other duties as assigned by the Intern Supervisor.
To apply for this position, please send an email to Brett.Cozzolino@mail.house.gov with a resume, cover letter, and a short writing sample.
Illinois Representative Mike Bost is looking for college students or recent grads for a Congressional internship. These internships are available now on either a full-time or part-time basis. Qualified candidates will be highly organized, prompt, responsible, and ready to work in a fast paced environment. Strong oral and communication skills are a must. Daily duties will include assisting staff, answering phones, organizing mail, giving tours of the Capitol Building, and attending hearings and briefings for legislative staff. Interns will gain valuable Capitol Hill experience and further their understanding of the legislative process. Illinois ties are preferred but not necessary. All interested applicants should e- mail their resume and/or cover letter to midwestinternship@gmail.com.
Florida Republican is seeking interns for early January through May 2016. Qualified candidates will be hardworking, motivated self-starters, detail-oriented, and professional with strong communication and writing skills. Daily duties as an intern will include providing general constituents services in the form of answering phone calls and sorting mail, leading Capitol tours, conducting research for staff members, drafting constituent correspondence, and attending hearings. Florida ties are a plus but not a requirement. This internship is unpaid, however, individuals will gain invaluable experience. Please send a resume and cover letter to FloridaConservativeRepublican@gmail.com with subject line “Intern” for consideration.
The Washington, DC office of Rep. Mark Sanford (SC-01) seeks applicants for unpaid fulltime internships for the fall season. Applicants should be able to competently handle telephone calls, be well-organized, have an eye for detail, possess strong writing skills, be generally knowledgeable of legislative and related issues, and be able to complete tasks as directed. Main duties include answering telephones, logging constituent calls, giving tours of the Capitol to visitors, opening and sorting mail, and assisting with other projects. Interns will have many opportunities to take on additional responsibilities within the office, at the discretion of staff. Interest in fiscal responsibility and ties to South Carolina preferred. Anyone interested should send a resume to Martha@mail.house.gov.
The Washington DC office of Congressman Patrick Meehan is currently accepting applications for Spring 2015. Intern responsibilities include researching legislation for the Member and legislative staff, attending hearings and briefings, answering phones, day to day office duties, and answering constituent letters on various issues before the House of Representatives. As a
 MEM-313-15
 MEM-312-15
 MEM-311-15
Page 9 of 19

 MEM-310-15
result, interns learn about the legislative process and the many other functions of a congressional office. The hours are flexible, but generally run 8:30 AM – 5:30 PM when Congress is in session, and 9:00 AM to 5:00 PM when not in session. Interested applicants should submit a resume and cover letter to MeehanDCIntern@gmail.com. The deadline to apply is November 20, 2015. Ties to Pennsylvania’s 7th Congressional District are preferred, but not required.
The DC office of Congressman Derek Kilmer, hailing from Washington’s 6th district, is looking for personable, diligent full or part-time interns to start for the upcoming Late Fall/Winter term. This is an opportunity to learn about the inner- workings of a congressional office on the Hill in a fast-paced work environment. The internship allows access to briefings and interesting events related to a wide range of important issues. Responsibilities include assisting with constituent correspondence, producing daily press clips, and leading tours of the Capitol. This is a unique opportunity and prime for students or recent grads who are interested in learning about the legislative process or may eventually want to work for the federal government. To apply, please send a resume, contact information for two references, and a cover letter outlining your interest in the position to nwcongressionalinternship@gmail.com, and expect a response within a week. Those with Washington state ties strongly encouraged to apply. We look forward to hearing from you!
The Office of Congressman Juan Vargas (CA-51) is currently seeking interns for the Washington, D.C. office for the Fall 2015 semester.
Intern responsibilities include but are not limited to, assisting staff with legislative research, administrative office duties, attending hearings/briefings for staff members, answering phones, sorting through mail, drafting response letters, and giving tours of the U.S. Capitol. This position is unpaid, but does offer a great educational experience for anyone with aspirations of working on the Hill. Ideal candidates should have good communication skills and a positive attitude. California ties and Economics/Business majors are preferred.
All interested applicants should send a cover letter and resume to daniel.gaytan@mail.house.gov.
Energetic NY Democrat is seeking a highly motivated Legal Fellow to assist with a number of issues, including criminal justice, intellectual property, and financial services. Responsibilities include analyzing policy issues, drafting memos, researching policy positions, and assisting extremely active legislative staff as needed. The ideal candidate is a law school student or recent law school graduate and should possess strong communication skills, attention to detail, and the ability to operate in a fast-paced environment. Candidates with New York ties and previous internship/work experience are strongly encouraged to apply. This fellowship is unpaid but is eligible for school credit where applicable.
 MEM-309-15
 MEM-308-15
Page 10 of 19

 MEM-307-15
Please e-mail a resume, cover letter, and a writing sample to NY.ResumeInbox@mail.house.gov with “Legal Fellowship” in the subject line. Equal opportunity employer. No calls or walk-ins please.
The Washington, DC office of Congressman Peter DeFazio (OR-04) seeks highly motivated interns, full time or part time, for Fall 2015. Successful candidates will demonstrate that they are organized, detail-oriented, and professional.
Strong written and oral communication skills are essential.
Intern responsibilities will include but are not limited to assisting staff with legislative, administrative, constituent relations, and press activities. Interns will: answer phones; sort, distribute, and respond to constituent mail; lead tours of the US Capitol building; attend hearings and briefings; and assist with legislative research. Internships are unpaid, but arrangements may be made to earn academic credit.
To apply, please send a resume, cover letter, and brief writing sample to OR04.InternCoordinator@mail.house.gov. Candidates with Oregon ties are strongly encouraged to apply. No phone calls or drop-ins, please.
Democratic Congressman Mike Honda is seeking interns for the fall.
 MEM-306-15
Interns
‐ Assist with office administrative tasks including, sorting incoming mail,
greeting visitors, and answering the telephone.
‐ Assist in the preparation of letters to constituents.
‐ Perform legislative research.
‐ Respond to requests from constituents.
‐ Attend briefings, hearings, and special events.
‐ Sit in on meetings with stakeholders.
‐ Gain valuable Hill experience and learn about the legislative process.
Candidates with full-time availability are highly preferred. Additionally, ties to the Bay Area and additional languages are preferred.
Congressman Mike Honda represents California’s 17th Congressional District, which includes much of Silicon Valley. He serves on the prestigious Appropriations Committee’s subcommittees on Commerce, Justice, and Science and on Energy and Water. He is a champion of progressive ideals has a strong focus on education, civil rights, and science and technology policy.
Applicants should email a resume and cover letter to: bayareademocrat@gmail.com.
The Office of Congressman Trent Franks (R-AZ) seeks Fall 2015 interns for his Washington D.C. office. Candidates should be energetic, hard-working, eager to
will:
 MEM-305-15
Page 11 of 19

 MEM-304-15
learn, and able to work in a fast-paced environment.
Interns will be responsible for answering phones, speaking with constituents about legislative affairs, scheduling and giving Capitol tours, attending briefings, and supporting the legislative staff. Other responsibilities may include editing or writing briefs, doing research on current legislation, planning events on the Hill, and responding to constituent mail.
Interested candidates should email a current resume to Chelsea.Patterson@mail.house.gov.
Congressman Benishek from Michigan’s First District seeks unpaid interns to fill positions for January through May 2016. Main responsibilities include answering phones, processing mail, drafting constituent correspondence letters, researching legislative issues, and attending meetings/hearings as needed. There will also be opportunities to attend receptions and seminars of interest. Candidates should be self-motivated, enthusiastic, flexible, and computer-literate (with a good understanding of MS Office). This is a great opportunity for college students seeking academic credit. Michigan ties are preferred.
Please e-mail your cover letter, resume, and references to Samuel Grossman at samuel.grossman@mail.house.gov.
Louisiana Republican seeks full and part time intern(s) to start immediately in Washington, DC office. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to, greeting constituents, answering phone calls, opening and sorting mail, scheduling and guiding US Capitol Building tours, and assisting staff with administrative tasks. Interns are also provided the opportunity to conduct legislative research and attend briefings, hearing, and press events.
Ideal candidate will have excellent written and verbal communication skills, strong work ethic, ability to multi-task, and a positive attitude.
Southern ties preferred, but not necessary.
Those interested please send resumes to Ann.Pierce@mail.house.gov with “Intern Application” in the subject line.
Congressman Bruce Westerman (AR-04) is currently accepting applications for his Spring and Summer 2016 internship program in his Washington, D.C. office. He is seeking highly qualified candidates who are motivated, detail-oriented, and personable. The ideal candidates will have excellent research and writing abilities, be able to multi-task and interact well with constituents. Interns will have the opportunity to experience working on Capitol Hill, learn about the legislative process, and attend briefings of interest. Responsibilities will include answering the phone, giving tours of the Capitol, assisting with constituent correspondence, and supporting the legislative and communication staff on
 MEM-301-15
 MEM-300-15
Page 12 of 19

 MEM-298-15
various projects. Although internships are unpaid, the office is happy to fill out any necessary forms for students to receive credit at their respective college or university. Arkansas ties are preferred, but not required. Interested candidates should email a resume and cover letter to Victoria.Bell@mail.house.gov.
Communications office for Democratic Leadership seeks a driven and dedicated press intern to assist a fast-paced press team with daily operations to start immediately. This is an unpaid, full-time, Monday through Friday position.
Job Description: Intern responsibilities include, but are not limited to: answering phones, fielding reporter inquiries, assisting with the management of press events, helping to monitor press clips, tracking social media and breaking news, and transcribing interviews, speeches, and remarks.
Requirements: Interns should have a demonstrated interest in political communication. Applicants should have strong writing and proofreading skills, an ability to handle high-pressure situations, and a solid understanding of politics and the legislative process. Prior Hill experience and/or social media and Spanish language skills are a plus.
Please e-mail resume and cover letter to taylor.griffin@mail.house.gov.
Congressman French Hill (AR-02) is pleased to announce the availability of full- time and part-time Congressional Communications Internships in his Washington, D.C. office beginning immediately.
Interns will work in a fast-paced Capitol Hill office, gaining valuable exposure and knowledge of the legislative process and the U.S. Congress. Intern responsibilities will include working closely with the Communications Director to draft messaging documents and respond to press inquiries messaging. Additionally intern responsibilities will include greeting constituents, answering constituent phone calls, opening and sorting mail, guiding U.S. Capitol building tours, and assisting staff with administrative tasks. Interns also will have the opportunity to conduct legislative research and assist with correspondence, as well as attend Capitol Hill briefings, congressional hearings, and press events.
Ideal candidates will have a positive attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills as well as social media and other communications experience. Additionally, ideal candidates will be self-starters, take and listen to direction, and be able to work both independently and as part of a team.
Applicants should have working knowledge of current events and policy topics as well as a willingness to assist with daily office tasks. Arkansas ties strongly preferred. Interested candidates should send their cover letter and resume to ar02.applications@mail.house.gov.
 MEM-296-15
 Page 13 of 19

MEM-295-15
The Democratic office of the Committee on House Administration seeks energetic and self-motivated undergraduate or graduate level students as well as recent graduates with an interest in government and public policy to apply for its Fall 2015 internship. Working closely with Committee staff, interns will have the opportunity to gain first-hand knowledge of the inner-workings of a congressional committee and learn about the day-to-day administrative operations of the House of Representatives. Interns are responsible for assisting Committee staff with official proceedings (hearings/markups), elections oversight, member services, and other projects as well as providing general front office support. Please note that this is not a paid internship. Interested applicants should send a cover letter, resume, and available hours to CHADem.Intern@mail.house.gov with the subject headline, “CHA Dem Internship.”
The Office of Congressman Garret Graves (LA-06) is currently seeking interns for the Washington, D.C. office for the Fall 2015 semester. Intern responsibilities include but are not limited to, assisting staff with general office duties, attending hearings/briefings for staff members, answering phones, sorting through mail, drafting response letters, and giving tours of the U.S. Capitol. Qualified applicants should be organized, enthusiastic and professional with have excellent written and oral communication skills. This position is unpaid, but does offer a great educational experience for anyone with aspirations of working on the Hill. Having Louisiana ties is a plus. All interested applicants should send a cover letter and resume to Chelsea.Keene@mail.house.gov.
The Washington, DC, office of a high profile Member of Congress has unpaid Press internship openings to begin immediately until end of the year.
Press interns are expected to work long hours and commit between 3-5 days per week. Internship duties include, but are not limited to compiling and daily clips, drafting press releases and op-eds, proofreading and editing, maintaining press lists, updating Member's communications calendar, website and social media platforms. Intern may also assist with answering phones, incoming and outgoing mail, addressing constituent concerns, and assisting the Legislative/District office staff. Strong writing skills are needed and familiarity with new media and website development is a plus. Priority will be given to those with journalism or communications education/experience.
The ideal candidate will be creative, motivated, mature, detail-orientated, and possess the ability to multi-task under high pressure. This is a great opportunity for college students and recent graduates. Women and minorities, especially those with Spanish language fluency, are highly encouraged to apply.
To apply for the position, please send your cover letter, resume and writing sample addressed to the Comm. Director at ny13intern@gmail.com with the subject: Press Intern.
Congressman Himes’ Washington D.C. office (CT-04) seeks motivated interns Page 14 of 19
 MEM-294-15
 MEM-291-15
 MEM-290-15

 MEM-289-15
available to start immediately. Potential interns should be able to work independently, have good communication skills, and have an interest in the legislative process. Tasks will include fielding constituent inquiries, drafting memos and letters, attending briefings, leading tours of the capitol and helping with administrative tasks. Interns will also have the opportunity to learn more about and focus on their issues of interest, through letter-writing and briefings.
Interns will work closely with the Staff Assistant, Legislative Correspondent, Legislative Assistants, and Scheduler on day-to day tasks and special projects. Connecticut ties and full time availability preferred but not required.
Interested parties should submit a cover letter, resume, and writing sample to Kamilah.Tisdale@mail.house.gov.
The office of a New York Congressman seeks an unpaid full-time press intern with exceptional writing and editing skills. Duties will include: authoring interesting and creative content for the website on various topics and other tasks as assigned. The intern must be highly motivated and have excellent writing and communication skills.
All interested and qualified candidates should email a resume and two writing samples. Please submit all inquiries with the subject “Press Internship” to: NY.ResumeInbox@mail.house.gov.
Southern Republican is seeking interns for the Fall 2015 semester to join the Washington, DC office. Ideal candidates will have excellent written and verbal communication skills as this position involves significant constituent interaction. Applicants must be detail oriented, professional, and highly organized. Responsibilities include scheduling and conducting Capitol tours, processing constituent mail, answering phones, conducting general administrative tasks, and supporting policy staff with various projects.
Interested applicants may send a resume and cover letter to eliza.thurston@mail.house.gov.
Congressman Tim Walz (MN-01) is seeking prospective interns available to start immediately. Applicants should be highly-motivated, well-organized and eager to assist with the legislative, communications and administrative needs of the office. Such duties include, but are not limited to, attending briefings, answering phones, drafting constituent response letters, conducting research, giving tours of the Capitol and various other administrative tasks. Applicants should possess an interest in the legislative process, as well as strong written and verbal communications skills. Minnesota ties are a plus, but not required.
Applications accepted for both full and part-time positions (min. 20 hours per week). This is an unpaid position.
 MEM-288-15
 MEM-287-15
Page 15 of 19

 MEM-286-15
To be considered, please send a resume, cover letter and at least three (3) references ASAP to: alyssa.berg@mail.house.gov.
Midwest Republican is currently seeking interns in his Washington, D.C. office for fall 2015 (September-December). Interns perform a variety of responsibilities, including answering phones, receiving guests, and providing tours of the Capitol Building. They will also research legislation for the legislative staff, attend hearings and briefings, and answer constituent letters on various issues before the House. Interns should possess strong research, writing, analytical, and interpersonal skills. Moreover, candidates should express an interest in politics and conservative values.
All internships are unpaid. However, if your college or university offers credit hours we are happy to complete any necessary evaluations.
Interested candidates should email their resume and cover letter to MOCongressionalInternship@gmail.com.
Intern needed to start immediately. Stipend available. Please indicate any connections to Minnesota in your cover letter's first paragraph.
We are seeking energetic and proficient interns in the Washington, D.C. office of Congresswoman Betty McCollum (MN04). An internship in Congresswoman McCollum’s office will provide valuable experience to students as they prepare for their professional careers. Interns have the opportunity to work with and assist all members of the staff, including legislative, administrative, outreach and press duties. Washington, DC interns will be encouraged to take advantage of the many hearings, workshops and seminars that are held on Capitol Hill.
In addition, we are happy to work with your college or university to arrange for academic credit. Applicants should be highly motivated and enthusiastic, as there are far more applicants than available positions.
Minnesota ties are strongly preferred.
Responsibilities include:
• Supporting administrative staff: answering phones, database entry, and sorting mail.
• Supporting legislative staff: tracking constituent correspondence, drafting letters, and conducting light research.
• Attending briefings and hearings for legislative staff.
• Compiling news clips.
• Promoting constituent outreach efforts by communicating with constituents and constituent groups, attending meetings and events, and drafting correspondence.
 MEM-282-15
Page 16 of 19

 MEM-281-15
Hours:
• Internships are available year‐round.
• They are available on a part‐time or full‐time basis. Minimum 25 hours a week. • Transportation and housing are the responsibility of interns.
Application process:
Applicants should send a cover letter, available hours and a resume. Those interested in a Washington, DC internship should email scheduler_mn04dc@mail.house.gov.
Please indicate any Minnesota ties in the first paragraph of your cover letter.
Ohio Democrat is seeking interns for the fall 2015 semester. Interns will work in a fast-paced Congressional Office, gaining valuable exposure and knowledge of the legislative process and the United States Congress. Interns will have the opportunity to conduct legislative research, assist with correspondence, as well as attend some Capitol Hill briefings, congressional hearings, and press events. Responsibilities will include handling constituent phone calls, opening and sorting mail, giving Capitol Tours, and assisting staff with administrative tasks. This internship is unpaid.
Qualifications: Interns must have a pleasant attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Successful interns will be able to find information with little assistance, be able to work both independently as well as part of a team, and have strong attention to detail.
9th District Ohio ties a plus!
Please email Courtney.hruska@Mail.house.gov with cover letter and resume. Availability must be in cover letter.
Congressman French Hill (AR-02) has available full-time and part-time, unpaid internships for the 2015 Fall and 2015 Winter semesters in his Washington, D.C. office beginning immediately. Interns will work in a fast-paced Capitol Hill office, gaining valuable exposure and knowledge of the legislative process and the U.S. Congress. Intern responsibilities include greeting constituents, answering constituent phone calls, opening and sorting mail, guiding U.S. Capitol building tours, and assisting staff with administrative tasks. Interns also will have the opportunity to conduct legislative research and assist with correspondence, as well as attend Capitol Hill briefings, congressional hearings, and press events.
Interns will have a positive attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Social media and other communications experience a plus. Successful interns will be self-starters, take and listen to direction, and be able to work both independently and as part of a team. Applicants should have
 MEM-279-15
Page 17 of 19

 MEM-278-15
working knowledge of current events and policy topics as well as a willingness to assist with daily office tasks. Arkansas ties strongly preferred.
Those interested please send resume and cover letter to ar02.applications@mail.house.gov.
Congresswoman Mimi Walters (CA-45), a Republican freshman member who holds a GOP leadership positon, seeks part-time interns to start immediately in her DC office. Responsibilities will include but are not limited to administrative duties, legislative research, helping with mail, assisting with tours and other constituent services.
Preference is for an individual who can work part-time from now through December. California ties are preferred, but not necessary.
If interested please send a resume and a brief cover letter to InternshipsCA45@gmail.com with “Internship Application” in the subject line.
Congressman Jim Renacci (R-OH) seeks part time/full time hard working intern for fall 2015. Responsibilities include, but aren’t limited to, answering phone calls, assisting with the mail program, providing constituent tours, attending various briefings, and providing research for the legislative staff.
Qualified candidates will have exceptional writing skills, strong communication skills, ability to work in a fast paced working environment, and have an interest in learning more about the legislative process.
Send a resume and a cover letter to Stephen.Hostelley@mail.house.gov. Ohio candidates are strongly preferred.
 MEM-277-15
  Northeastern House Democrat seeks a full-time intern to start immediately in Washington, D.C. office. Duties will include drafting constituent correspondence, sorting mail, answering telephones, attending legislative briefings, assisting the legislative staff with research, and other tasks as assigned. Ideal candidates will have strong written and verbal communications skills, the ability to multi-task, and a positive attitude.
Please email cover letter, resume, and availability to housedeminterns@gmail.com.
 MEM-275-15
MEM-272-15
The office of Congressman Jeff Fortenberry (NE-01) is seeking full and part-time interns for the fall semester in its DC office. Interns engage in a variety of tasks, and their responsibilities are assigned based on interests, capabilities, and the needs of the office. Interns will have the opportunity to hone their legislative research and writing skills and interact with senior legislative staff; attend hearings and briefings on Capitol Hill; assist with media/communications tasks
Page 18 of 19

 MEM-271-15
and gain proficiency in IQ; and participate in our office’s top priority, constituent outreach, by leading tours, greeting visitors, and answering phones. Exceptional interns in the past have gotten opportunities to write constituent letters and contribute to constituent and staff meetings on and around Capitol Hill.
If you are interested in applying for one of the most robust internship programs on the Hill, please submit a cover letter including the reason you would like an internship in Congressman Fortenberry’s office, your résumé, two writing samples, and references to NE01internships@gmail.com.
The Office of Congressman Paul D. Tonko offers unpaid internship opportunities for students and recent college graduates seeking to gain a better understanding of the legislative process. Interns in our office are offered a comprehensive learning opportunity that goes above and beyond a normal internship on Capitol Hill.
Part of an intern’s responsibilities in our office are fairly typical, including answering phones and helping with our mail program. However, they are also offered the opportunity to research and draft constituent correspondences on a wide variety of issues, provide Capitol tours to constituents, attend briefings both for staffers and for their own learning purposes, and assist with research for legislative staff members.
Every intern plays a critical role in the day-to-day operation of the office, and staff members do everything they can to ensure they receive a beneficial and rewarding experience here in our office.
Ideally looking for an intern who can start immediately or in early September and can intern at least 3 full days a week. Full-time preferred.
If you have any questions regarding our internship program, please do not hesitate to contact James Johnson by email at: james.johnson@mail.house.gov or by phone at (202) 225-5076.
 Page 19 of 19
