 ________________________________________________________________________
House Vacancy Announcement and Placement Service (HVAPS)
B-235 Longworth House Office Building Washington, D.C. 20515 202-226-5836
Vacancy Bulletins are available for pick-up in
Longworth HOB - B-227 (CAO First Call Customer Service Center) or in the CAO Human Resources Office - Ford HOB 102
To Subscribe or Unsubscribe to the Vacancy Listserv visit:
http://www.house.gov/content/jobs/
Job Line: 202-226-4504 _____________________________________________________________________________
 INTERNSHIP VACANCY LISTING
Week of January 4, 2016
 Rep. Xavier Becerra is looking for interns for his Leadership
office. Responsibilities include (but are not limited to) transcribing videos, collecting press clips, live-streaming briefings, supporting the Operations team in preparing Caucus events, answering phones, providing constituency outreach support to Democratic Members of Congress and their staff, conducting research, extracting and formatting large quantities of data, writing detailed memos, attending relevant briefings and meetings, and assisting with team projects. Applicants should be motivated, detail-oriented, possess excellent verbal and written communication skills, and be able to problem solve and multi-task. Experience or interest in social media is a plus. Women and minorities are strongly encouraged to apply.
Applicants must be either college/graduate students receiving academic credit or congressional internship/fellowship program participants. The intern should be prepared to start working in full-time.
Applications will be reviewed on a rolling basis. To apply, please send a cover letter and resume to caucusinternresume@mail.house.gov.
 MEM-450-15
Page 1 of 22

MEM-447-15
The Washington, DC office of Congresswoman Doris Matsui (CA-06) is seeking motivated, organized, and reliable interns to fill spring positions. Intern responsibilities include, but are not limited to, answering phones, conducting Capitol tours, sorting incoming mail, attending briefings, conducting legislative research and performing other administrative tasks as necessary. Successful candidates will possess excellent written and oral communication skills, a strong attentiveness to detail, an ability to work in a fast-paced environment, and an eagerness to learn about the political process and congressional affairs. California ties are a plus. Please send a résumé, cover letter and dates of availability
to Andrew.Heineman@mail.house.govwith “Internship” in the subject line.
The House Natural Resources Committee Democrats is seeking a full-time press intern. The ideal candidate must be detail-oriented, motivated, and able to multi- task efficiently. Applicants should possess strong written and oral communication skills and have an interest in working on environmental issues.
Daily responsibilities may include:
 Updating website content
 Updating social media channels (Facebook, Twitter, YouTube)
 Compiling daily press clips
 Video filming and editing
 Conducting research projects
 Drafting press materials (including e-newsletters, background
information, and press releases)
 Assisting with press events
This is an excellent opportunity for a candidate to gain substantive press experience in the environmental field. Interested candidates must be willing to commit to the full term of the internship, February to June (start and end date is flexible), and available to work from 9 a.m. to 5 p.m. daily. To apply, please submit a cover letter, brief writing sample, and resume to nrdems@mail.house.gov.
Representative Rick Larsen (WA-02) is currently seeking a full-time intern to start the second week of January with a flexible end date. Ideal candidates have excellent writing and research skills, a positive attitude, and a willingness to complete tasks as assigned. Intern responsibilities include researching and writing Congressional correspondence, helping constituents find information and fielding constituent phone calls. This internship also provides the opportunity to work closely with staff members and assist in various projects. Washington/West Coast ties are preferred, but are not required. If interested, please send a resume, cover letter and two references to: katy.nazaretova@mail.house.gov. Please include “WA-02 Internship” in the subject line. This internship is unpaid but office will assist in acquiring academic credit for internship.
 MEM-446-15
 MEM-443-15
 Page 2 of 22

MEM-442-15
MEM-441-15
California Democrat is seeking hardworking interns for the Spring 2016 internship session. Interns will conduct legislative research, compile press clips, assist with front office operations, help with constituent relations, coordinate and conduct tours, and learn from staff about the day-to-day operations of a congressional office. Ideal candidates will be hardworking, creative, critical thinkers with a good sense of humor. Strong communications and writing skills are crucial. Northern California ties are preferred, but not required. Please submit a cover letter, brief writing sample, and resume to bera.resume@mail.house.gov.
The Washington office of Rep. Mark Sanford (SC-01) seeks applicants for fulltime, unpaid, internships to begin immediately. Applicants should possess strong writing skills, be well organized, generally knowledgeable of legislative and related issues, able to complete tasks as directed, and have an eye for detail. Main duties include answering telephones, logging constituent calls, giving tours of the Capitol to visitors, opening and sorting mail, and assisting with other administrative tasks. Interns will have many opportunities to take on additional responsibilities within the office, at the discretion of staff. Anyone interested should send a resume and cover letter to SC01InternApplicants@mail.house.gov.
Florida Democrat is seeking a full-time, unpaid press intern for the Washington, D.C. office, starting immediately. The ideal candidate is detail-oriented, motivated, and able to multi-task efficiently. Applicants should possess strong written and oral communication skills. Preference will be given to candidates with Florida ties and those who speak Spanish.
Daily responsibilities may include:
• Updating website content;
• Compiling daily press clips;
• Video filming and editing;
• Conducting research projects;
• Drafting press materials (including e-newsletters, background information, and press releases);
• Assisting with press events; and
• Transcribing interviews
This is an excellent opportunity for a candidate to gain substantive press experience with an extremely active Member. Please email a one-page writing sample, résumé, and cover letter (all in .PDF format) addressing prior press experience or interests, to DCInternships.Grayson@mail.house.gov. Please use “Press Intern Application” in the subject line.
  MEM-439-15
  Congressman Fincher is currently seeking motivated college students to serve as
 interns for the 2016 Spring semester in his Washington, D.C. office. Intern
 responsibilities include: assisting the staff with general office duties, attending
 briefings and hearings, answering phones, sorting mail, giving Capitol tours, and
MEM-437-15
Page 3 of 22

 MEM-436-15
Congressman Perlmutter offers internships throughout the fall, spring and summer semesters for high school or college students. Students have the opportunity to learn about the inner workings of a congressional office to supplement their related course work. Students must receive some form of academic credit for their internship. Interns are responsible for working with their academic department and advisors to receive credit and comply with all other internship guidelines set by their educational institution.
Please submit a cover letter and resume if you are interested in an internship to Julia.harrington@mail.house.govif you would like to intern in our DC office.
In Washington, the hours are flexible to accommodate students' hectic course schedules, but generally run 9:00 a.m. to 6:00 p.m. when Congress is in session, and 9:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m. when not in session. Interns' responsibilities will vary from day to day. They will be asked to research legislation for the Member and legislative staff, attend hearings and briefings answer phones, and help with constituent communications on various issues before the House. As a result, interns learn about the legislative process and the many other functions of a congressional office. If you would like more information on Congressional Internships in Washington, DC, please contact Julia Harrington at Julia.Harrington@mail.house.gov.
Washington, D.C. — The House Democratic Caucus is looking for a full-time press intern for the spring semester with availability, beginning in
January 2016. Responsibilities include assisting with press clips, video production and editing, graphic design, tracking metrics, transcribing interviews and supporting team projects. Applicants should be self-starters, motivated, detail-oriented, possess excellent verbal and written communication skills, and be able to problem solve and multitask. Experience in Adobe Suite or other design software and proficiency in Spanish highly preferred. Experience and interest in press operations and the congressional process is a plus. Minorities are strongly encouraged to apply.
Applicants must be either college/graduate students or Congressional internship program participants. Interested candidates should send a resume and cover letter detailing availability to Miranda.Margowsky@mail.house.gov.
performing various other tasks based on ability and interests. Applicants must
 possess strong communication skills, have a positive attitude and be well-
 organized. Interested candidates should send a cover letter and resume to
 TN08.Intern@mail.house.gov. Tennessee ties preferred.
   MEM-435-15
  The office of Congressman Jim Costa is seeking interns who are interested in
 gaining hands-on experience in a congressional office. In our Washington office,
 internships allow individuals to actively observe the legislative process while
 participating in the administrative operations of a congressional office. Intern
 responsibilities include attending hearings, researching legislative issues,
 responding to constituent inquiries, processing tour and flag requests, opening
 and routing incoming mail, giving tours of the Capitol, and performing general
MEM-434-15
Page 4 of 22

  MEM-433-15
office duties.
Please email a resume, cover letter, and writing sample to Resumes.CostaInterns@mail.house.gov.
Florida Democrat is seeking interns for the Washington, D.C. office for the Spring 2016 semester. Candidates should be motivated, enthusiastic, and possess strong interpersonal skills. The internship will provide exposure to all areas of a legislative office. Interns will be responsible for assisting the team with phones, tour and flag requests, and other related front office duties. Additional tasks may include drafting constituent correspondence, research projects, and attending briefings and hearings. This is a great opportunity for individuals who are interested in learning about the workings of Capitol Hill and the legislative process in a busy office. Please email a cover letter and résumé in .PDF format to DCInternships.Grayson@mail.house.gov. In your message, indicate your specific full-time OR part-time availability with your anticipated starting and ending dates.
Energetic New York Democrat is seeking a highly motivated legislative intern to join his Washington, DC office for a part time unpaid internship this spring. Candidates should possess a professional and courteous demeanor, interest in the legislative process, excellent communication skills, the ability to multi-task, attention to detail, and a sense of humor. Main responsibilities include, but are not limited to, attending Congressional briefings, responding to constituent correspondence, assisting with flag requests, and general office duties. Candidates with New York ties and previous internship/work experience are strongly encouraged to apply. Please e-mail a resume, cover letter, and a short writing sample to NY.ResumeInbox@mail.house.gov. Equal opportunity employer. No calls or walk-ins please.
The office of a New York Congressman seeks an unpaid full-time press intern with exceptional writing and editing skills. Duties will include: authoring interesting and creative content for the website on various topics and other tasks as assigned. The intern must be highly motivated and have excellent writing and communication skills. All interested and qualified candidates should email a resume and two writing samples. Please submit all inquiries with the subject “Press Internship” to: NY.ResumeInbox@mail.house.gov.
The Office of Congresswoman Tulsi Gabbard (HI-02) is seeking a full- or part- time press intern for our Washington, D.C. office for the spring semester (January-May 2016). Candidates should be well organized, have good oral and written communication skills, and possess a strong interest in learning about press operations, the political process, and congressional affairs. The intern will assist in the day-to-day operations of a DC Congressional office by supporting members of staff with press clips and constituent communication and will help to draft press releases, prep memos, and social media posts, in addition to assisting
 MEM-432-15
 MEM-431-15
MEM-428-15
 Page 5 of 22

 MEM-427-15
with legislative research and administrative activities. Hawaii ties are appreciated but not necessary. Please note that this internship is unpaid. Interested candidates should send a resume, writing sample, and cover letter detailing availability to our intern coordinator, Andres Chovil, at Andres.Chovil@mail.house.gov. No calls or walk-ins please.
Congressman Jim Renacci (R-OH) seeks applicants for a part time/full time unpaid internship for the winter/spring of 2015. Responsibilities include, but aren’t limited to, answering phone calls, assisting with the mail program, providing constituent tours, attending various briefings, and providing research for the legislative staff. Qualified candidates will have exceptional writing skills, strong communication skills, ability to work in a fast paced working environment, and have an interest in learning more about the legislative process. Send a resume and a cover letter to Alex.Dominguez@mail.house.gov. Ohio candidates are strongly preferred.
  Rep. Xavier Becerra is looking for interns for his Leadership
office. Responsibilities include (but are not limited to) transcribing videos, collecting press clips, live-streaming briefings, supporting the Operations team in preparing Caucus events, answering phones, providing constituency outreach support to Democratic Members of Congress and their staff, conducting research, extracting and formatting large quantities of data, writing detailed memos, attending relevant briefings and meetings, and assisting with team projects. Applicants should be motivated, detail-oriented, possess excellent verbal and written communication skills, and be able to problem solve and multi-task. Experience or interest in social media is a plus. Women and minorities are strongly encouraged to apply.
Applicants must be either college/graduate students receiving academic credit or congressional internship/fellowship program participants. The intern should be prepared to start working in full-time.
Applications will be reviewed on a rolling basis. To apply, please send a cover letter and resume to caucusinternresume@mail.house.gov.
 MEM-426-15
MEM-425-15
The Office of Congresswoman Ann McLane Kuster (NH-02) is seeking qualified candidates to intern full time and part time in our Washington, D.C. office. Interns will have a chance to experience first-hand the operations of a U.S. Congressional office, learn about the legislative process, and gain Capitol Hill experience.
Responsibilities include administrative tasks such as answering phones, welcoming guests, and leading constituent tours. In addition, interns will be required to conduct legislative research, draft constituent correspondence and vote recommendations, attend briefings and hearings, and other projects as needed.
Page 6 of 22

 MEM-424-15
Candidates should have excellent writing and communication skills, strong organizational abilities, a good work ethic, an ability to work independently, and a drive to take initiative. Candidates with ties to the Northeast—especially New Hampshire—are preferred, but not required.
If candidates have any questions or wish to apply, please send a cover letter, resume, writing sample, and references to NH02.Internship@mail.house.gov. Please include “Last Name, First Name - Internship Application” in the subject line and include your available start and end dates and weekly schedule in the email.
Nevada Republican seeks a legislative intern for January 2016 and/or Spring 2016. Interns will work in a fast-paced Congressional Office, gaining valuable exposure and knowledge of the legislative process and the United States Congress. Intern responsibilities include greeting constituents, handling constituent phone calls, opening and sorting mail, guiding Capitol building tours, and assisting staff with administrative tasks. Interns will also have the opportunity to conduct legislative research, and assist with correspondence, as well as attend Capitol Hill briefings, congressional hearings, receptions, and press events.
Our office is looking for an intern with a positive attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Successful interns will be self- starters, take and listen to direction, and be willing to work both independently as well as part of a team environment. Applicants should have working knowledge of current events and policy topics, as well as a willingness to do assist with daily office tasks. Nevada ties strongly preferred.
Interns must be able to commit a minimum of three full days a week (9:00am- 6:00pm). Students welcome to apply. Those interested please send cover letter, updated resume, and references to kelsey.wolfgram@mail.house.gov.
Nevada Republican seeks an unpaid communications intern for January 2016 and/or Spring 2016. Interns will work in a fast-paced Congressional office, gaining valuable exposure and knowledge of the communications process and the United States Congress. Communication intern responsibilities include tracking and reporting on social media and news story comments, drafting social media posts, establishing and managing a twitter account, and reaching out to local/national reporters on social media. Interns will also have the opportunity to attend events and committee meetings to take photos and videos, work with the communications director to put press releases on the website, and assist with writing projects at the discretion of the communications director. Interns will also help facilitate our constituent communications program and guide constituents on tours of the US Capitol building.
Our office seeks an intern with a positive attitude, strong work ethic, and Page 7 of 22
 MEM-423-15

 MEM-422-15
excellent written and oral communication skills. Successful interns will be self- starters, take and listen to direction, and be willing to work both independently and as a member of a team environment. Applicants must have a working knowledge of current events and policy topics as well as a willingness to assist with daily communication tasks. Nevada ties strongly preferred.
Interns must be able to commit a minimum of three full days a week (9:00 am- 6:00 pm) with the option of working full-time, spring semester beginning in January. Students are welcome to apply. If interested, please send a cover letter, updated resume, sample of a social media post for a congressperson, and references to kelsey.wolfgram@mail.house.gov.
Congresswoman Candice S. Miller (R-MI) seeks legislative interns for the Spring 2016 semester. Interns will work in a fast-paced congressional office, gaining valuable exposure and knowledge of the legislative process and the United States Congress. Intern responsibilities include greeting constituents, managing constituent phone calls, and assisting staff with administrative tasks. Interns will also have the opportunity to conduct legislative research, assist with constituent correspondence, and attend legislative briefings, congressional hearings, receptions, and press events.
Interns must have a good attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Successful interns will be able to find information with little assistance, be able to work both independently as well as part of a team environment, and possess a strong attention to detail. Applicants should have working knowledge of current events and policy topics, as well as a willingness to perform a variety of tasks and administrative functions. Michigan ties are preferred, but not required. To apply, please send cover letter and resume to mi10intern@gmail.com.
Rep. Charles Rangel's Office seeks self-motivated and professional college students or recent college graduates for a part-time or full-time spring internship, from January to May 2016. Intern responsibilities include, but are not limited to: answering phones, leading Capitol tours, conducting research on various legislative issues, attending hearings, preparing follow-up memos, processing constituent correspondence mail and other administrative duties. This internship presents an opportunity for both a unique learning experience and an inside look at the political process.
Applicants must be hard-working, have strong writing and communication skills and have a demonstrated interest in public policy. This is an unpaid internship. New York ties a plus. Please send a resume, cover letter, a 2-3 page academic writing sample to CBR.intern13@mail.house.gov and a fill out the intern application found here.
The Washington, DC office of Congresswoman Doris Matsui (CA-06) is seeking Page 8 of 22
 MEM-421-15
  MEM-420-15

  MEM-416-15
motivated, organized, and reliable interns to fill winter/spring positions. Intern responsibilities include, but are not limited to, answering phones, conducting Capitol tours, sorting incoming mail, attending briefings, conducting legislative research and performing other administrative tasks as necessary. Successful candidates will possess excellent written and oral communication skills, a strong attentiveness to detail, an ability to work in a fast-paced environment, and an eagerness to learn about the political process and congressional affairs. California ties are a plus. Please send a résumé, cover letter and dates of availability to Austin.Laufersweiler@mail.house.gov with “Internship” in the subject line.
Congresswoman Lois Frankel’s (FL-22) DC office seeks interns for the Spring semester, from January to May 2016. The position requires a high deal of professionalism and efficiency, as well as strong writing and communication skills. The ideal candidate is organized, diligent, and positive. Duties include: answering telephone calls, responding to general constituent inquiries and requests for tours, assisting with constituent correspondence, and providing administrative assistance to the legislative staff. Undergraduate students or recent college graduates preferred, South Florida ties a plus. Women and minorities are encouraged to apply. Interested applicants should send a resume and cover letter to: olivia.hodge@mail.house.gov. Please include your availability in your cover letter.
The Office of Congressman Sam Graves (MO-06) is currently accepting applications for his Spring 2016 internship program in his Washington, D.C. office. The office is seeking highly qualified candidates who are motivated, detail-oriented, and personable.
Ideal candidates must be able to multi-task, have outstanding oral and written communication skills, and a desire to learn about the legislative process. Interns will have the opportunity to experience working on Capitol Hill, learn about the different career opportunities, and attend briefings of interest. Responsibilities will include answering the phone, giving tours of the Capitol, assisting with constituent correspondence, and supporting the staff on various projects. Missouri or Midwestern ties are preferred. Interested candidates should email a resume and cover letter to Abigail.Camp@mail.house.gov.
The office of Congresswoman Jackie Walorski (IN-02) is seeking a full-time communications intern for her Washington D.C. office for Spring of 2016. Ideal candidate must possess strong writing skills, be detail-oriented and professional. Intern will work directly with the communications director and members of the media. Responsibilities would include writing releases, monitoring social media and developing media strategies. Position is unpaid and serves to provide professional and educational value to participants. Office is flexible in allowing interns to attend hearings and briefings as well as work with LA’s on issues of their interest. Potential applicants must be willing to work in a fast-paced environment and be interested in learning more about the legislative process. Candidates with photography and graphic design experience strongly encouraged
 MEM-415-15
 MEM-414-15
Page 9 of 22

 MEM-413-15
to apply.
Please send resume and cover letter to internship.in02@gmail.com. No phone calls, please.
The office of Congresswoman Jackie Walorski (IN-02) is seeking full-time interns for her Washington D.C. office for Spring of 2016. Ideal candidate would be professional, dependable and possess strong writing skills and work ethic. Responsibilities include phone assistance, constituent correspondence, Capitol tours and other legislative projects. Positions are unpaid and serve to provide professional and educational value to participants. Office is flexible in allowing interns to attend hearings and briefings as well as work with LA’s on issues of their interest. Candidates must be willing to work in a fast-paced environment and be interested in learning more about the legislative process.
Please send resume and cover letter to internship.in02@gmail.com.
No phone calls, please.
The Democratic Staff of the Committee on Science, Space and Technology is seeking paid and unpaid interns for the spring starting in January. Interns are asked to work with staff to help prepare for committee hearings and markups. Interns will work on substantive research projects and press matters. Additionally, interns are critical to the daily operation of the office including tasks such as answering phones, greeting visitors, and filing official documents. Interested applicants should visit the Committee’s website at http://democrats.science.house.gov/internships. Please fill out the application provided and send in a resume.
Minnesota Democrat seeks intern applicants for the Washington, D.C. office during the 2016 spring semester. Interns should expect to primarily assist with front office operations, but will also get opportunities to conduct legislative research, and obtain first-hand and comprehensive knowledge of the day-to-day operations of a Congressional office.
Interns will assist staff with front office duties, including sorting mail, answering telephones, data entry, and list building tasks. Assist legislative and communications staff on projects as needed. Perform research, attend briefings, and assist with constituent correspondence. Greet visitors, conduct tours of the Capitol, and other assignments as needed.
Candidates should demonstrate excellent oral and written communication skills and have a good understanding of the legislative process. Qualified applicants will be organized, dependable, able to multi-task, willing and quick to learn, able to work in a fast-paced environment and have a good sense of humor.
 MEM-412-15
 MEM-411-15
Page 10 of 22

 MEM-410-15
Internships are unpaid, but we are happy to work with your College or University to receive academic credit for your internship.
Minnesota ties and full-time availability are preferred, but not necessary.
To apply, please submit a resume and cover letter here.
Congressman Gus Bilirakis (FL-12) seeks applicants for full and part-time internships in his Washington, D.C. office for the spring semester. Washington, D.C., interns are responsible for assisting staff with day-to-day functions within the D.C. office, including but not limited to constituent correspondence and legislative research. They may also assist constituents in their visits to Washington, D.C., providing tours of the U.S. Capitol. The ideal candidate will be a college student or recent graduate who is motivated, possesses strong writing and organizational skills and is willing to jump in wherever needed with a positive attitude. A congressional internship provides unparalleled value and insight into the workings of a Capitol Hill office and the legislative process, as well as networking opportunities and exposure to important issues before Congress. While the internship is unpaid, college credit is available. Both part- time and full-time applicants will be considered. Florida ties preferred, but not required. To apply, please email a current resume, cover letter, and writing sample (500 words) with the subject line “Spring Internship” to FL12Resumes@gmail.com.
Congressman Vern Buchanan (R-FL-16) has full-time and part-time, unpaid internships available for the spring session (December - May) in his Washington, DC office. Duties include but are not limited to answering telephones, greeting visitors, conducting tours of the Capitol, researching legislative issues and writing letters. There will also be opportunities to experience Washington DC and attend briefings, classes and hearings.
Qualified candidates should possess excellent organizational and communication skills, should have a positive attitude, and a strong work ethic. Although internships are unpaid, our office is happy to fill out any necessary forms for students to receive credit at their respective college or university.
All interested individuals should submit a cover letter and resume to sheila.heiman@mail.house.gov with “2015 Spring Internship” in the subject line. Include in your cover letter why you would like to intern for Congressman Buchanan’s Washington Office, why you believe you are qualified, and your availability. Potential candidates will be contacted via email.
The Office of Congressman Raul Ruiz (CA-36) seeks highly-motivated, qualified interns with excellent research and communication abilities to join his District offices in Palm Desert and Hemet, California as part of the Spring 2016 Congressional Internship Program. Although congressional interns are unpaid they are considered an integral part of the office and are given an opportunity to
 MEM-409-15
 MEM-408-15
Page 11 of 22

 MEM-407-15
expand their knowledge about public policy and the legislative process.
Congressional intern responsibilities may include, but are not limited to, conducting research for staff members, assisting staff at community or public events, attending meetings, transcribing documents, and providing general constituent services in the form of answering phone calls. Congressman Ruiz’s internship program also features staff-lead workshops designed to develop essential and professional skill that students may apply in any setting.
Students interested in applying for a congressional internship in one of the offices of Congressman Raul Ruiz have the opportunity to apply to the Spring 2016 session. Applications will be accepted on a rolling basis. Prospective interns should complete an internship application (available here: https://ruiz.house.gov/services/internships), attach their resume, and submit to Tony Aguilar at tony.aguilar@mail.house.gov
The Office of Congressman Tom McClintock (CA-04) is seeking full or part-time winter/spring interns for his Washington, D.C. office. Applicants should possess conservative values and hold strong written and verbal communication skills. Position duties include: attending Congressional hearings, leading Capitol tours, answering phones, sorting mail, and assisting legislative staff with research.
While this is an unpaid internship, we are happy to work with current students looking to receive college credit for their internship. Recent graduates are welcome to apply. Interested applicants should send their resume and availability to Rachel.Long@mail.house.gov. Please use “2016 McClintock Internship” in the subject line. No phone calls, drop-ins, or faxes, please.
The Office of Congresswoman Susan W. Brooks (IN-05) is seeking full-time and part-time interns in her Washington, D.C. office. The internship would take place over the Spring term, beginning in January and lasting through May (start and end dates flexible). The office is looking for both legislative and press interns. Legislative responsibilities include researching legislation for the Member and legislative staff, answering constituent letters on various issues before the House, and leading U.S. Capitol tours. Press responsibilities include assisting the communications director with gathering news clips, drafting releases, and maintain social media. Interns will also partake in administrative duties such as answering phones and maintaining the office’s constituent database. Candidates should be motivated and have a desire to learn about the legislative process. Strong verbal and interpersonal skills required. Indiana ties preferred, but not required. If interested, please submit an application on our website, susanwbrooks.house.gov. Please refer to the “services” tab, click on internships, and submit your application. In the comments section, please indicate whether you are interested in legislative, press, or both. Any questions can be directed to mimi.strobel@mail.house.gov.
 MEM-406-15
 Page 12 of 22

MEM-405-15
MEM-404-15
The Office of Majority Whip Steve Scalise (LA-01) is seeking interns for Winter and Spring. Interns will be placed on a rotational program through both the leadership and personal offices of Congressman Scalise. Previous Hill internship experience and/or Louisiana ties are preferred, but not required. Please send any resumes and cover letters to John Woodard at John.Woodard@mail.house.gov.
The Washington, DC office of Congresswoman Lucille Roybal-Allard is seeking motivated, organized, and reliable individuals to fill winter/spring internship positions. Intern responsibilities include, but are not limited to, answering phones, conducting Capitol tours, sorting incoming mail, attending briefings, conducting legislative research and performing other administrative tasks as necessary. Successful candidates will possess excellent written and oral communication skills, a strong attentiveness to detail, an ability to work in a fast-paced environment, and an eagerness to learn about the political process and congressional affairs. Spanish-fluency, California ties, and full-week availability are all plusses. Please send a résumé, cover letter, a short writing sample (no longer than one page), and dates of availability to jhostyn.duval@mail.house.gov with “Intern” in the subject line.
The Washington, DC office of Congressman Ruben Gallego (D-AZ) is seeking enthusiastic and motivated interns for Spring 2016.
The ideal candidates will interact well with constituents, be able to multitask, and have a strong interest in public service. Excellent research and writing skills are crucial. Arizona ties are a plus, but not required.
Interns will have the opportunity to gain experience working on Capitol Hill and learn firsthand about the workings of a Congressional office. Responsibilities include answering the phone, guiding tours of the Capitol, assisting with constituent correspondence, and attending briefings and hearings. Internships are unpaid, but the office will fill out any necessary forms for students to receive academic credit.
Interested applicants should send a cover letter, resume, and a 2-5 page writing sample to AZ07Internships@mail.house.gov with the subject line “Name— Spring Internship Application.” Cover letters should include the applicant's anticipated availability for the duration of the internship; writing samples may be excerpts of larger works. Interns will begin early to mid-January, depending on their availability, and end in mid-May. Applications will be considered on a rolling basis, and qualified candidates will be contacted for an interview.
The Office of Rep. Scott Rigell (VA-02) is seeking politically Conservative unpaid Spring 2016 interns in their Washington, DC, office to begin in December/ January through May. The Office seeks an outgoing, enthusiastic person with at least 3 days/week availability who would like experience working in a Congressional Office. Virginia ties are a plus but not required. Interested persons should submit resume to Julie.Moorhead@mail.house.gov.
  MEM-403-15
 MEM-399-15
 Page 13 of 22

MEM-396-15
The Office of Congressman Sam Farr (D-CA) is looking to hire full and part-time unpaid Legislative Interns to work in our Washington, DC office. The internship will begin Jana and go through March. You’ll be responsible for attending hearings and briefings, providing administrative support, guiding Capitol tours, conducting legislative research, drafting correspondence and a variety of policy related projects to assist legislative staffers. Excellent time management skills, a healthy sense of humor, creativity and a strong commitment to teamwork are qualities we’re looking for. CA ties a plus, but not required.
If you’d like to be considered for a Legislative Internship position, please send a cover letter with your availability and resume to Dushani.desilva@mail.house.gov with “Legislative Intern Application” in the subject line. Applications will be reviewed on a rolling basis. Please no phone calls.
Congressman Lloyd Doggett (D-TX) is seeking Internship applicants for his Washington, DC office for Spring 2016. These positions offer a unique opportunity to help respond to individuals who need help with a federal problem, and to learn about broader community and national concerns. Interns assist staff with constituent services and legislative research. If you are interested in interning, email Lloyd.Doggett@mail.house.gov with your resume and three references, a writing sample, and advise when you would be available. Candidates should have a strong work ethic and a positive attitude. Texas ties and Spanish skills a plus.
The Office of Rep. Tom Graves (GA-14) is seeking full and part-time interns for the Winter/Spring 2016 semester in its Washington D.C. office. Applicants should possess strong written and verbal communication skills and a strong work ethic. Intern responsibilities include, but are not limited to, assisting the staff with general office duties, answering phones, responding to constituent mail, researching legislative issues, leading Capitol Hill tours, and attending briefings and hearings. Although internships are unpaid, our office is happy to fill out any necessary forms for students to receive credit at their respective college or university. Interested candidates should send a cover letter and resume to Ryan Diffley at Ryan.Diffley@mail.house.gov. State ties preferred, but not required.
The Office of Congressman David N. Cicilline (D-RI) is seeking full-time and part-time interns for the 2016 Spring semester (January – May) in its Washington, D.C. location.
The ideal candidate will have excellent research and writing skills, be able to multi-task, and interact well with constituents. Interns will have the opportunity to gain experience working on Capitol Hill, learn about the legislative process, and attend briefings of interest. Responsibilities include answering the phone, guiding tours of the Capitol, assisting with constituent correspondence, and supporting the legislative and communications staff on various projects.
 MEM-395-15
 MEM-394-15
 MEM-393-15
Page 14 of 22

 MEM-392-15
Internships are unpaid, but both full-time and part-time positions are available. Hours are 9-6 when Congress is in session, and 9-5 out of session. To apply, please visit https://cicilline.house.gov/serving-you/internships or email Annika.Lichtenbaum@mail.house.gov with a resume and one-page writing sample.
The Washington, DC office of Congressman Luis V. Gutiérrez (IL-04) is seeking motivated, organized, and reliable individuals to fill internship positions in the Spring of 2016.
Intern responsibilities include, but are not limited to, answering phones, conducting Capitol Tours, sorting incoming mail, attending briefings, conducting legislative research and performing other administrative tasks.
Successful candidates will possess excellent written and oral communication skills, a strong attentiveness to detail, an ability to work in a fast paced environment, an eagerness to learn about the legislative process, as well as a minimum four day per week availability. Spanish-fluency and Illinois ties are a plus. Internships are unpaid.
Please send a résumé, cover letter, and dates of availability to gutierrezopportunities@gmail.com with “Intern Spring 2016” in the subject line.
The House Committee on Energy and Commerce Democratic Staff seeks qualified graduate and undergraduate interns for the spring 2016 semester. An internship with the House Energy and Commerce Committee is designed to give students a thorough understanding of a Congressional committee’s role in the legislative process. Throughout the course of their internship, interns will assist staff with administrative tasks such as answering phones, organizing documents, and running errands around the Capitol complex. In addition, interns will have the opportunity to perform legislative research, shadow staff at hearings, and assist in drafting letters and memos on subjects within the Committee’s broad jurisdiction.
If you are interested in applying, please send a resume, cover letter, and two references to InternshipResume.EC@mail.house.gov.
The Office of Congressman Michael Capuano (D-MA) is looking for full-time interns to aid our administrative and legislative teams. Responsibilities include: researching legislative issues, attending legislative hearings, answering phone calls, processing constituent mail, leading tours of the U.S. Capitol, and assisting in any other special projects/tasks that may arise. Applicants should be self- motivated, reliable, hardworking, and have strong communication skills. Massachusetts ties preferred, but not required.
Winter internships start in January and run through the end of April/May. Internships are unpaid, but academic credit is available.
 MEM-391-15
 MEM-390-15
Page 15 of 22

 MEM-389-15
MEM-388-15
Interested candidates should submit a resume, cover letter, and a one-page writing sample in PDF format to eliza.ramirez@mail.house.gov.
The Washington, D.C. office of Congressman Dan Donovan (NY-11) is seeking applications for full- or part-time, unpaid interns for the Spring semester. Applicants must be willing to work at least two full days a week. Interns will be responsible for answering phones, talking with constituents, scheduling and giving tours of the U.S. Capitol, attending briefings and hearings for legislative staff, and supporting the office with any additional duties. Interested candidates should email a current resume, cover letter, and a list of three references, with the subject line “Spring Internship” to NY11Resumes@mail.house.gov.
The Democratic office of the Committee on House Administration seeks energetic and self-motivated undergraduate or graduate level students as well as recent graduates with an interest in government and public policy to apply for its Winter/Spring 2016 internship. Working closely with Committee staff, interns will have the opportunity to gain first-hand knowledge of the inner-workings of a congressional committee and learn about the day-to-day administrative operations of the House of Representatives. Interns are responsible for assisting Committee staff with official proceedings (hearings/markups), elections oversight, member services, and other projects as well as providing general front office support. Please note that this is not a paid internship. Interested applicants should send a cover letter, resume, and available hours to CHADem.Intern@mail.house.gov with the subject headline, “CHA Dem Internship."
The Office of Congressman Curt Clawson (R-FL) is seeking full-time and part- time interns for the 2016 Spring semester (January – May) in its Washington, D.C. location.
The ideal candidate will have excellent research and writing skills, be able to multi-task, and interact well with constituents. Interns will have the opportunity to gain experience working on Capitol Hill, learn about the legislative process, and attend briefings of interest. Responsibilities include answering the phone, guiding tours of the Capitol, assisting with constituent correspondence, and supporting the legislative and communications staff on various projects.
Internships are unpaid, but the office will fill out any necessary forms for students to receive academic credit. Full-time and part-time positions are available, and hours are 8:30 – 5:30 on available days. Please contact Alex.Krueger@mail.house.gov with a resume and one-page writing sample to apply.
Congressman Ted W. Lieu’s internship program offers college students a unique opportunity to learn about the functions of the U.S. House of Representatives, as well as the Congressman’s work as the representative of CA-33, which includes parts of Los Angeles, the West Side, and the South Bay.
  MEM-387-15
 MEM-385-15
Page 16 of 22

 MEM-384-15
An internship with Congressman Lieu presents a variety of opportunities to participate in the daily operations of a Congressional District Office.
General intern responsibilities include:
Answering telephones, data entry, responding to constituent requests, assisting with special projects such as legislative research, assisting with constituent casework, and other miscellaneous tasks, as required.
In the busy atmosphere of a Congressional office, it is imperative that interns conduct themselves in a mature, professional manner, are well organized, able to take initiative, follow instructions, perform well under pressure, and work as an integral part of a team.
Skills required include:
Effective and professional phone manner, computer experience, good typing ability, punctuality, attention to detail, ability to follow instructions, ability to complete tasks efficiently and thoroughly, maturity, empathy, professionalism, and discretion.
This internship is unpaid. Congressman Lieu supports students requesting credit for their internship through their school or university. The deadlines for each internship sessions are as follows: Spring- December 11th, Summer- April 1st, Fall- August 5th. Preference will be given to residents of CA-33.
Please note that because of the competitive nature of the internship program, internship positions are available to college students only. Part time and full time internships are available.
If you would like to apply for our internship program please send your resume, cover letter, and writing sample to internship.lieu@mail.house.gov with your name and the term in the subject line. If you have any questions regarding the application, please contact the Intern Coordinator, Ashley Fumiko Dominguez at internship.lieu@mail.house.gov or 323-651-1040.
Congressman Ted W. Lieu serves on the House Committees on the Budget and Oversight & Government Reform. He is also the Democratic Freshman Class President and a Lieutenant Colonel in the Air Force Reserves.
Congressman Dave Loebsack (IA/02/D), member of the House Energy and Commerce Committee, is currently hiring spring interns for his Washington, D.C. office. Interns are responsible for answering phones, sorting mail and faxes, giving tours of the Capitol, and assisting with constituent correspondence. Other tasks may include attending briefings and hearings, letter writing, and assisting press staff. Intern candidates should be current or recent college students, regardless of major. To apply please email your cover letter, resume, a short writing sample and a letter of recommendation to LoebsackInternship@mail.house.gov. No phone calls or drop-ins please.
 Page 17 of 22

MEM-378-15
Congressman Coffman (R-CO) seeks hard-working, enthusiastic legislative interns for the Spring 2016 semester in his Washington, DC office. Interns are responsible for: giving tours of the U.S. Capitol, answering constituent calls, sorting constituent correspondence, assisting legislative staff with research and writing, processing U.S. flag requests, attending Congressional briefings and hearings, and attending events with the Congressman as necessary. Applicants should have strong written and oral communication skills, exceptional interpersonal skills, and have demonstrable interest in public policy and government. Attractive applicants will have completed at least 60 credit hours of undergraduate coursework. Those with Colorado ties and professional proficiency in Spanish are encouraged to apply. Applicants should be aware that this is an unpaid internship that tentatively lasts from January through May 2016. To apply, please visit: http://coffman.house.gov/services/internships.
Intern needed to start immediately. Remainder of Fall 2015 & Spring 2016
We are seeking energetic and proficient interns in the Washington, D.C. office of Congresswoman Corrine Brown (FL05). An internship in Congresswoman Brown’s office will provide valuable experience to students as they prepare for their professional careers.
Interns have the opportunity to work with and assist all members of the staff, including legislative, administrative, outreach and press duties. Washington, DC interns will be encouraged to take advantage of the many hearings, workshops and seminars that are held on Capitol Hill.
In addition, we are happy to work with your college or university to arrange for academic credit. Applicants should be highly motivated and enthusiastic self- starters.
Responsibilities include:
• Supporting administrative staff: answering phones, database entry, and sorting mail.
• Supporting legislative staff: tracking constituent correspondence, drafting letters, and conducting research.
• Attending briefings and hearings for legislative staff.
• Compiling Social Media Post.
• Promoting constituent outreach efforts by communicating with constituents and constituent groups, attending meetings and events, and drafting correspondence.
Application process: Applicants should send a cover letter, availability and a resume. Those interested in a Washington, DC internship should email Brown.Website@mail.house.gov.
The Office of Congresswoman Eleanor Holmes Norton (D-DC) is seeking a full- time or part-time intern for the Spring of 2016. This is an opportunity to learn
 MEM-376-15
 MEM-374-15
Page 18 of 22

 MEM-373-15
about the inner-workings of a congressional office on the Hill in a fast-paced work environment. The internship allows access to briefings and interesting events related to a wide range of important issues. Responsibilities will include, but are not limited to, attending Congressional briefings, giving tours of the Capitol, conducting research, responding to constituent inquiries, and processing tour and flag requests. Qualified applicants should possess a professional and courteous demeanor, excellent communication skills, the ability to multi-task, fastidious attention to detail, and interest in the legislative and governmental process. To apply, please send a resume, three references, writing sample, and cover letter to william.washington@mail.house.gov, with the subject ‘Norton Internship.’ No phone calls or drop-ins please.
The Washington, D.C. office of Representative Buddy Carter (GA-01) is currently seeking applicants for the fall semester. Internships are available to qualified college students seeking college credit or recent college graduates. Positions are unpaid and serve to provide professional and educational value to participants as well as an understanding of our federal legislative process. Georgia ties are preferred, but they are not required. Responsibilities include but are not limited to: providing tours of the Capitol, answering phones, helping staff process constituents’ mail and inquiries. Other responsibilities may include assisting staff with legislative research, writing meeting briefings, and attending committee hearings. Candidates should possess an interest in the legislative process, strong communication skills, along with organizational skills. If you are interested in being considered for an internship, please send your resume, cover letter, and any relevant writing samples to Hart.Thompson@mail.house.gov. No drop-ins please.
The Committee on Science, Space, and Technology, Republican Staff is currently seeking interns for Spring 2016 (available to start in January).
Interns perform a variety of tasks that support the staff in our legislative and media work. Legislative tasks may include, but are not limited to, legislative research, assembling information, assisting staff during hearing and markup preparation and execution, and attending hearings, markups, briefings and meetings. Media work may include assisting staff to organize and staff Committee press conferences and assisting with the production of daily news clips relating to Committee’s issues. Undergraduate Interns are also trained to perform administrative duties, such as answering phones, and sorting and distributing mail.
Interested applicants should email their cover letter and resume to Brian Corcoran at brian.corcoran@mail.house.gov.
Democratic Member of Congress seeks full-time or part-time unpaid Congressional interns to begin immediately. The responsibilities of a Congressional intern primarily focus on helping the Congressman communicate
 MEM-371-15
 MEM-370-15
Page 19 of 22

 MEM-369-15
with his 700,000-plus constituents. Interns will assist the team with phones, mail, tours of the U.S. Capitol Building, and related front office duties. Additional tasks, including drafting correspondence, research projects, and attending hearings may be assigned on a case by case basis.
Candidates should possess excellent communication skills (both verbal and written) and an understanding of the functions of the United States Congress. Ideal candidates are positive, energetic, and eager to assist with the legislative and administrative needs of the staff. West Coast ties are preferred. Please send a resume, cover letter, and writing sample to andy.hackbarth@mail.house.gov.
Congresswoman Suzan DelBene seeks late fall/winter interns for her Washington, D.C. office. Interns will work in a fast-paced and fun congressional office, gaining valuable experience and knowledge of the United States Congress. Intern responsibilities include greeting constituents and handling constituent phone calls, assisting staff with administrative tasks, conducting research, and assisting with constituent correspondence. Additionally, interns will have the opportunity to lead tours of the U.S. Capitol as well as attend hearings and briefings for the legislative staff. The ideal candidates will possess exceptional written and oral communication skills, a high degree of professionalism, as well as a strong interest in public service. Prospective interns should be able to commit at least 16 hours per week. Washington state ties are a plus, but are not required. Interested applicants should send a current resume and cover letter to Internship.DelBene@mail.house.gov. No phone calls please.
The Office of Rep. Rich Nugent (R-FL-11) is seeking a highly motivated intern for its office in Washington, DC. Successful candidates will be organized, hard- working, and detail-oriented. Intern will be responsible for assisting staff with legislative and administrative duties such as greeting visitors, drafting constituent correspondence, answering phones, and leading Capitol tours. Intern will also have opportunities to attend staff briefings and committee hearings to gain firsthand knowledge of the legislative process. The position is unpaid, and the intern is responsible for finding housing in the DC area. Florida ties preferred. If interested, please send a cover letter, resume, and available dates to fl11internship@gmail.com. No phone calls or walk-ins, please.
The office of Congressman Marlin Stutzman is seeking an unpaid intern in the Washington, D.C. office for the 2016 spring semester. Responsibilities will include but are not limited to: answering phones, sorting constituent mail, attending committee hearings and briefings for staff, assisting in legislative research, and giving tours of the U.S. Capitol. Applicants should possess excellent written and verbal communication skills, be self-motivated, and able to work as part of a professional team. Hill experience not necessary.
To apply, send resume and cover letter to in03internship@gmail.com.
The Washington, D.C. office of Congresswoman Maxine Waters, Ranking
 MEM-366-15
 MEM-365-15
MEM-363-15
 Page 20 of 22

 MEM-362-15
Member of the Committee on Financial Services, is offering winter/spring internship opportunities for students and recent graduates. First-hand experience in Congresswoman Waters’ office will provide interns with an unparalleled knowledge and understanding of public policy and the legislative process. Intern responsibilities include drafting letters to constituents, attending committee hearings, writing press releases, researching various issues for the legislative staff, and assisting with additional office duties.
The internship provides different professional development opportunities with staff to discuss their experiences on the Hill and future employment strategies. Applicants should e-mail a cover letter, resume, and a one to three page writing sample to Sean Higgins at Sean.Higgins@mail.house.gov.
A Tennessee House Republican seeks full-time and part-time interns to begin as soon as possible for the spring 2016 semester. Duties will include:
• Conducting legislative research and writing memos,
• Attending Congressional hearings and briefings on behalf of the staff, • Welcoming guests,
• Handling constituent communications, and
• Giving tours of the Capitol.
College students, recent graduates, and those with an interest in tax, budget, and health care policy are encouraged to apply. Tennessee ties are a plus, but not required. Interested applicants should send a resume and cover letter detailing their interest and time commitment they are willing to make to meghan.oakes@mail.house.gov.
Congressman Dave Reichert’s Washington, DC office is looking for energetic and hard-working interns to start as soon as possible. Qualified candidates should have an interest in American government and working in a fast-paced political environment.
All interns are expected to effectively communicate with staff members and constituents. Daily tasks include, but are not limited to; administrative duties, leading tours of the United States Capitol Building, communicating with constituents and other offices on Capitol Hill, writing briefings and memos, conducting research, and experiencing the city of Washington, DC. Interns will also have the opportunity to attend hearings and meetings on a wide range of topics.
All internships are unpaid. However, if your college or university offers credit hours, we are happy to complete any necessary evaluations. In addition, housing is not provided but assistance will be offered.
If you are energetic, hard-working, and interested in a position in Rep. Reichert’s Washington, DC office, please contact Isaac Tobis at 202-225-7761 or send your
 MEM-360-15
Page 21 of 22

 MEM-358-15
resume and a cover letter to Isaac.tobis@mail.house.gov.
Congressman Paul Cook’s Washington, D.C. office is now accepting internship applications for the Winter 2015 and Spring 2016 term. Interns are invaluable multifunctional team members who manage an array of administrative tasks and traffic flow in the office, relieving the pressure on the legislative team for daily committee and voting activities. Interns will be responsible for assisting the team with phones, mail, tours, flag-requests, and related front office duties. Additional tasks, including drafting correspondence, research projects, and attending hearings may be assigned on a case by case basis. Ideal candidates are positive and energetic, have excellent people and organizational skills, and are eager to assist with the legislative and administrative needs of the staff.
Undergraduate and post-graduate students are eligible to apply. Positions are unpaid and serve to provide professional and educational value to participants, but students have the opportunity to gain academic credit. California ties are preferred. If interested, please contact our office at Kassandra.Taira@mail.house.gov with "Internship" in the subject line. Please include cover letter, resume and a writing sample.
Congresswoman Candice S. Miller (R-MI) seeks legislative interns for the Spring 2016 semester. Interns will work in a fast-paced congressional office, gaining valuable exposure and knowledge of the legislative process and the United States Congress. Intern responsibilities include greeting constituents, managing constituent phone calls, and assisting staff with administrative tasks. Interns will also have the opportunity to conduct legislative research, assist with constituent correspondence, and attend legislative briefings, congressional hearings, receptions, and press events.
Requirements: Interns must have a good attitude, strong work ethic, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Successful interns will be able to find information with little assistance, be able to work both independently as well as part of a team environment, and possess a strong attention to detail. Applicants should have working knowledge of current events and policy topics, as well as a willingness to perform a variety of tasks and administrative functions. Michigan ties are preferred, but not required. To apply, please send cover letter and resume to mi10intern@gmail.com.
 MEM-357-15
 Page 22 of 22
