 ________________________________________________________________________
House Vacancy Announcement and Placement Service (HVAPS)
B-235 Longworth House Office Building Washington, D.C. 20515 202-226-5836
Vacancy Bulletins are available for pick-up in
in the CAO Human Resources Office - Ford HOB 102
To Subscribe or Unsubscribe to the Vacancy Listserv visit:
http://www.house.gov/content/jobs/
Job Line: 202-226-4504 _____________________________________________________________________________
INTERNSHIP VACANCY LISTING
Week of October 28, 2019
    time congressional interns for his Washington, D.C. office. Candidates should be motivated, flexible, and detail-oriented individuals with availability beginning in January, and a preference for those who can stay at least three months. Pennsylvania ties are a plus but are not required.
Intern responsibilities include answering constituent phone calls, leading tours of the Capitol, sorting mail and faxes, and assisting experienced staff with projects in diverse issue areas. Candidates should be outgoing and possess strong oral and written communication skills, an ability to multitask in a fast-paced environment, and a good sense of humor. Candidates with Pennsylvania ties are strongly encouraged to apply.
Please e-mail a resume and cover letter including desired start date and weekly availability to lamb.tours@mail.house.gov
  MEM-547-19
Congressman Conor Lamb (PA-17) has Spring 2020 openings for full and part-
MEM-546-19 The Office of Congressman Jared Huffman (D-CA) seeks a Communications/Digital Fellow. Qualified candidates will have strong writing, editing, and social media skills, as well as basic familiarity with graphic
 Page 1 of 25

design/video editing software. One to two years of experience in a press or digital media role (including internships) preferred. California ties are a plus!
This position requires the ability to thrive under pressure, multi-task, and
work in a team environment. Candidates must have strong written and verbal communication skills, with the desire to come up with creative communications ideas and the ability to work under tight deadlines. The fellow will work closely with the Communications Director and the legislative staff of Congressman Huffman.
Responsibilities include:
●Drafting social posts
●Maintaining/updating website
●Designing graphics + editing photos/videos
●Assisting with drafting speeches, press releases, op-eds, advisories, and other written materials
●Creating and maintaining media lists
Interested applicants should email a resume, two writing samples, and two digital samples to huffmanpressfellow@gmail.com with the subject line “Last Name - Press Fellow.” This is a full time position and offers a monthly stipend
     full-time interns for the fall 2019 semester (October – December) with the possibility of extension through the spring 2020 semester. Interns will be responsible for providing staff members with policy and administrative support. Duties may include answering phones, compiling press clips, attending staff briefings, performing legislative and policy research, and other tasks.
This internship is open to undergraduates (juniors and above) and recent graduates. The office is an equal opportunity employer and minorities, women, and LGBTQ persons are encouraged to apply. Please note that this internship is unpaid.
If you would like to be considered, please submit a one-page resume and cover letter to housesmallbusinessinternshipr@gmail.com and include “Fall 2019 Internship Application” in the subject line of the email.
 MEM-545-19
The House Small Business Committee Minority Staff is currently looking for
MEM-544-19
The Office of Congressman Tom Malinowski (NJ-07) is currently seeking qualified candidates for their Spring 2020 internship program in the Washington D.C. office. This internship runs from January to May. Ideal candidates will be professional, motivated, dependable, a team player, and be able to show strong written and verbal communication skills.
Responsibilities include, but are not limited to, answering phones, assist with writing constituent correspondence, Capitol tours, attending Congressional
 Page 2 of 25

hearings and briefings, assisting legislative staff and producing press clips. Interns will work closely with legislative staff on interested issue areas and assist with the Congressman’s committee work.
Applicants must be able to commit to a full-time schedule (35-40 hours per week) and must be enrolled in a college or graduate program to be eligible for the position. Applicants with New Jersey ties, previous internship/ work experience, and receiving educational credit are strongly preferred. Start date is in early January.
Please e-mail a resume, cover letter, and writing sample (1 page only) in a single PDF document to nj07.interns@mail.house.gov with “(Last name) - Paid Spring Internship.”
No calls or drop ins. Deadline to submit applications is Nov. 5th.
     qualified candidates for an unpaid internship for Spring 2020 in the Washington D.C. office. This internship runs from January to May but considers the availability of the applicant. Ideal candidates will be professional, motivated, a team player, and be able to show strong written and verbal communication skills.
Responsibilities include, but are not limited to, answering phones, assist with writing constituent correspondence, Capitol tours, attending Congressional hearings and briefings, assisting legislative staff and producing press clips. Interns will work closely with legislative staff on interested issue areas and assist with the Congressman’s committee work.
Applicants should be able to commit to a part-time schedule (15-25 hours per week). Applicants with New Jersey ties and have previous internship/ work experience are a plus, but not required.
Interested applicants should e-mail a cover letter (1 page only), resume, writing sample and available dates in a single PDF document to nj07.interns@mail.house.gov with “(Last name) - Unpaid Spring Internship” in the subject line.
No calls or drop ins. Deadline to submit applications is Nov. 5th.
 MEM-543-19
The Office of Congressman Tom Malinowski (NJ-07) is currently seeking
MEM-542-19
The Office of Congressman Matt Cartwright (PA-08) is seeking candidates for a part-time or full-time paid internship able to start immediately in our Washington, D.C. office. Responsibilities will include drafting memos and constituent letters, assisting legislative staff with research, answering phones, managing the front office, giving Capitol tours, greeting constituents, and other tasks as assigned.
 Page 3 of 25

Send resume and cover letter only to Alexander.Heldring@mail.house.gov with “Fall Intern Application” in the subject line. Pennsylvania ties are strongly preferred. The office is an equal opportunity employer and encourages women, minorities, and LGBTQ candidates to apply.
  MEM-540-19
The Office of Congressman Harley Rouda (CA-48) is seeking a paid Press/Digital Intern in his DC office.
Qualified candidates will have strong writing, editing, and social media skills, as well as basic familiarity with graphic design/video editing software. California ties are a plus!
This position requires the ability to thrive under pressure, multi-task, and work in a team environment.
Responsibilities include:
•Drafting social posts
•Compiling daily press clips
•Assisting with speechwriting •Maintaining/updating website
•Designing graphics + editing photos/videos
Interested applicants should email a cover letter, resume, short writing sample/portfolio to ca48resumes@gmail.com with "Press/Digital Intern" in the subject line.
  MEM-538-19
Democratic Congressman seeks applicants for full or part-time congressional internship for Spring. Duties will include conducting legislative research, drafting memos, assisting with front office duties, and performing basic administrative tasks. Candidates must exhibit strong writing and communication skills.
California residents or strong ties to San Diego are preferred. Candidates should be prepared to work a minimum of 10 hours per week. Please send a resume, cover letter, writing sample (1-2 pages), and availability (start and end dates as well as days per week) to CA52Internship@mail.house.gov with “Last Name, First Name, CA52 Internship” in the subject line.
     temporary paid position in his Washington, D.C. office. The intern will assist with the greater communications operation, but will focus on digital media content creation.
Intern responsibilities include but are not limited to social media content generation, website maintenance, analytics, photography, videography, media monitoring and staffing the member. Candidates will have a keen eye for design,
MEM-537-19
Congressman Andy Levin (D-MI) is seeking a Digital Media Intern for a
Page 4 of 25

a desire to grow and learn in the political communications space, knowledge of graphic design and video editing, a positive attitude and a sense of humor. Candidates of all backgrounds are encouraged to apply.
To apply, please send a resume, cover letter, a writing sample, graphic design sample and a link to a video using the subject line “Digital Media Intern” to MI09.Resumes@gmail.com
  MEM-536-19
The House Foreign Affairs Committee Majority Staff is currently looking for a legal intern for the Spring 2020 semester.
In addition to providing administrative and operations support to the committee as needed, the legal intern will work closely with the Counsels team with research projects, drafting legislation, providing support for full committee markups and hearings, and attending meetings and briefings. Candidates should be current law students and require little supervision. Minorities, women, and LGBTQ persons are strongly encouraged to apply.
If you would like to be considered for an internship please submit a one-page resume and cover letter in PDF format to hcfa.democrat@mail.house.gov and include “Spring 2020 Legal Internship Application” in the subject line of the email.
  MEM-535-19
The Office of Congresswoman Katherine M. Clark [MA-05] is currently seeking full-time & part-time paid interns for Spring 2020 in her Washington, D.C. office. Qualified applicants should have strong oral & written communication skills, the ability to manage multiple tasks, the willingness to work in a fast-paced environment, and be comfortable assisting constituents. A sound knowledge of Microsoft Office, a solid work ethic as well as a basic understanding of the political process in Congress is expected.
Responsibilities include but are not limited to: answering and screening phone calls, leading capitol tours, working with staff to research legislative issues and process information, attending congressional briefings, assisting with administrative tasks, drafting constituent correspondence on a variety of issues, assisting the communications team with various tasks, and other projects as they arise.
Full-time and part-time positions are available beginning in January 2020. To apply, please send a resume, cover letter, and a brief writing sample to RepClarkInternships@mail.house.gov. Please indicate availability and expected start date.
     join his Washington, DC office in early to mid-November. Candidates should be
MEM-534-19
Congressman John Garamendi (CA-03) is seeking a highly motivated intern to
Page 5 of 25

professional, quick learners, and phenomenal team players. Strong oral and written communication skills and close attention to detail are imperative.
Duties include assisting staff with legislative, administrative, and press related projects, writing memos and talking points, attending hearings and meetings, answering constituent phone calls, leading tours of the US Capitol, assisting with scheduling, sorting and distributing mail, and managing tour and flag requests.
Full-time candidates with California ties and previous internship/work experience are preferred. This is an paid internship. Please e-mail a resume, cover letter and dates of availability to Garamendi.Internships@mail.house.gov.
  MEM-530-19
Marisol del Carmen Rodriguez was a faithful and tireless advocate of civic engagement. Marisol herself was afforded a public service internship that led to a lifelong commitment to the ideals of enriching and empowering all people in her community. Through this fellowship, Marisol will continue her legacy of service, education and a selfless dedication to the betterment of her community.
The Marisol del Carmen Rodriguez Congressional Fellowship is a fully funded fellowship program in Congresswoman Sylvia R. Garcia’s Washington, DC office. It is a competitive program awarded to outstanding students with a demonstrated interest in public service or public policy and strong ties to the 29th Congressional District of Texas.
The fellow will gain hands-on office experience while learning about the legislative process. They will work closely with staff conducting research, drafting letters, and preparing for hearings. Other responsibilities will include leading Capitol tours, answering and screening telephone calls, managing the front office, tracking media coverage, and other duties as necessary.
Qualified applicants have strong writing and communication skills, the ability to manage multiple tasks, a strong sense of professionalism and demonstrate a solid work ethic. English and Spanish bilingual candidates are strongly encouraged to apply.
The position is available beginning in January 2020. To apply, send a resume and cover letter to ellie.valega@mail.house.gov with the subject “Marisol Rodriguez Congressional Fellowship”. In your cover letter please indicate expected start and end dates, hours available to work, and if course credit is available for this internship.
This office is an equal opportunity employer: Women and minorities are strongly encouraged to apply. This office does not discriminate on the basis of race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity and expression, national origin, disability military status, age, marital status, or parental status.
  Page 6 of 25

MEM-529-19
“The Republican Office of the Committee on Science, Space, and Technology seeks energetic and self-motivated undergraduate or graduate-level students, as well as recent graduates, with an interest in government and public policy for a Spring 2020 internship. Working closely with Committee staff, interns will have the opportunity to gain first-hand knowledge of the inner-workings of a congressional committee and learn about the day-to-day administrative operations of the House of Representatives.
Interns are responsible for assisting Committee staff with official proceedings (hearings/markups), oversight, research, assisting with phone inquiries and providing support to all Committee staff. Background in science is a plus. To apply, please send your resume and cover letter to house.science.committee@mail.house.gov.”
  MEM-528-19
Southern Democratic Member of Congress seeks both full-time and part-time interns for their Spring 2020 paid internship in the Washington, D.C. office. Responsibilities include answering phones, researching legislation for the Member and legislative staff, attending hearings and briefings, running errands, drafting constituent correspondence, and other tasks as assigned.
Applicants should have excellent written and verbal communication skills, and work well under pressure in a fast-paced environment. No drop-ins or phone calls.
Please email nchousejobs@gmail.com with the subject line “Spring 2020 - Internship Application” and attach a resume, writing sample, and include information regarding your full-time or part-time availability.
The office is an equal opportunity employer, and diverse candidates are encouraged to apply.
     2020 interns for our Washington, D.C. office. Responsibilities will include drafting memos and constituent letters, assisting legislative staff with research, answering phones, managing the front office, giving Capitol tours, greeting constituents, and other tasks as assigned.
Preferred candidates are current college students or recent graduates who work well under deadlines, pay close attention to detail, have a strong work ethic, have excellent customer service skills, and work well on a team. Nevada ties are strongly preferred, but not required. Women, LGBTQ+, and minority candidates are encouraged to apply. All applicants will be considered without regard to race, color, national origin, religion, sex, gender identity, disability, or age.
Interested candidates should send a resume and cover letter to NV03Resumes@gmail.com with “Spring Intern” in the subject line by COB
 MEM-527-19
The Office of Congresswoman Susie Lee is seeking full-time, unpaid Spring
Page 7 of 25

Friday, November 15, 2019. Please indicate expected start and end dates in your cover letter. No phone calls or walk-ins please.
 MEM-526-19
The Office of Congressman Anthony Brindisi (NY-22) is seeking candidates for a full-time paid internship for the Spring 2020 Semester in our Washington, D.C. office.
Responsibilities include but are not limited to answering phones, conducting legislative research and analysis, attending briefings/hearings, leading Capitol tours, and managing the front office.
New York ties are preferred but not required. To apply, please send a resume, cover letter, and a writing sample to Kevin.Porter@mail.house.gov with the subject line “Spring Internship Application”.
  MEM-525-19
Congressman Alcee L. Hastings (FL-20) is seeking enthusiastic and highly motivated applicants for a full or part-time unpaid internship starting January 2020.
Candidates should possess a strong interest in the legislative process. Strong oral and written skills and close attention to details are imperative. Interns are considered an integral part of the team and will have the opportunity to gain experience working on Capitol Hill and learn firsthand about the workings of a Congressional office.
Responsibilities will include conducting legislative research, drafting memos and responses to letters from constituents, assisting constituents and visitors to the office, and attending briefings and hearings. Congressman Hastings supports students requesting credit for their internship through their school or university.
Please e-mail a resume, cover letter, writing sample and dates of availability to internship.alhastings@mail.house.gov with “Internship" in the subject line. No phone calls or walk-ins will be accepted.
     for internships in the Congressman’s D.C. office for the spring of 2020. Duties include drafting constituent correspondence, greeting constituents and answering phones, performing legislative research, leading tours of the Capitol, attending policy briefings and meetings, and conducting research and additional tasks to assist the Congressman’s staff.
We’re looking for college students or recent graduates who are motivated, detail- orientated, and ready to work in a fast-paced setting. A positive attitude and an interest in politics are a must. District 8 or Indiana ties are preferred but not required. To apply for the position, please follow the directions outlined on the
MEM-524-19
The office of Congressman Larry Bucshon (IN-08) is currently seeking applicants
Page 8 of 25

Congressman’s website here: https://bucshon.house.gov/constituent- services/internships.htm
     MEM-523-19
The Washington D.C. office of Congressman Ken Buck (CO-04) is currently accepting internship applications for the Spring of 2020. Typical duties will include answering phones, leading Capitol tours, researching legislation for the Member and legislative staff, attending hearings and briefings, and answering constituent letters on a variety of issues. The ideal candidate for this paid internship will be team-oriented and have strong written and verbal communication skills.
Students and recent graduates interested in learning more about our country’s legislative process are encouraged to apply. The Congressman sits on both the Judiciary Committee and the Foreign Affairs Committee, making this an ideal opportunity for those interested in law and/or foreign policy. Colorado ties are preferred but not required.
All interested applicants should e-mail their resume and a brief writing sample to Zach Mendelovici at Zach.Mendelovici@mail.house.gov with the subject line “Spring 2020 Internship.”
  MEM-522-19
The Majority Staff of the Select Committee on the Climate Crisis seeks full or part-time Legal Interns for an early to mid-January start date, running through April 2020. Responsibilities may include conducting legislative research, producing legal analyses on proposed climate and environmental policies, attending briefings and hearings for staff, and other tasks as assigned or needed.
The ideal candidate will be detail-oriented, self-motivated, reliable, and have excellent writing and communications skills. An interest in environmental law is strongly desired; this internship is geared towards those in 2L or 3L programs in Washington, DC.
Please send a resume and cover letter to SCCCDjobs@mail.house.gov with “Winter/Spring Legal Intern” in the subject line by November 15, 2019. Please include your approximate dates of availability in the message, and how many days per week you would be available. The office is an equal opportunity employer, and diverse candidates are encouraged to apply. No calls or drop-ins please.
  MEM-521-19
The Majority Staff of the Select Committee on the Climate Crisis seeks full or part-time Interns for an early to mid-January start date, running through April 2020. Responsibilities may include conducting administrative tasks for the committee, attending briefings and hearings for staff, conducting research projects, preparing and assembling materials for Committee hearings and events, and other tasks as assigned or needed.
 Page 9 of 25

MEM-520-19
The Office of Congressman Doug Collins (GA-09) is looking for candidates for an internship in his Washington, D.C. office. We are looking for highly qualified candidates that are motivated, detail-oriented, personable, and have a passion for public service. The ideal candidates will have excellent research and writing abilities, be able to multi-task and interact well with constituents visiting the office and on the phone.
Interns will have the opportunity to experience working on Capitol Hill, learn about the legislative process, and attend briefings of interest. Responsibilities include answering the phone, researching and preparing policy memos, giving tours of the Capitol, assisting with constituent correspondence, supporting the communications staff among many other projects.
Qualifications:
•Current student or recent graduate interested in politics and gaining legislative experience
•Exhibits passion for politics, government, and/or any related policy areas
• Excellent verbal and written communication and interpersonal skills
•Ability to multitask independently, learn quickly, and demonstrate sound judgment
•Exhibits great attention to detail, punctuality, respect, and initiative
•Ability to work and contribute in a highly collaborative, team environment Benefits:
•Working closely with the representative and Chief of Staff
•Observation of internal campaign operations and preparation for campaign and political jobs
•Opportunity to bolster organizational and communication skills
•Attend special events, political meetings, and congressional hearings
•Meals and snacks will regularly be provided at events and activities
Interested candidates should email a resume and cover letter to Raymond Sweney, at raymond.sweney@mail.house.gov
MEM-518-19
The ideal candidate will be detail-oriented, self-motivated, reliable, and have excellent writing and communications skills. An interest in environmental, climate change, or science policy is strongly desired and preferred.
Please send a resume and cover letter to SCCCDjobs@mail.house.gov with “Winter/Spring Intern” in the subject line by November 15, 2019. Please include your approximate dates of availability in the message, and how many days per week you would be available. The office is an equal opportunity employer, and diverse candidates are encouraged to apply. No calls or drop-ins please.
    The Office of Congressman Mark Pocan (D-WI) is seeking full and part-time
   Interns for the Washington, D.C. office starting at the end of December or early January. Interns in our office perform legislative and administrative work while
Page 10 of 25

gaining valuable career and educational experience. Specific duties include drafting constituent correspondence, attending policy briefings and committee hearings, performing legislative research, producing daily press clips, and supporting staff members on various projects of interest.
Qualified candidates are organized and detail-oriented, responsible, willing to learn, able to work cooperatively, possess strong oral and written communication skills, and are committed to public service. Wisconsin ties and sense of humor are a plus! Candidates of all backgrounds are encouraged to apply.
To apply, please submit a form on our website at:
https://pocan.house.gov/services/internships/congressional-internship-application
or send a resume, cover letter, and a brief writing sample to Sydney.Scott@mail.house.gov with “Winter 2020 Pocan Internship” in the subject line.
For further information regarding the internship program, please see the internship page on our website at: https://pocan.house.gov/services/internships/. We also highly encourage every applicant to apply to our scholarship program after submitting an application. The application can be found here: https://pocan.house.gov/scholarship-program.
        the United States Representative for one of the largest non-state districts in the nation. Texas-23 stretches from San Antonio to El Paso and encompasses 820 miles of border. Prior to Congress, Hurd served for nearly a decade as an undercover CIA officer and helped start a cybersecurity company. The third-term Congressman is known for his bipartisan work on national security, border security, and cybersecurity.
An internship in the Washington, DC office encompasses a variety of tasks and assignments such as answering phones, greeting visitors, giving Capitol tours, writing letters, and assisting with media clips. In addition, interns may be assigned to work with the legislative team and outreach staff to assist with legislation, special projects, writing, and/or research.
The ideal intern should be responsible, focused, enthusiastic, able to work cooperatively with Congressional staff, and possess excellent oral and written communications skills. Schedule is flexible and stipends may be available. Texas ties preferred. Spanish speaking skills preferred, but not required.
To apply for an internship, please email your resume and a brief cover letter to Reilly.Knecht@mail.house.gov with “2019 Spring Internship” in the subject line. In your email, please specify your dates of availability. “
 MEM-517-19
“San Antonio-native and fighting Texas Aggie, Congressman Will Hurd serves as
Page 11 of 25

MEM-516-19
Congressman Jim Himes (CT-04) is currently seeking interns for the Spring/Winter 2020 Internship Program. Applicants should be dependable, team- oriented, and have a strong desire to work for the residents of Connecticut’s 4th District.
This position is an exciting opportunity to gain first-hand knowledge of how the legislative process works. Congressional interns are expected to draft constituent correspondence, attend briefings and Congressional hearings, prepare memoranda and daily press clips, and lead Congressional tours.
Please apply by submitting your application materials through the internship page on himes.house.gov. Please be sure to put Winter/Spring 2020 in the subject line when applying. A need-based stipend may be available and the schedule is flexible. The application deadline is November 1st, 2019. Connecticut ties preferred but not required.
  MEM-515-19
MEM-511-19
Congressman Jim Himes (CT-04) has an immediate opening for our Fall 2019
   internship program. Applicants should be dependable, team-oriented, and have a strong desire to work for the residents of Connecticut’s 4th District. This position is an exciting opportunity to gain first-hand knowledge of how the legislative process works. Congressional interns are expected to draft constituent correspondence, attend briefings and Congressional hearings, prepare memoranda and daily press clips, and lead Congressional tours.
Please apply by submitting your application materials through the internship page on himes.house.gov. Please be sure to put Fall 2019 in the subject line when applying. A need-based stipend may be available and the schedule is flexible.
 The Office of Congressman Pete Stauber is seeking part-time or full-time interns
   for the Spring of 2019. Responsibilities will include answering phones, managing the front office, giving Capitol tours, greeting constituents, assisting legislative staff with research, assisting with constituent letters, and other tasks as assigned.
Preferred candidates are current college students or recent graduates who have excellent customer service skills, have a strong work ethic, and pay close attention to detail. Qualified candidates will also have strong oral and written communication skills and be able to work well on a team. Minnesota ties are strongly preferred.
Internships include a monthly stipend and the office will work with current students to receive college credits. Interested applications should send their resume, brief cover letter, and references to Eric.Gebhart@mail.house.gov. Please indicate expected start and end dates as well as hours available to work in your cover letter.
  Page 12 of 25

MEM-510-19
The Office of Congresswoman Susie Lee is seeking Fall 2019 interns for our Washington, D.C. office. Responsibilities will include answering phones, managing the front office, giving Capitol tours, greeting constituents, assisting legislative staff with research, and other tasks as assigned.
Preferred candidates are current college students or recent graduates who work well under deadlines, pay close attention to detail, have a strong work ethic, have excellent customer service skills, and work well on a team. Nevada ties are preferred, but not required. Women, LGBTQ+, and minority candidates are encouraged to apply. All applicants will be considered without regard to race, color, national origin, religion, sex, gender identity, disability, or age.
Interested candidates should send a resume and cover letter to NV03Resumes@gmail.com with “Fall Intern” in the subject line. No phone calls or walk-ins please.
     investigative body of the House of Representatives, is seeking full- and part-time interns for the remainder of the fall semester. Interns will have the opportunity to work with the administrative, policy, and press teams, conducting research, assisting during hearings and markups, and helping with other administrative tasks as necessary.
This position is available immediately and would go through December, with the potential for extending into the spring semester. Specific dates for this internship will be determined on a case-by-case basis, and preference will be afforded to those who are available at least 15 hours a week.
Applicants must be strong writers, organized, and detail-oriented, as they will balance multiple, often disparate, projects corresponding with the broad jurisdiction of the Committee. The strongest candidates will also exhibit discretion in working on confidential matters and be enthusiastic and knowledgeable about the Committee’s work. Previous experience on Capitol Hill is desired, but not required. The position is unpaid, but we are happy to work with an applicant so they can receive class credit.
Interested individuals should submit a cover letter and resume to oversight.committee@mail.house.gov. Please place "INTERN" in the subject line. Applications will be reviewed on a rolling basis.
 MEM-509-19
The Republican Staff of the Committee on Oversight and Reform, the chief
MEM-508-19 The Republican Staff of the Committee on Oversight and Reform, the chief investigative body of the House of Representatives, is seeking full- and part-time law clerks for the remainder of the fall semester. Law Clerks will have the opportunity to work with the oversight and policy teams, conducting researching, reviewing documents, and preparing for hearings and markups. Law clerks will
 Page 13 of 25

balance multiple, often disparate, projects corresponding with the broad jurisdiction of the Committee.
This position is available immediately and would go through December, with the potential for extending into the spring semester. Specific dates for this internship will be determined on a case-by-case basis, and preference will be afforded to those who are available at least 15 hours a week.
Applicants must be current law school students or recent graduates of law school who are organized and detail-oriented. Strong writing and blue booking skills are also necessary. The strongest candidates will also exhibit discretion in working on confidential matters and be enthusiastic and knowledgeable about the Committee’s work. This position is unpaid, but we are happy to work with an applicant so they can receive class credit.
Interested individuals should submit a cover letter and resume to oversight.committee@mail.house.gov. Please place "LAW CLERK" in the subject line. Applications will be reviewed on a rolling basis.
     part-time legislative and press interns for spring 2020. Responsibilities include but are not limited to conducting legislative research, answering phones, attending briefings and hearings for staff, compiling press clips, drafting content, and other tasks depending on the needs of the Committee and the intern’s interests.
Qualified candidates will have strong oral and written communications skills as well as a desire to help veterans and learn about the House and legislative process.
Apply by submitting an application at https://veterans.house.gov/contact/internship and sending a resume and cover letter to veterans.internships@mail.house.gov. Applications are considered on a rolling basis. Student veterans preferred, but not required.
This internship is unpaid, students receiving outside funding or school sponsorship are preferred.
  MEM-507-19
The Democratic Staff of the House Committee on Veterans’ Affairs seeks full or
MEM-505-19
The Office of Congressman Greg Murphy (NC-03) is currently seeking paid interns with our DC office for the Spring 2020 session. The internship would begin in January and last until early May. Our specific dates are tentative on the release of the official House schedule.
This is a great opportunity to gain hands-on experience and knowledge over the day-to-day happenings within Congress. The internship is an ideal fit for any student that is interested in politics, law or government – however, any interested
 Page 14 of 25

student is encouraged to apply! Interns will assist the legislative staff by conducting policy research, answering phones, leading tours, and helping with administrative tasks.
Qualified candidates should:
• Be a current undergraduate or graduate student, or have recently graduated
• Demonstrate an interest in politics, policy and/or public service
• Have strong communications and writing skills.
• Be hard-working, dependable, detail-oriented and professional.
The deadline to apply for the Spring Session is Friday, November 15th. Interested candidates should address their application materials to Collin Sabine at Interns.NC03@gmail.com. Applications should include a cover letter, resume, and what the individual’s internship schedule may look like.
  MEM-504-19
The Office of Congressman Denny Heck (D-WA) is seeking applicants for paid full-time or part-time Fall 2019 internships in Washington, D.C. Responsibilities include answering phone calls, greeting visitors, leading tours of the Capitol, drafting letters to constituents, attending briefings and hearings, and helping conduct research for various projects.
Ideal candidates will have a meticulous attention to detail, strong writing skills, an ability to work in a fast-paced environment, and an enthusiasm for the political process and congressional operations. Pacific Northwest ties preferred but not required.
Interested applicants should send a resume, cover letter, and two references to noelle.gasper@mail.house.gov with “Fall 2019 Internship” in the subject line.
     Spring 2020 in Washington, D.C. Interns will assist the legislative and administrative staff, attending briefings, answering phones, coordinating and conducting tours, drafting constituent correspondence letters, performing legislative research and analysis, and various other tasks. District and Florida ties are encouraged but not required. No phone calls or drop ins, please.
To apply, email a single PDF including your resume, 1-2 page writing sample, and cover letter listing your availability to FL13.Internships@mail.house.gov.
 MEM-503-19
Congressman Charlie Crist (FL-13) is seeking Full time or Part Time interns for
MEM-502-19
The Office of Rep. Ro Khanna (D-CA) seeks Press/Legislative interns for the upcoming winter/spring 2020 term.
Press responsibilities will include building press lists, drafting social media posts for the Member’s official social media pages (including Facebook, Twitter, and Instagram), designing graphics, and creating short video clips as needed. The intern will be an integral part of the communications team, generating engaging content for the Member and supplying creative ideas throughout the week. Ideal
 Page 15 of 25

applicants will have a background in iMovie, the Adobe creative suite, and TweetDeck.
Legislative responsibilities include researching legislation for both the Member and legislative staff, attending hearings and briefings, and drafting constituent letters on the Member’s behalf.
This is a unique opportunity to gain both legislative and communications experience in a fast-paced and high-volume congressional office.
All interns are paid $15.00 per hour for a maximum of 30 hours a week, and are expected to work collaboratively with the staff to answer phones, greet constituents, and guide tours of the U.S. Capitol Building. The Office of Rep. Ro Khanna is an equal opportunity employer. We do not discriminate based on race, ethnicity, gender, sexual orientation, religion, national origin, age, or socio- economic status. All are welcome and encouraged to apply.
Applicants should send a resume, a short writing sample (no more than 2-pages), sample tweets on a current event, a sample graphic (optional) and availability to julia.albertson@mail.house.gov.
  MEM-501-19
Congressman Dwight Evans (PA-03) is seeking highly motivated interns for the Winter/Spring of 2020. Strong communication skills required. Must be dependable and a team player.
Duties include answering constituent phone calls and inquiries, attending congressional briefings and hearings, conducting research for legislative staff, compiling press clips for the communications team, and leading Capitol tours. Interns will gain valuable professional experience and inside knowledge of the legislative process on Capitol Hill.
Minorities, women, and LGBTQ persons are encouraged to apply. Philadelphia or Pennsylvania ties preferred but not required. Qualified candidates should send a resume and cover letter to Matthew.Holcombe@mail.house.gov with the subject line “Spring 2020 Internship.”
  MEM-500-19
The Office of Congresswoman Gwen Moore (WI-04) is seeking a press intern to assist with a fast-paced communications operation for Spring 2020 (starting at the beginning of January 2020). This is a paid position. Qualified candidates will have strong writing, editing, event planning, social media, graphic design, and photography skills, and be able to work on tight deadlines. Selected candidates will also be expected to perform standard administrative duties.
Intern responsibilities include:
* Social media content development * Event photography
 Page 16 of 25

* Compiling press clips * Clipping videos
* Creating graphics
* Drafting press releases * Answering phones
Interested applicants should email a cover letter, resume, short writing sample, and dates of availability to GwenMoorePress.Moore@mail.house.gov with “Spring 2020 Press Internship” in the subject line. We also recommend, but do not require, applicants submit 1-3 sample graphics.
  MEM-499-19
The office of Congresswoman Rosa L. DeLauro is accepting applications for the Spring 2020 internship program in the Washington, DC office. Applicants should have an ability to work in a fast-paced environment, possess excellent writing skills, and an enthusiastic attitude.
Intern responsibilities include supporting legislative and press staff, attending hearings and briefings, answering constituent phone calls, leading US Capitol tours, organizing constituent mail, greeting office visitors, and various ad hoc projects. For application information, please visit https://delauro.house.gov/services/internships. Please email your completed application to Harper.White@mail.house.gov
Applicants and employees shall not be discriminated against with respect to compensation, terms, conditions, or privileges of employment, because of such person’s race, color, religion, sex, age, national origin, service in the military, disability or sexual orientation.
      applicants in the D.C. office for Spring of 2020. Qualified applicants should possess strong communication skills, be interested in learning about the legislative process, and have a willingness to work in our fast-paced office.
Responsibilities would include answering phones, leading tours of the Capitol, attending policy briefings and meetings, and conducting research and additional tasks to assist the Congressman’s staff. Ohio ties are preferred but not required.
Interested applicants should send resume, cover letter and availability to intern.OH06@gmail.com.
 MEM-497-19
Congressman Bill Johnson’s office (OH-06) is currently seeking internship
MEM-496-19 “A Midwest Republican House Member is seeking paid interns for the Fall 2019/Spring 2020 session in his Capitol Hill office. The Spring session dates are January 13th-May 15th, but more flexibility can be offered. The internship schedule is also flexible to accommodate classes. Interns will have the opportunity to attend committee hearings and briefings for staff members, assist
 Page 17 of 25

MEM-493-19
in the constituent correspondence process, as well as assist with other constituent services.
Responsibilities include: taking phone calls, processing constituent mail, and performing other general office duties. Ideal applicants should be interested in the legislative process, enthusiastic, reliable, and hard-working. Full or part time internships with flexible schedules are available. Ties to the Midwest are preferred but not required.
Interested candidates should e-mail their resume and cover letter to Dylan.Jones@mail.house.gov. Please specify what your internship schedule may look like, including preferred start/end dates.”
  MEM-494-19
Congressman Jodey Arrington (TX-19) is seeking highly motivated interns to
   join his Washington D.C. team in January for a 4-5 month paid internship. Candidates should be motivated, professional, quick learners, and phenomenal team players. Strong oral and written communication skills and close attention to detail are important.
Duties include assisting staff with legislative, administrative, and press related projects, writing memos and talking points, attending hearings and meetings, answering constituent phone calls, leading tours of the US Capitol, and sorting and distributing mail.
Full-time candidates with Texas ties and previous internship/work experience are preferred. Please e-mail a resume, cover letter and dates of availability to marisa.burleson@mail.house.gov
 Republican Florida Office Searching for Paid Spring Interns.
   Florida ties preferred but not required. Full and Part Time Internships available.
TITLE: Intern
REPORTS TO: Intern Coordinator/Supervisor
CORE RESPONSIBILITIES:
•to assist in performing research, processing the mail, data entry, reception duties and other office errands.
QUALIFICATIONS:
•good oral and written communication skills;
•ability to work cooperatively and courteously with others; •good organizational skills; and
•responsible, dependable and willing to learn.
DUTIES:
•performs research (CRS, the Library of Congress, MIN, or other available resources);
Page 18 of 25

•sorts and distributes mail;
•attends committee meetings, intern conferences, and seminars;
•performs data entry, which involves logging in letters and constituent requests, including names and addresses of constituents;
•answers the telephones;
•notes constituent opinions, including their full names, addresses, and all relevant information;
•greets visitors and signs for deliveries; and
performs other duties as assigned by the Intern Supervisor
Please submit applications to Carl.Schuler@mail.house.gov please include a resume and writing sample.
     full-time, paid interns for the Spring semester. Interns are asked to work with staff to help prepare for committee hearings and markups and will work on substantive research and oversight projects in addition to press matters. Furthermore, interns will be critical to the daily operation of the office including tasks such as answering phones, greeting visitors, and filing official documents.
Interested applicants should visit the Committee’s website at https://science.house.gov/contact/internships. Please fill out the provided application and attach a resume. No calls or drop-ins please.
 MEM-492-19
The Democratic Staff of the Committee on Science, Space and Technology seeks
MEM-491-19
The Office of Congresswoman Gwen Moore (WI-04) is seeking a highly motivated full-time intern for Spring 2020 (starting at the beginning of January 2020). This is a paid internship. Qualified candidates will be dependable team players, capable of excelling in a fast-paced office, and will possess strong writing, editing, verbal communication, and organizational skills. Experience with research is a plus since there are opportunities to work with the legislative staff on relevant issues.
This position’s responsibilities include serving as a primary contact with constituents, greeting visitors, providing Capitol Tours, and assisting with projects assigned from other staff members. These projects often include assisting with data entry or drafting correspondence.
Interns will have the ability to attend Capitol Hill briefings, hearings, and other informative events that are available. Interns will also have the opportunity to gain professional and educational experience while learning more about Congress and the legislative process. Wisconsin ties are a plus.
Interested applicants should email a cover letter, resume, short writing sample, and dates of availability to maryah.thompson@mail.house.gov with “Spring 2020 Internship” in the subject line.
  Page 19 of 25

MEM-490-19
Congressman Jason Smith (MO-08) is currently seeking full or part-time interns to work in his Washington, DC office for the Spring 2020 term from January to May.
Primary intern responsibilities include answering phones, interacting with residents of the district in person or over the phone, sorting mail, leading Capitol building tours, reviewing legislative correspondence, and assisting staff with administrative and research tasks. Interns will also have opportunities to conduct legislative research and attend staff briefings, Congressional hearings, and press events.
The ideal candidate has a positive attitude, disciplined work ethic, strong attention to detail, and excellent written and oral communication skills. Ties to Missouri are preferred but not required. Please note state ties in your cover letter or email.
Those interested should send a resume and cover letter to Zach.Wong@mail.house.gov with “Spring Internship” in the subject line. Applications are reviewed on a rolling basis until all spots are filled. Internship time frame and hours are flexible and can be adjusted to accommodate class/work schedules.
     applications for the current fall and winter semester at our Washington, D.C. office. Interns' responsibilities will vary.
Applicants must be motivated, professional, dependable and hold strong written and verbal communication skills.
Responsibilities include, but are not limited to, answering phones, corresponding with constituents, leading U.S. Capitol tours, attending Congressional hearings, assisting the legislative staff, and participating in a legislative project. Successful candidates will be mature, personable, detail-oriented, and self-starters.
The hours may be flexible to accommodate students' course schedules, but generally run 8:30 a.m. to 5:30 p.m. when Congress is in session, and 9:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m. when not in session. Internships are available for 6 weeks, 8 weeks, and semester length.
To apply, please send a resume, cover letter, and available start date to Kimberly Hammond at Kimberly.hammond@mail.house.gov
 MEM-489-19
The office of Congressman Ralph Norman (SC-05) is currently seeking
MEM-488-19 The Committee on Education and Labor, Majority is currently seeking undergraduate and graduate interns and fellows for spring of 2020. Specifically we are seeking general undergraduate interns, graduate and legal interns and fellows for the labor policy team, graduate and legal interns and fellows for the
 Page 20 of 25

health policy team and graduate and legal interns and fellows for the oversight team. Interns perform a variety of tasks that support the staff in our legislative and media work.
Legislative tasks may include, but are not limited to: legislative research and fact checking; technical writing including legislation, memos, and speeches; assisting staff in hearing and markup preparation and execution; and attending other hearings, markups, briefings and meetings for the purpose of informing staff and Members as they work to craft legislation and policy proposals. Media tasks may include helping to organize and staff Committee press conferences and assisting with the production of daily news clips.
Applicants who are applying for graduate internships or fellowships should be able to demonstrate academic or professional exposure to the subject matter of the team to which they are applying. Fellows must be participating in an established fellowship program. Applicants should be able to start in January and commit through April/May.
Interested applicants should email their cover letter, resume and internship applicant information form to E&L_Interns&Fellows@mail.house.gov and indicate, in the subject line of the email, to which position they are applying.
Please also include ‘Spring 2020’ in the subject line. If you are applying for a graduate internship or fellowship, please include two short, relevant writing samples in your application materials. Please visit our website at https://edlabor.house.gov/about/internships for more information. Applicants should aim to submit their materials by November 1, 2019.
The Committee on Education and Labor is a legislative office within the U.S. House of Representatives. The Committee has jurisdiction over a broad array of child welfare, education and labor policy areas, including early childhood education, K-12 education, higher education, employer/employee relations, worker safety, and employer provided health care. Representative Robert C. “Bobby” Scott (D-VA) serves as Chairman.
  MEM-486-19
The Office of Congresswoman Brenda L. Lawrence (MI-14) seeks motivated, detail-oriented, and energetic professionals for internships in Washington, DC. Qualified applicants should have strong interpersonal skills, the ability to manage multiple tasks, possess strong writing skills, and demonstrate a solid work ethic.
Responsibilities include but are not limited to:
Answering and screening telephone calls, managing the front office, greeting constituents and visitors, leading Capitol tours, assisting legislative staff with research, attending congressional briefings, participating in hearing preparation, drafting constituent correspondence on a variety of issues, assisting the
 Page 21 of 25

Communications Director with drafting talking points, creating graphics for social media, tracking media coverage, and other duties as necessary.
Full-time and part-time internship positions are available beginning in January 2020.
To apply, please send a resume, cover letter, and brief writing sample to Ryan.Casman@mail.house.gov with the phrase “Internship Application” in the subject line. Please indicate expected start and end dates as well as hours available to work in your cover letter.
  MEM-485-19
Congresswoman Lauren Underwood (IL-14) is delighted to announce spring internship opportunities in her Washington, DC and West Chicago, IL offices. Internships are designed to offer students and recent graduates direct participation in public service through supporting our offices' constituent engagement and services, administrative responsibilities, and research.
Interns' responsibilities will vary. They will be asked to answer phones, assist with correspondence, coordinate and conduct tours, research legislation, assist with constituent casework, and attend hearings and briefings on various issues. Qualified candidates must be friendly, organized, flexible, and possess the ability to multitask in a fast-paced environment.
Spring internships are available from January through mid-May, with start and end dates tailored to accommodate an academic calendar year. Internship hours run from 9:00 a.m. to 6:00 p.m. on weekdays. Please note that interns are expected to work a minimum of 20 hours per week. A limited number of paid positions are available for internship applicants who are not sponsored by outside organizations.
The deadline to apply, for the spring semester is October 31, 2019. Preference will be given to applicants with ties to the Illinois 14th.
To learn more and apply, please click here. (https://underwood.house.gov/services/internships/internship-form)
For questions about internships please call our office (202) 225-2976.
  MEM-484-19
Republican Congressman Rob Wittman (VA-01) is seeking unpaid interns for the Spring 2020 session in his Capitol Hill office. The spring session dates are January 6th- May 15th. The internship schedule is flexible to accommodate classes. Interns will have the opportunity to attend committee hearings and briefings for staff members, assist in the constituent correspondence process, as well as assist with other constituent services.
Responsibilities include: taking phone calls, processing constituent mail, and performing other general office duties. Ideal applicants should be interested in the legislative process, enthusiastic, reliable, and hard-working. Full or part time
 Page 22 of 25

MEM-476-19
internships with flexible schedules are available. Ties to Virginia’s First Congressional District are preferred but not required.
Interested candidates should e-mail their resume and cover letter to Curran.smolinsky@mail.house.gov before November 4th. Please specify what your internship schedule may look like.
  MEM-481-19
The Washington, D.C. Office of Congressman Steve Cohen (D-TN-09) is seeking
   interns for spring 2020. This position offers an opportunity to learn about the U.S. House of Representatives and gain substantive work experience in an exciting and fast-paced office. Internships are offered on a full-time and part-time basis, and stipends are offered based on need and ties to Tennessee’s 9th District. Interns will work for 10-12 weeks (January – May).
Qualifications:
•Demonstrated interest in politics, policy and/or public service.
•Strong communications and writing skills.
•Hard-working, dependable, detail-oriented and professional.
•Ties to Tennessee’s 9th District are a bonus, but not required. Responsibilities:
•Assisting with office administrative tasks including sorting incoming mail, greeting visitors and answering calls.
•Attending briefings, hearings and special events for legislative staff. •Writing constituent response letters and performing legislative research on behalf of the Member and legislative staff.
•Responding to requests from constituents including leading tours of the U.S. Capitol building.
To apply, applicants must send the following materials to Cohen.Internships@mail.house.gov:
•Resume.
•Cover letter.
•Three references.
 The House Committee on Financial Services-Republican Staff is seeking a legal
   intern for the Spring Semester. (Washington, DC) Applicants should be in their second or third year of law school. Although the internship is unpaid, the committee can offer credit. Excellent writing, verbal and organizational skills are essential along with the ability to be a self-starter while working in a fast-paced environment. Job responsibilities include:
•Researching policy issues under the committee’s jurisdiction •Conducting legal research
•Attending briefings and hearings on the Hill
•Drafting memos
•Supporting committee counsel and professional staff members
Page 23 of 25

Please send resume and cover letter to Meg Shannon at
meg.shannon@mail.house.gov
  MEM-475-19
The Democratic Staff of the House Natural Resources Committee is seeking full- time Legislative Interns for the Spring session (Jan-April). Applicants must be organized, detail oriented, and dependable. Above all, we seek interns who are passionate about issues within the Natural Resources Committee’s jurisdiction and demonstrate exceptional interpersonal skills.
A Legislative Internship offers a unique set of opportunities including the chance to attend Committee hearings, markups, briefings, and meetings, in addition to gaining firsthand experience with the legislative process at the Committee level. Primary duties include administrative assistance such as answering phone calls and processing mail, researching natural resources policy issues, and preparing for Committee hearings.
The deadline to apply for the Spring season is Friday November 1st. To apply, address your application materials to Carlyn LeGrant at NRD.Internships@mail.house.gov with the subject line “Spring Legislative Internship Application.” Please include a cover letter, resume, and short writing sample. For more information, visit www.naturalresources.house.gov/contact/internships
   MEM-472-19
The Office of Congressman Doug Lamborn (CO-05) is currently seeking candidates for a paid internship for the 2019 Fall semester in our Washington D.C. office.
Interns will assist the legislative staff by conducting research, answering phones, leading tours, and helping with administrative tasks. Interns will also greet constituents and should be team-oriented and have strong communication skills.
This is a paid internship that provides a truly unique experience to gain experience in a fast-paced office on Capitol Hill. Qualified candidates should submit a resume and cover letter to Wesley.Harkins@mail.house.gov with the subject line saying “Fall Internship”. Colorado ties not necessary but preferred.
  MEM-446-19
The Office of the Representative Linda Sánchez is currently accepting applications for a full-time Spring internship. Ideal candidates will possess excellent communication skills, a strong attention to detail, the ability to work in a fast-paced environment, and a good sense of humor.
Primary responsibilities will include processing mail, greeting visitors, answering phones, leading Capitol tours, attending briefings, drafting memos and constituent correspondence, and assisting staff with various administrative tasks. Southern California ties are preferred, but not required.
 Page 24 of 25

Interested applicants should send a resume, cover letter, a one-page writing sample, and dates of availability in a single PDF to DCInternship.CA38@mail.house.gov with “CA-38 Spring Internship” in the subject line. The application deadline is Friday, November 8th.
  MEM-416-19
The Democratic Staff on the House Education and Labor Committee seeks a health care intern/fellow. This position will work on the health team. Candidates should have familiarity with health policy, including the Affordable Care Act. Knowledge of other statutes and policies within the Committee’s jurisdiction and how they impact health and human services policy is preferred. Prior Hill experience or policy experience is also preferred.
Tasks will include supporting the development of legislation regarding health policy, conducting issue and legislative research, and preparing written materials and legislative analyses. Applicants should be available to start in September 2019 and commit through December 2019.
To apply, applicants must submit the internship applicant information form (https://edlabor.house.gov/about/internships/form), a resume and a short writing sample. The office is an equal opportunity employer and encourages candidates of diverse backgrounds to apply.
Please email resume and writing sample to E&L_Interns&Fellows@mail.house.gov with "Health Policy Intern/Fellow" in the subject line.
            Page 25 of 25
